<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hK3gAKy.png" width="50" alt="Oreo Biscuits"
    title="Something Stupid" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi all,

    This week we bring you a variety of events, including our second Bar Night
    brought to you by Palantir!
    The first batch of tickets for our early AlphaGo screening is now sold out, but
    watch out for our second (and last) batch available to _all Imperial students_,
    which will be available **today** (Tuesday 14/11) at 16.00.

    There's plenty more, so keep reading!
  </text>

  <hr/>
  <text>Our upcoming events:</text>

  <heading>Palantir Extreme Startup</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1842428509401230"
      alias="https://docsoc.co.uk/extreme-startup/" />
    <links>
      <link
        href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/palantir-extreme-startup-tickets-39830884247">
        Tickets (Eventbrite)
      </link>
    </links>
		<text>
      &lt;font color="red"&gt;**Tickets for this event will be available TODAY
      AT 12.00.**&lt;/font&gt;

			Today's critical institutions don't just protect public safety or provide vital
			goods and services—they also deal with astonishing amounts of data. At Palantir,
			we build software that lets organisations integrate and analyse their data to
			solve problems they couldn't before. For example, we're helping our customers
			combat terrorism at home and abroad, investigate and prosecute financial fraud
			rings, offer more credit to retail banking customers, manufacture products
			faster and more safely, and fight violent crime in the world’s great cities. And
			we're just getting started.

			Very often, doing this efficiently requires quick iteration and adaptation to
			customers' requirements, needs and resources. This can only be done effectively
			with a platform that is designed for easy extension and configuration.

			Come join us at our Extreme Startup event and test your engineering skills!
			We'll work on a scenario that Palantir uses internally to train their software
			engineers to develop clean, maintainable and adaptable code.

			Food and drink will be provided at the event. Palantir will also be holding a
			Bar Night afterwards: (see below)
		</text>
  </event>

  <heading>Palantir Bar Night</heading>
  <event location="Metric">
    <facebook id="357500474697963" alias="https://docsoc.co.uk/palantir-bar-night" />
    <text>
      This event follows directly after Palantir's "Extreme Startup" workshop - you
      are encouraged to attend this fantastic event! (see above)

      It's time for DoCSoc's second bar night of the year! This time, we're kindly
      supported by our sponsor Palantir.

      Whether you went to our first bar night or not, this bar night is going to be a
      big one so come along! This time, we will be in Metric.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to any member of the Department
      of Computing. Tokens are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.

      18+ Only - IDs will be checked. You must be a member of DoCSoc before the day of
      the event in order to attend. Computing, JMC, and EIE students are automatically
      DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £15 at docsoc.co.uk/join
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>DoCSoc Breakfast 2</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1905369099792703" />
  </event>

  <heading>Facebook Crush Your Coding Interview Workshop</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1351641428278830" />
  </event>

  <heading>Live with DeepMind: An Early Screening of AlphaGo Movie</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="787130688161502" alias="https://docsoc.co.uk/alphago-movie/" />
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/live-with-deepmind-an-early-screening-of-alphago-movie-tickets-39618186061">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      Make sure you get your hands on a ticket for the incredible opportunity to watch
      an early screening of the AlphaGo documentary, followed by an exclusive Q&amp;A
      session with one of DeepMind's very own software engineers, Julian
      Schrittwieser.

      Tickets for all Imperial students will be available &lt;font color="red"&gt;**TODAY**&lt;/font&gt;, Tuesday 14/11 at 16.00.

      WATCH THE TRAILER: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8tq1C8spV_g

      On March 9, 2016, the worlds of Go and artificial intelligence collided in South
      Korea. The best-of-five-game competition, coined The Deep Mind Challenge Match,
      pitted a legendary Go master against an AI program that was still learning to
      play the world’s most complex board game. AlphaGo chronicles a journey from the
      backstreets of Bordeaux, past the coding terminals of Google DeepMind in London,
      and, ultimately, to the seven-day tournament in Seoul. As the drama unfolds
      before an audience of over 280 million viewers worldwide, more questions emerge:
      What can artificial intelligence reveal about a 3000-year-old game? What will it
      teach us about humanity?

      Directed by Greg Kohs with an original score by Academy Award nominee, Hauschka.
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Academic Reading Groups</heading>
  <text>
    Our second Programming Languages academic reading group is happening &lt;font color="red"&gt;**TODAY**&lt;/font&gt;,
    Tuesday, at 1pm in Huxley room 145. Speakers will be Paul Kelly and Anastasios
    Andronidis (Cristian Cadar's Group).
    Please check the website https://docsoc.co.uk/papers/ the exact agenda.

    Thank you for providing your feedback on our first Programming Languages
    academic reading group. We've looked through this feedback and will allocate
    more question time in forthcoming events by reducing the number of
    speakers to 2.
  </text>

  <heading>BAML Blog Post</heading>
  <sponsor company="baml">
    Our generous sponsor, Bank of America Merrill Lynch, recently made a post on our blog.

    Pooja Gulabani is a Python developer and a project lead in Fixed Income
    Currencies &amp; Commodities Technology at Bank of America Merrill Lynch. She lives
    in North Greenwich, South East London. She writes about *A day in the life of a
    Python developer at Bank of America Merrill Lynch*.

    [Read the Blog Post](https://docsoc.co.uk/articles/2017-11-07-baml-day-in-the-life/).
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoC Careers Talks</heading>
  <text>
    The department are hosting a series of talks on Careers. Hosted in Huxley 311.
    Attendance is optional and on a first-come, first-serve basis, but talks will
    also be on your timetables.

    *Friday 17th November, 13.00-13.45 &amp;mdash; Finding Internships, Insight Weeks,
    Projects and Vacation Opportunities.*&lt;br&gt;
    Advice on sourcing a range of experiential learning opportunities including ways
    to explore the "hidden job market" and forge your own role.

    *Friday 24th November, 13:00-13:45 &amp;mdash; Application Forms - Fact &amp; Fiction.*&lt;br&gt;
    Uncover the mysteries of application forms and learn how to create excellent
    answers to help you secure an interview.

    *Please note that these events are not organised by DoCSoc.*
  </text>

  <heading>Royal Society Milner Award Lecture</heading>
  <event startDate="2017-11-22T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2017-11-22T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="The Royal Society, 6-9 Carlton House Terrace, SW1Y 5AG, London"
    external="true">
    <links>
      <link href="https://royalsociety.org/science-events-and-lectures/2017/11/milner-lecture/">Royal Society</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      The Royal Society is hosting a lecture coinciding with the annual
      presentation of the Milner Award for outstanding achievement in computer
      science research.

      The 2017 Milner Award Lecture will be given by Professor Andrew Zisserman
      FRS, entitled *How can a computer understand what is happening in a
      video?*.
    </text>
  </event>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
