<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Bank of America Technology Panel Discussion" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Bank of America Merrill Lynch reached out to advertise their Technology Panel
    Discussion aimed at those looking for a spring week program place (for
    non-penultimate years) and those looking for a summer internship (penultimate
    years). If you think this might interest you, see below for more details.
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    **Bank of America Merrill Lynch: Technology Panel Discussion**

    Monday 1st October 2018, 16:00 - 18:00.

    To register please click [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/mobile-0/brand-5/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/2972-UK-London-Universities-Technology-Presentation/en-GB)

    Every day is another chance to create. What are you working for?

    Technology touches every part of Bank of America Merrill Lynch and underpins
    each deal we make.  Owing to our investment in leading technology the Global
    Technology and Operations (GT&amp;O) division places growth and success as a
    central part of its strategy. This gives our business the competitive edge
    to solve business problems by delivering high quality and practical solutions.
    Did you know that the banks mainframe environment is the third largest in
    the world?

    Join us on **Monday 1st October** for an insight into Technology roles at
    Bank of America Merrill Lynch.

    You will hear from senior representatives who will demystify the importance
    of technology at an investment bank in a lively panel discussion and provide
    you with the opportunity to learn more about our culture and ethos.

    After the panel discussion you are invited to network with employees over
    drinks and canapes to find out more about their roles and what a career in
    Technology could look like. You’ll also have the chance to network directly
    with our Technology Graduate Recruiter to discuss the various campus programs
    on offer.

    Get Started. Apply Now at: [campus.bankofamerica.com](https://campus.bankofamerica.com)
  </text>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
