<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

	<image width="50"
				 src=""
				 alt=""
				 title="" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
      <!-- Intro Section -->
      We hope everyone had a great night a Fiesta del Revel on Thursday! Now all
      the eyes are on the Leadership Elections: who will be leading Imperial
      College Union and running DoCSoc next year? Don't forget to vote at
      vote.union.ic.ac.uk before Friday 12pm!
      
      This week we will host a Meet the Candidates event at lunchtime as well as
      the NewVoiceMedia Panel and Bar Night which was unfortunately postponed a
      couple of weeks ago!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <!-- Content Section -->


  <heading>DoCSoc: Meet the Candidates</heading>
  <event> 
      <facebook id="139889083496364" />
      <text>
      Nominations are closed, and the manifestos are in. This can only mean
      one thing - it's time to Meet the Candidates! Join us in Huxley 308 from
      1pm to meet the candidates running for all of the positions in DoC. This
      is your chance to ask any questions you may have, and hear more about
      what each candidate is campaigning for! Candidates for DoCSoc and Dep Reps
      will all be present.
      
      Candidates for contested positions: Please turn up and prepare a 1 minute
      speech on why you think you'd be good for the position. After each pitch
      up to 2 questions will be asked by the audience.
      </text>
  </event>


  <heading>NewVoiceMedia: Meet the Engineers + Bar Night</heading>
  <event>
      <facebook id="1967862183542078" />
      <links>
          <link
              href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSenwx_n0-skq4PR94e9ElB4404UOB8yn7izcwAEnXglehV3QA/viewform">
              Submit your Questions! 
          </link>
      </links> 
      <text> What is being a
          software engineer really like?  What does the job involve?  What does
          working in an agile team really involve?  What kinds of problems and
          technical challenges will I be solving?
          
          If you are interested in the answers to the these questions and more,
          NewVoiceMedia will be hosting a panel consisting of several
          professionals with a variety of experience in different roles who will
          be able to give you a flavour for what working in the industry is
          really like while answering these questions and many more. 
          
          If you have any questions you would like to ask the engineers, please
          submit them through the form above.
          
          This event will also be followed
          by a bar night in the Union Bar, an excellent opportunity to ask
          further questions! Please note you will need to have attended the
          workshop in order to come to the bar night. 
      </text>
  </event>



  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Nik.
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
