<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/NwTWnqP.jpg"
    alt="Stack of biscuits on a plate"
    title="Oddly satisfying" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    The past week week was another fun week, with ice skating sessions by the
    Natural History Museum and a great security talk from Facebook.

    In the coming week, we have another social trip (to watch The Book of Mormon),
    followed by two major events: our joint diversity panel event with CGCU on
    Thursday and Google DevFest London on Saturday. Also, Liquidnet have an open
    office on Tuesday, involving casual networking drinks open to all DoCSoc
    members, so if you're looking for a relaxed evening in the City of London,
    this would be a good opportunity to take. Read on for more information!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DevFest Volunteers</heading>
  <text>
    DevFest is _this_ Saturday (1st December)! The event is already sold out, with
    1000 people attending. We need as many hands as possible for this event so
    if you're interested in helping out, join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    group.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Careers Service: CV Reviews</heading>
  <text>
    Looking to get your CV reviewed? The Careers Service has an online review
    system, My CVs, where you can upload your CV, provide details and get feedback
    from the Careers team within three working days.

    To get started, upload your CV under the "My Profile" section of [JobsLive](http://www.imperial.ac.uk/careers/services/jobslive/).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>CO Careers Talk: LinkedIn - Leverage the Power of Social Media</heading>
  <text>
    This Friday, the Careers Service will be holding the last DoC Careers Talk of
    the year, where you'll learn how to make the most of LinkedIn to promote your
    personal brand and network effectively.

    This talk will be held in HXLY 311 on Friday from 13:00 - 13:50.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>CGCU &amp; DoCSoc - Diversity in Engineering</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/SweqIyL.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-29T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-29T22:00:00+00:00"
    location="Clore Lecture Theatre (Huxley)">
    <text>
      **Submit your questions to the panel here: https://goo.gl/3j3e3w **

      Open to all Imperial students!

      CGCU &amp; DoCSoc are very excited to announce our launch event of a brand new diversity initiative!

      We have picked some of the most talented engineers from a range of backgrounds
      and engineering disciplines to feature in a live Q&amp;A panel where they
      will be sharing their experiences and challenges throughout their career.
      This will be followed by a networking reception with drinks and canapés
      where engineers and recruiters will be able to share advice one on one
      with you. These engineers will be from a number of highly influential
      companies, including:

      - Google
      - P&amp;G
      - Bloomberg
      - Lendlease
      - Facebook
      - InterEngineering
      - Microsoft
      - Palantir

      ...and more yet to be announced!

      _Note: Year 12/13 students will also be invited to this event where they
      will benefit from your own experiences during the networking session as
      much as the engineers' attending, should you wish to share. We invite you
      to come and play your part in pushing inclusion to the forefront of our
      engineering disciplines, however of course this is not mandatory._
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/293123184877438/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Google DevFest London 2018</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-12-01T09:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-01T18:30:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London (South Kensington Campus)">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/yHopaE6.jpg" />
    <text>
      DoCSoc is proud to be hosting Google DevFest London on our very own campus
      this year! Read on for more information.

      **Learn the latest in web, mobile, cloud, machine learning and more at the
      UK's largest community organised free conference.**

      GDG London, Google and DoCSoc present GDG Devfest London - a multi-track
      event covering: cloud and machine learning; web; mobile; assistant; codelabs
      and demos.

      To find out more about speakers, topics and agenda, visit devfest.gdg.london

      Don’t miss out on a fun, interesting and informative day of expert speakers,
      demo stands coding labs and much much more.

      You’ll also get the chance to network with experts from Google, Imperial
      College and beyond and learn more from some of the amazing developer
      communities we have in London.

      There will be people taking photographs and potentially filming the event.
      By attending you agree to the possibility of being photographed and filmed
      once inside the venue.

      Thank you for your interest in GDG DevFest London and we look forward to seeing you there!

      (Tickets are sold out, so if you have a ticket but are unable to attend,
      please release your ticket on Eventbrite so someone else can go!)
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/gdg-devfest-london-2018-tickets-50723931645">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/255733691798751">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Liquidnet In-Office Interactive Session: Trading, AI and Augmenting Behavior</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9yqANVy.png" width="80" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-27T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-27T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 21st Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London, EC2A 2EW"
    external="true">
    <text>
      JOIN LIQUIDNET CHIEF DATA SCIENTIST TOM DORIS, PHD. to discuss challenges
      in adoption and adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct
      the methods that were effective in overcoming the obstacles, and review
      similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology
      team, our Recruitment Team and Product Team once the interactive session
      has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-trading-ai-and-augmenting-behavior-tickets-51867766887">Eventbrite</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG WIN Breakfast Sessions for Young Female Talents</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg" />
  <event startDate="2018-12-05T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-05T10:00:00+00:00"
    location="LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London, EC4M 7LS"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Limited spaces available!**

      The **LSEG WIN (Women Inspired Network)** Community aims to provide a
      platform to celebrate female talents within and outside the Group. As part of the
      WIN Campus Taskforce, we’d like to invite a small group of elite female
      students from four top London universities (LSE, UCL, KCL, and Imperial
      College London) to attend our breakfast sessions to understand and explore the
      financial industry with the help of industry leaders and senior executives.

      We are excited to offer this opportunity to young talented female students to
      help them to gain more exposure to financial markets, whilst networking with
      like-minded peers.

      Our last breakfast session is **Alternative Career Options in Finance**, on
      Wednesday, 5 December, 9:00am – 10:00am. For more details, see the PDF attached.

      Location: LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London EC4M 7LS

      If you're interested, email DoCSoc at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and they'll pass your
      details onto us!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>WinC@IC talks: Research Careers in Industry and Academia</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-11-28T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-28T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley Building"
    external="true">
    <text>
      What do you want to do after your research degree? Do you want to learn
      more about the opportunities and challenges of continuing a career in research?
      Two wonderful speakers, Dr Emily Adlam and Dr Victoriia Sharmanska, will
      share their research interests and career paths within industry and academia.

      **The Women in Computing group** at Imperial is thrilled to announce the
      first event of the year with two wonderful speakers, who will share their
      research interests and career paths within industry and academia.

      **Emily Adlam** graduated with a PhD in theoretical physics from the
      University of Cambridge and currently works as a Quantitative Researcher
      G Research, a world-leading tech company that uses machine learning,
      artificial intelligence and big data analytics to predict prices in global
      financial markets.

      **Victoriia Sharmanska** is a Research Fellow in the Department of
      Computing at Imperial, leading the project in 'Deep Understanding of Human
      Behaviour from Video Data: Action Emotion Approach'. Her research interests
      include deep learning methods and cross-modal transfer that are suitable for
      learning from complex visual data.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/wincic-talks-research-careers-in-industry-and-academia-tickets-52830593728">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
