<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="LSEG Talk: Technologies Driving the Financial Markets"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi all!

    Next week, DoCSoc will be hosting a talk by the current Chief Operating and
    Information Officer at the London Stock Exchange Group, Chris Corrado.

    Chris was also the **former CTO of eBay, Deutsche Bank and Merrill Lynch**,
    former CIO at Morgan Stanley and AT&amp;T, former Head of Platform Services
    at UBS, and has been featured by Forbes and Bloomberg. He has a unique (and
    exceptionally sought after) insight of today’s financial markets, and will be
    discussing the technological advancements that will be defining the future of
    financial trading. This talk should be high priority for **anyone who is
    interested in working in or around finance**, or practically any area that
    may be benefited by knowledge of financial markets.

    We will be holding this talk on Monday the 12th of November where there will
    also be ample opportunity to ask questions to Chris and his colleagues from LSEG.

    As usual, **drinks and food will be provided**. For more information, see below!
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bIqMC8v.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-12T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-12T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) will be hosting this talk with the aim
      of helping students understand more about this unique financial services
      business. The keynote speaker is Chris Corrado, LSEG's Chief Operating
      Officer (COO) and Chief Information Officer (CIO).

      This iconic heritage brand can trace its history back to 1698. Today with
      over 4,500 employers and offices in 20 cities globally it leads the world’s
      financial market infrastructure and capital markets as a recognised leader
      in emerging fast-changing financial technology (or FinTech).

      During the presentation you will have ample networking opportunity for
      one-on-ones with recent graduates and senior representatives from the many
      different business areas as well as recruiters. This is a great opportunity
      for you to get the latest technology market knowledge, advice and insight
      into LSEG’s 2019 Graduate and Internship programmes, its cultures, values
      and exciting roles on offer.

      Drinks and food provided. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/284082455563025/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
