<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

	<image width="50"
				 src="https://i.imgur.com/pYfDnUC.jpg"
				 alt="Garibaldi Biscuit"
				 title="Seems like nobody actually cares about suggesting biscuits. We've had suggestions at a rate of one per week, which is not exactly great :(" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hello Everybody,

    Welcome to yet another week, and again we have much to share!

    If you were unlucky in getting a *Fiesta del Revel* ticket this past week do
    not fear, as our biggest batch yet will be on sale this Thursday 22nd at
    13.30!

    Also don't forget that the nominations for elections are closing on Sunday
    25th February at 23.59! If you're considering to run and would like to see
    how we operate, feel free to join us at our fortnightly committee meeting
    this Wednesday 21st February in Huxley 217 at 19.00. More information below.

    You may have seen the NewVoiceMedia event this week advertised on
    Facebook. Unfortunately we will have to postpone this event as the venue was
    unavailable for the date. We'll let you know in due course, both on Facebook
    and through the digest.

    Also check out the opportunities that our amazing sponsors CapitalOne and EF
    are offering below!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Fiesta del Revel</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="372487326558223" />
    <links>
      <link href="https://revel.london/">Countdown</link>
      <link href="https://fiestadelrevel.eventbrite.co.uk/">Placeholder Tickets</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      **The LAST BATCH will be released THIS THURSDAY 22ND AT 13.30!**&lt;br/&gt;
      As in the Standard release batch, you will need to secure **Eventbrite
      Placeholder Tickets** in order to purchase the actual tickets on the
      Union's website. Check the Facebook event for more information on the day.

      It's back with a vengeance. DoCSoc, EESoc and RCSU have come together to
      give you an unforgettable night.

      First we took the rooftops, then showed the Cirque how to party. This year
      we bring you the London skyline from Aqua Nueva - a Spanish bar high on
      class, TWO roof terraces where you can enjoy your glass! What's that?
      Drinks? We've got you covered. Enough beer, wine and soft drinks to keep
      the party rolling and some bowl foods to keep you from rolling. Dress to
      impress in your black tie suit or cocktail dress, and keep an eye out for
      our photographer!
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>Committee Meeting and Elections</heading>
  <text>
    Come join us at our fortnightly General Committee Meeting! The next one is
    taking place on Wednesday 21st February at 19.00, in Huxley Room 217.

    Especially if you are considering or have [nominated
    yourself](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/leadership-elections-2018)
    for a DoCSoc Committee role in the Leadership Elections 2018, this is a
    great opportunity to see how the committee operates.

    **Note that if you have not yet nominated yourself for a role, the deadline
    is 23.59, SUNDAY 25th FEBRUARY.**

    If you have any questions please email docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Entrepreneur First Seeking Founders!</heading>
  <sponsor company="ef">
    Do you know what you're doing after Imperial?

    Entrepreneur First's early deadline is coming up on the 31st of March. They
    are offering all DocSoc members a fast-track application if you [apply
    now](https://www.joinef.com/apply-now?utm_source=utm_campaign%3Dimperial&amp;utm_campaign=DocSoc%20Breakfast).

    EF are the world's leading company builder; funding you to build your own
    tech company from scratch, pre-team and pre-idea.

    If you'd like to be the first to hear about any future EF opportunities,
    workshops or events, click
    [here](https://entrepreneur-first.typeform.com/to/GYRChf).
  </sponsor>

  <heading>Capital One Early Careers</heading>
  <sponsor company="capital_one">
    **Say hello to your future.**

    In the digital age, money and the way people interact with it is evolving.
    At Capital One we're all about Reimagining Money and putting technology to
    work to make money make sense for our customers. There's lots of ways you
    can be part of this, and we have opportunities across our Internship and
    Graduate Programmes.

    Our **Software Academy** will give you the opportunity to work with
    cutting-edge technologies, including Big Data, Cloud and Cyber Security that
    allow us to deliver great experiences for our customers. And our **Business
    Analysts** change the way we do business; creating ground-breaking
    strategies to launch new products, win new customers and help people stay on
    track with credit.

    The work you do here is going to matter, so much so that we'll give you a
    competitive salary of up to £40,000 for graduate positions and £18,000
    (pro-rata) for internships. Our internship programme is for students who
    intend on graduating in 2019.

    Don't just imagine the possibilities, explore them. Our programmes are
    filling up fast and with the closing day next Friday 2nd March, you won't
    want to miss out.

    [Apply now](https://ad.doubleclick.net/ddm/clk/414179192;215035247;c).
  </sponsor>


  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Darth Plagueis The Wise.
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
