<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Entrepreneur First - Join Now"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi all!

    Entrepreneur First have reached out with details about their startup programme.
    Their deadline for early applications is fast approaching.

    EF's cohorts aren't made up of over-aspirational entrepreneurs, but instead,
    highly qualified engineers, scientists and others from all walks of life, so
    if you're a final year student (especially Masters and PhDs with specialised
    skills), this may especially interest you.
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <sponsor company="ef">
    **Want to build a startup? Join Entrepreneur First! Early deadline in seven days.**

    Entrepreneur First exists to support the world's most ambitious individuals
    to build the most important companies. They run a bespoke programme, the first
    of its kind in the world, that funds individuals to find a co-founder, create
    a high-growth tech company from scratch, and raise investment. Magic Pony
    Technology is EF’s largest exit to date, having been acquired by Twitter for
    a reported $150m. Magic Pony’s founders, Rob Bishop and Zehan Wang, studied
    together at Imperial, but didn't meet until they both joined EF's cohort in 2014.

    EF are on the hunt for their next cohort of 100 exceptional people who are
    ready to become startup founders. If you are finishing your PhD or Masters
    soon and want to build a company, you should apply. You don't need an idea,
    just your skills and commitment. The next cohort kicks off in **April 2019**, and
    their early deadline for DoCSoc members is **Sunday 25 Nov**.

    You can apply [here](https:/www.joinef.com/apply-now) using this link and you'll have your application considered
    ahead of everyone else.
    To have a chat with someone from the team there, email ambica@joinef.com.

    Find our more at: https://www.joinef.com/
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
