<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/UXACn8D.jpg"
    alt="Picture of a cup of tea with two cigarette biscuits leaning against the tea plate"
    title="Cigarettes Russes"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone! Here's yet another digest.

    First off, thanks to everyone who came to the Welcome Bar Night last Thursday.
    We had a great attendance of 350 members and hope everyone who went enjoyed
    it! For those who missed it, no worries - there will be many more bar nights
    to come (including one with Netcraft _this coming Thursday_!).

    To reiterate from the last digest, all of our industrial events are catered
    (usually with pizza). If you have any dietary requirements and if you are
    planning on attending an event, please make sure you [get in touch](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk)
    at least two days before the event to tell us. You can use the same email address to
    give us any feedback about our events as well!

    This digest is packaged with information and events, so stay tuned and read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Mums and Dads Subsidy</heading>
  <text>
    Part of the Mums and Dads scheme but haven't met up with your family for food and drinks
    yet? DoCSoc are subsidising up to £20 for families to get to know each other!
    If you're a parent, you're eligible to claim £20 back for a family meetup,
    no matter whether you're introducing your children to curly fries at the Union or
    hiring a squash court at Ethos.

    To get the reimbursement, you'll need to be sure to ask for and hold onto a
    receipt and make a claim over [eActivities](https://eactivities.union.ic.ac.uk/training/articles/13) to CGCU DoCSoc (605).

    Feel free to [get in touch](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk) if you have any questions.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Year Representatives</heading>
  <text>
    In our first digest of the year, we introduced your departmental representatives (dep reps),
    responsible for representing Computing, JMC and EIE students to the department.
    With Autumn elections now over, your _year_ representatives (year reps) have now
    been announced!

    Academic year reps are responsible for issues relating to your year group
    (e.g., work not returned on time, too much coursework being scheduled at one
    time, etc.). Wellbeing year reps are people you can speak to confidentially
    on a personal level. Feel free to contact them over Messenger and they will
    be happy to get back to you!

    There's a lot of representatives to list, so we encourage you to take a brief
    look at your year reps:
    - [Computing](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/your-representatives/a-to-z/computing-ug)
    - [JMC](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/your-representatives/a-to-z/jmc-ug)
    - [EIE](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/your-representatives/a-to-z/electronic-information-engineering-ug)

    Also, in case you forgot, here are our dep reps:
    - **Computing**: Martin Zlocha ([email](mailto:dep-rep@doc.ic.ac.uk))
    - **Joint Maths and Computing (JMC)**: Rachel Mekhtieva Lee and Fawaz Shah ([email](mailto:dep-rep@doc.ic.ac.uk))
    - **Electronic and Information Engineering (EIE)**: Willem van der Schoot (Academic, [email](willem.van-der-schoot16@imperial.ac.uk)) and Mayank Surana (Wellbeing, [email](mayank.surana16@imperial.ac.uk))
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    Searching for internships or placements? Check out our Sponsors Portal, where
    you can find out more details about our sponsors, read their blog posts and
    see their open internship/placement positions. You can also upload your CV
    and directly apply to all of our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Competition Winners</heading>
  <text>
    At the Welcome Bar Night, we announced the winners of different competitions
    we hosted over the past few months. Here are the winners again!

    At Freshers' Fair, we gave freshers the chance to compete in a **typing competition**
    to win great prizes. The winners are:
    - TODO
    - TODO
    - TODO

    Last year, we entered those who completed the **End of Year Survey** into a raffle
    for a £50 Amazon voucher. The winners of the raffle are:
    - TODO

    During the Mums and Dads meeting, we created a bingo-like checklist. The winners
    of the **Mums and Dads Checklist** won an additional subsidy to spend at a family
    meetup. The winners are:
    - TODO

    If you have not collected your prize please get in touch with us and we will
    give it to you at a convenient time!

    Thanks for everyone who participated in these events and congratulations to
    those who won!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir - Interpreting Law and Policy as Technologists</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-22T18:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-22T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qkZxAgO.jpg" />
    <text>
      In May 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) became one
      of the most important reforms of data protection law worldwide. Strangely,
      this law did not come with technical specifications. Join Paula Kift, of
      the Privacy and Civil Liberties team at Palantir, for a workshop that aims
      to highlight for those interested in the intersection of law and technology
      how they can shape it in practice, while tackling some of the most important
      privacy challenges of our time.

      Food and drinks provided!

      **Please RSVP using the link provided** before clicking 'Going' on Facebook.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://imperialpcl1022.splashthat.com/">RSVP</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/337105763726925/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Netcraft - Cryptocurrencies for Fun and Profit</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-25T18:15:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-25T20:30:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qImfYjE.jpg" />
    <text>
      Rolling your own cryptocurrency: what could possibly go wrong?

      Over the past few years, the popularity and value of cryptocurrencies,
      such as Bitcoin, has soared. Bitcoin has also spawned a number of spinoff
      currencies, known as 'altcoins'. Some altcoins provide genuine technical
      improvements over Bitcoin; however, most are forks with minimal changes -
      designed to be pump and dump schemes to enrich their creators.

      In July 2018 Imperial College jointly published a report written by Prof
      William Knottenbelt with eToro, a cryptocurrency exchange. The report was
      widely regarded by the press to be a puff piece promoting cryptocurrencies,
      poorly disguised as academic research. The Financial Times dubbed it "cryptopuff".

      Not wanting to miss out on the fun (or profit!), Netcraft has designed its
      own cryptocurrency and named it Cryptopuff in tribute to Prof Knottenbelt's
      report. However, Cryptopuff was written in a rush during a single weekend -
      who knows what vulnerabilities may be lurking in its depths?

      Your challenge, after a short talk illustrating the concepts, is to compete
      against your peers to earn as much Cryptopuff as possible.

      You'll need to find and exploit vulnerabilities to steal coins from your
      peers, while also defending your own node against attack to protect your
      own coins. Or perhaps you could sell 'zero-day' vulnerabilities to other
      teams rather than doing the dirty work of exploiting them yourself.

      The team with the greatest number of coins at the end of the event will be
      declared the winner.

      To take part, bring your own laptop with a web browser and an SSH client
      (e.g. Putty http://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/putty/ for Windows
      users; OpenSSH for Linux/Mac users)

      **There will a free bar night at the Union Bar after the competition.**
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2190799097619225/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Netcraft Breakfast</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/roLL583.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-10-26T08:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-26T10:00:00+01:00"
    location="HXLY 341/342">
    <text>
      Get your Friday off to a great start with DoCSoc's first free breakfast of
      the year, generously sponsored by Netcraft! Come along to Huxley 341/342 any time
      from 8am-10am and enjoy a great pre-lecture breakfast with other DoCSoc members.

      If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few days beforehand!

      You can learn more about Netcraft at https://www.netcraft.com!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2203250796371790/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Tech Talk @ BlackRock's Offices</heading>
  <sponsor company="blackrock" />
  <event startDate="2018-10-24T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-24T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="BlackRock London Office"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Do you want to have a career that’s exciting, rewarding and full of
      possibilities? Are you driven by change and making an impact?**

      Join us at this Technology @ BlackRock event to learn how you can put your
      ideas to work at one of the largest FinTech firms in the world!

      At this event we will be delivering a Tech Talk on Continuous Deployment/Containerisation
      and Cloud. You’ll also hear more about our opportunities, network with
      current BlackRock employees and receive advice on how to make a successful
      application!

      Since our inception in 1988, we’ve grown from an entrepreneurial start-up
      into the world’s largest investment manager, with more than $6 trillion of
      assets under management, by putting technology and continuous innovation
      at the heart of our business.

      Join us and learn how you can make an even bigger impact.

      Upload your CV [here](https://blackrock.tal.net/vx/lang-en-GB/mobile-0/brand-3/xf-16a200d7d3fb/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/2817-Technology-BlackRock-London/en-GB) to register your interest in attending this event.

      **Registrations will close on Monday 22 October.**

      _Economy Travel Expenses from outside London (from £25 up to £100) will be
      reimbursed. Taxi fares will not be reimbursed._
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://blackrock.tal.net/vx/lang-en-GB/mobile-0/brand-3/xf-16a200d7d3fb/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/2817-Technology-BlackRock-London/en-GB">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>
  <hr />

  <heading>Bank of America "Discover Technology" Office Visit</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-29T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-10-29T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Bank of America Merrill Lynch Offices"
    external="true" >
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/RY5d1rC.jpg" />
    <text>
      Bank of America Merrill Lynch are looking for **first year students**
      interested in their Spring Week and **penultimate year students** interested in
      internships to come along to their offices and learn more about the Bank and
      their tech (drinks and canapés provided!).

      ---

      Technology touches every part of Bank of America Merrill Lynch and underpins
      each deal we make.  Owing to our investment in leading technology the Global
      Technology division places growth and success as a central part of its strategy.
      This gives our business the competitive edge to solve business problems
      delivering high quality and practical solutions. Did you know that the
      banks mainframe environment is the third largest in the world?

      Join us for our exclusive **‘Discover Technology’ event** at our St Paul’s
      offices for Imperial students only on **Monday 29 October 6pm-8pm**.

      During the event you will find out more about Bank of America Merrill Lynch
      and the important role our Technology division has in the running of our
      business. We’ll have a number of representatives on hand to give you an
      insight into our campus programs, what we look for in students, and what
      it would be like to work for us – in addition to an opening presentation
      from a senior Director, you’ll also have the chance to network over drinks
      and canapés with Imperial alumni as well as get a tour of our offices!

      This is a fantastic opportunity for students who have either already applied
      for one of our programs and would like to follow up with a networking opportunity,
      or to those considering whether to apply – this event should help you in putting
      in the best application you can.

      Spaces are limited, so apply as soon as possible!

      Please click [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-5/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/3331-UK-Imperial-College-Discover-Technology-at-Bank-of-America-Merrill-Lynch/en-GB) to register for this event.

    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-5/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/3331-UK-Imperial-College-Discover-Technology-at-Bank-of-America-Merrill-Lynch/en-GB">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Google DevFest London 2018</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-12-01T09:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-12-01T18:30:00+01:00"
    location="Imperial College London (South Kensington Campus)">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/yHopaE6.jpg" />
    <text>
      DoCSoc is proud to be hosting Google DevFest London on our very own campus
      this year! Read on for more information.

      **Learn the latest in web, mobile, cloud, machine learning and more at the
      UK's largest community organised free conference.**

      GDG London, Google and DoCSoc present GDG Devfest London - a multi-track
      event covering: cloud and machine learning; web; mobile; assistant; codelabs
      and demos.

      To find out more about speakers, topics and agenda, visit devfest.gdg.london

      Don’t miss out on a fun, interesting and informative day of expert speakers,
      demo stands coding labs and much much more.

      You’ll also get the chance to network with experts from Google, Imperial
      College and beyond and learn more from some of the amazing developer
      communities we have in London.

      There will be people taking photographs and potentially filming the event.
      By attending you agree to the possibility of being photographed and filmed
      once inside the venue.

      Thank you for your interest in GDG DevFest London and we look forward to seeing you there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/gdg-devfest-london-2018-tickets-50723931645">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/255733691798751">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="palantir">
    Palantir is hiring across all roles in London and beyond! We are looking for
    strong engineers to help us continue helping the worlds most important institutions
    solve their most challenging problems using data. Find out more here: https://www.palantir.com/students/
  </sponsor>

  <hr />

  <heading>Internships at Artificial</heading>
  <sponsor company="artificiallabs">
    Interested in working in software engineering or data science? Artificial is
    hiring so if you are, be sure to read on!

    We're a start-up in the insurance technology sector. Our mission is to make
    the insurance process frictionless. We do this by enabling insurance companies
    to leverage innovative technology so they can make their customers happier,
    act more efficiently, and scale faster. We are dedicated to building the
    advanced and flexible machine learning enabled insurance platform to cater
    for insurers, brokers and underwriters of all sizes and sectors.

    We're looking to recruit interns for summer 2019 in software engineering and
    data science. Check us out at https://artificial.io/ and apply at https://artificial.workable.com/.
  </sponsor>

  <hr />

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
