<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/N5zo1QB.jpg"
    alt="A selection of very festive biscuits"
    title="A festive selection of biscuits with Christmas around the corner!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    We made it! Welcome to the last week of term. With December exams and code
    reviews, there's no doubt most of us will be working right until the end.
    However, that means there's more reason to celebrate, so if you're still around
    on Saturday, join us for another DoCSoc Bar Night! More details below.

    If you're a second year, congratulations on finishing Pintos! It's time to
    have some well-deserved rest. If you're a third or fourth year with the next
    week being the final hurdle of the term, we wish you good luck with your exams!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Pintos Glasses</heading>
  <text>
    If you're a second year who missed their Pintos glass collection, we'll be
    doing a final pickup session at 2pm on Tuesday in labs (after the final OS
    lecture).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Merch</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/XFjBZW5.png" />
  <text>
    Head on over to the Union's website to buy DoCSoc-branded hoodies, T-shirts,
    and beanies. They will be available on the shop until 6pm on Wednesday 26th
    December, of course at rock-bottom prices thanks to our generous sponsors.

    Available here: https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/club-society-project-products/computing-products
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Organisers</heading>
  <text>
    This year, we're back bigger than ever for IC Hack 19, targeting 400 attendees.
    With help needed in Logistics, Hacker Experience, Sponsorship, Marketing
    and more, IC Hack 19 is an opportunity to go beyond the standard role of a
    volunteer and become a _core organiser_ of a major hackathon. For more information,
    join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    group.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Christmas Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/KTzAWzP.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-12-15T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-15T23:00:00+00:00"
    location="Union Bar">
    <text>
      DoCSoc's third and final bar night of the term, and final bar night of 2018
      is here - the Christmas Bar Night!

      We'll be enjoying free drinks (alcoholic or not), celebrating our successes
      throughout the year, and looking forward to 2019 and beyond! Don't miss it!

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to DoCSoc members. Tokens
      are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks. Note that this event
      is on a SATURDAY - the day after term ends.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/528361920996868/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Wishing everyone a festive holiday,
  </sign>
</email>
