<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/T18dBBr.jpg"
    alt="Row of Leibniz biscuits"
    title="This is what happens when you let mathematicians name biscuits" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Another busy week has gone by, with the events over the past week including
    the Game AI workshop, Bloomberg CodeCon Qualifiers and our first off-campus
    social event this year, DoCSoc Gets Locked in a Room! Thanks to everyone who
    attended and as always, thanks to everyone who helped out at these events.

    Over the next week, we're holding a talk and a coding challenge with two of
    our sponsors, LSEG and G-Research, which are events not to be missed!
    Additionally, preparations for Google DevFest London and IC Hack '19 are
    well underway and we're in search for organisers and volunteers. For more
    details, read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DevFest Volunteers and IC Hack '19 Organisers</heading>
  <text>
    This academic year, we're not only hosting our flagship hackathon, IC Hack
    (26/27th Jan 2019), but also Google DevFest London (1st Dec 2018)!

    Both events are fast-approaching. For IC Hack in particular, we're looking
    for organisers taking on responsibilities beyond the standard volunteering
    role.

    To get involved, join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    Facebook group and learn more about organising IC Hack [here](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/permalink/2300633930262198/).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG - Technologies Driving the Financial Markets</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bIqMC8v.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-12T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-12T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Next week, DoCSoc will be hosting a talk by the current Chief Operating and
      Information Officer at the London Stock Exchange Group, Chris Corrado.

      Chris was also the **former CTO of eBay, Deutsche Bank and Merrill Lynch**,
      former CIO at Morgan Stanley and AT&amp;T, former Head of Platform Services
      at UBS, and has been featured by Forbes and Bloomberg. He has a unique (and
      exceptionally sought after) insight of today’s financial markets, and will be
      discussing the technological advancements that will be defining the future of
      financial trading. This talk should be high priority for **anyone who is
      interested in working in or around finance**, or practically any area that
      may be benefited by knowledge of financial markets.

      This iconic heritage brand can trace its history back to 1698. Today with
      over 4,500 employers and offices in 20 cities globally it leads the world’s
      financial market infrastructure and capital markets as a recognised leader
      in emerging fast-changing financial technology (or FinTech).

      During the presentation you will have ample networking opportunity for
      one-on-ones with recent graduates and senior representatives from the many
      different business areas as well as recruiters. This is a great opportunity
      for you to get the latest technology market knowledge, advice and insight
      into LSEG’s 2019 Graduate and Internship programmes, its cultures, values
      and exciting roles on offer.

      Drinks and food provided. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/284082455563025/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>G-Research Coding Challenge</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/kgo5FRo.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-15T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-15T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      Calling all software engineering enthusiasts that enjoy a bit of healthy
      competition!

      G-Research is a leading quantitative research and technology company. By
      using the latest scientific techniques, we produce world-beating predictive
      research and build advanced technology to analyse the world's data.

      Join us for the G-Research Coding Challenge where you will compete in
      teams in a series of progressively difficult challenges. Open to absolutely
      anyone, you will be competing in teams of 2-3 to build a natural language
      calculation engine (no prior NLP experience required). The challenges will
      cover things like evaluation of arithmetic expressions to unit conversions
      and equation solving.

      We will allocate teams when you arrive, you don't need to find a team
      beforehand - but feel free to bring your own team if you would like. To
      take part, you will need to bring at least one laptop per team.

      There will be a live leaderboard up on the projector to give all teams the
      opportunity to see where they are placing throughout the challenge. 1st,
      2nd and 3rd place (decided by a point system) will win prizes!
      Following the event there will be pizza and a chance for you to informally
      talk with our employees about internships, graduate roles and life at G-Research.

      Languages for the challenges - .NET Core 2 , Java and Maven or Python 3
      with client starter kits provided when you login.

      Registration beforehand is optional. To register, please email graduates@gresearch.co.uk
      detailing whether you are registering as an individual or a team.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/277450032912641/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Facebook Women Create Workshop</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/F82Obs2.png" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-26T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-26T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Facebook, 1 Rathbone Square, Fitzrovia, W1T1FB"
    external="true">
    <text>
      Hi there!

      Come learn how to put your best foot forward at this Crush Your Coding
      Interview Workshop by Facebook.

      This presentation will be delivered by one of Facebook’s Software Engineers
      and will cover:
      - How to walk through an algorithm problem,
      - How to brainstorm solutions,
      - How to discuss the problem with your interviewer,
      - How to write (and test) code on a whiteboard.

      The talk will finish with a panel of Engineers from Software, Solutions,
      FrontEnd and Product exploring their life at Facebook, how they got to where
      they are and any tips they have for future candidates.

      Lastly, we will have 30 minutes of informal networking with food and drink.

      Sign-up link: https://womencreate-codinginterviewworkshop.splashthat.com/

      Visit this link to prepare: https://www.facebook.com/careers/life/preparing-for-your-software-engineering-interview-at-facebook

      We look forward to seeing you there!

      The Facebook Team

    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://womencreate-codinginterviewworkshop.splashthat.com/">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Liquidnet In-Office Interactive Session: Trading, AI and Augmenting Behavior</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9yqANVy.png" width="80" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-27T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-27T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 21st Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London, EC2A 2EW"
    external="true">
    <text>
      JOIN LIQUIDNET CHIEF DATA SCIENTIST TOM DORIS, PHD. to discuss challenges
      in adoption and adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct
      the methods that were effective in overcoming the obstacles, and review
      similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology
      team, our Recruitment Team and Product Team once the interactive session
      has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-trading-ai-and-augmenting-behavior-tickets-51867766887">Eventbrite</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Google DevFest London 2018</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-12-01T09:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-01T18:30:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London (South Kensington Campus)">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/yHopaE6.jpg" />
    <text>
      DoCSoc is proud to be hosting Google DevFest London on our very own campus
      this year! Read on for more information.

      **Learn the latest in web, mobile, cloud, machine learning and more at the
      UK's largest community organised free conference.**

      GDG London, Google and DoCSoc present GDG Devfest London - a multi-track
      event covering: cloud and machine learning; web; mobile; assistant; codelabs
      and demos.

      To find out more about speakers, topics and agenda, visit devfest.gdg.london

      Don’t miss out on a fun, interesting and informative day of expert speakers,
      demo stands coding labs and much much more.

      You’ll also get the chance to network with experts from Google, Imperial
      College and beyond and learn more from some of the amazing developer
      communities we have in London.

      There will be people taking photographs and potentially filming the event.
      By attending you agree to the possibility of being photographed and filmed
      once inside the venue.

      Thank you for your interest in GDG DevFest London and we look forward to seeing you there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/gdg-devfest-london-2018-tickets-50723931645">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/255733691798751">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG WIN Breakfast Sessions for Young Female Talents</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg" />
  <event startDate="2018-12-05T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-05T10:00:00+00:00"
    location="LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London, EC4M 7LS"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Limited spaces available!**

      The **LSEG WIN (Women Inspired Network)** Community aims to provide a
      platform to celebrate female talents within and outside the Group. As part of the
      WIN Campus Taskforce, we’d like to invite a small group of elite female
      students from four top London universities (LSE, UCL, KCL, and Imperial
      College London) to attend our breakfast sessions to understand and explore the
      financial industry with the help of industry leaders and senior executives.

      We are excited to offer this opportunity to young talented female students to
      help them to gain more exposure to financial markets, whilst networking with
      like-minded peers.

      Our last breakfast session is **Alternative Career Options in Finance**, on
      Wednesday, 5 December, 9:00am – 10:00am. For more details, see the PDF attached.

      Location: LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London EC4M 7LS

      If you're interested, email DoCSoc at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and they'll pass your
      details onto us!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
