<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="70"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/L2vMIuM.png"
    alt="Pie Chart of Last Week's Biscuit Vote"
    title="Thanks for voting, people who care about the biscuit &lt;3!" />

  <hr />

  <text>
    Hello everyone,

    Welcome to another week of the DoCSoc digest!

    This week, we bring you a Microsoft Cognitive Services workshop and UROP
    101!

    **Also, you can sign up for our very own Valentine's Service, only until
    23.59 on Thursday 8th February. If there is someone special who you would
    like to send a rose and message to,
    [sign up here](https://docsoc.co.uk/valentines).**

    Last week, over 70 of you voted and decided the future of the biscuit.
    From now on, the bottom of the digest will include a link to a form where
    biscuits for the next week may be suggested. The biscuit that we send out
    remains at the discretion of the DoCSoc committee, but your suggestions
    should really help. Plus, we'll credit you for the suggestion next to the
    biscuit form link!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Microsoft Cognitive Services: Hands On Workshop</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="451262598634020" />
    <text>
      Come along to learn about Microsoft Cognitive Services, including the
      Custom Vision AI Service. After learning about these services, there will
      be a hands on workshop so you can see for yourself how easy it is to build
      and deploy your projects using these services!

      All experience levels welcome and please make sure you bring your laptop
      with you. Food and drink will be provided at the event and there will also
      be giveaways!
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>UROP 101</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1980894172231621" />
  </event>

  <heading>Docker Workshop</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="935309229966009" />
    <text>
      Docker is a tool designed to make it easier to create, deploy, and run
      applications by using containers. Containers allow a developer to package
      up an application with all of the parts it needs, such as libraries and
      other dependencies, and ship it all out as one package.

      This workshop is targeted to those who want to learn about the basics of
      Docker. If you are taking Distributed Algorithms (CO347), this workshop
      will definitely help you with the course. You may also encounter Docker in
      some format during a placement or internship this summer..

      This workshop will be hosted by Abhinav Mishra.
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>The Valentine's Bar Night</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1607380125981757" />
    <text>
      It's time for the first Bar Night of 2018! Once again, we'll be meeting in
      Metric at 7pm for an evening of free drinks and great conversation.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to any member of DoCSoc.
      Tokens are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>Internship 101</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="140931969937020" />
  </event>

  <heading>JetBrains: Kotlin Hands-On</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="166048430696844" />
  </event>

  <hr />
  <text>
    And later we'll bring you...
  </text>

  <heading>DoCSoc hosts Google Hash Code</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="397017594079193" />
    <links>
      <link href="https://hashcode.withgoogle.com">Tickets</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2018</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1698424526881229" />
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>3Hack 2.0</heading>
  <event external="true">
    <facebook id="742171662642922" />
    <links>
      <link href="http://www.3hack.co.uk/">Website</link>
      <link
        href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/3hack-20-powered-by-microsoft-tickets-42676282911">Tickets</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      This is an open-ended hackathon focused on bringing together students
      interested in one of the 3 major areas: graphic designing,
      entrepreneurship, and engineering/programming to create something new
      while building connections with one another.

      Coming alone on the day of the hack? Not to worry, we can help you form a
      team on the day. Don't worry if you lack experience, we will have plenty
      of mentors to help and take this opportunity as a chance to learn!
      Not only is it a great chance to create something special, but one to
      network with our mentors/organisers which consists of Microsoft seniors,
      Internet entrepreneurs, successful mobile-app developers and students from
      other societies.

      Organised by Microsoft Student Partners of Imperial College London.
    </text>
  </event>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Biscuit Voters!
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
