<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Jump Trading FPGA Hardware Internships and Full-Time Opportunities" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Our sponsor, Jump Trading, have got in touch to advertise their FPGA internship
    and full-time opportunities. If this interests you, read on!
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <image
    src="https://i.imgur.com/5h3xQfF.png"
    width="50"/>
  <text>
    We’ve been fortunate to hire several Imperial students over the past several
    years ([Jaden Liu](https://www.linkedin.com/in/jaden-jianxiong-liu-56a86015/)
    and [Dylan McCormick](https://www.linkedin.com/in/dylan-mccormick-17a81676/))
    and we’re looking forward to meeting more students for opportunities in 2018 and beyond.

    Our FPGA team is looking to grow and we’re hoping to hire several interns and
    new grads. If you're intrigued by the intersection of software and hardware,
    and are looking for a challenge, please consider our job postings below.

    **APPLY TO JUMP TRADING**

    FPGA ENGINEER INTERNSHIP - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1045825

    FPGA ENGINEER NEW GRAD - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1044275

    **ABOUT JUMP TRADING**

    At Jump Trading, you will find a group of driven, dynamic people focused on
    researching, interpreting and capitalizing on the global trading markets.
    Headquartered in Chicago since 1999, Jump has expanded over the years as a
    global operation with offices in London, Singapore, New York, and Shanghai.

    We are a privately-funded company that is owned and managed by trading
    professionals who have set high standards around trust and leadership in a
    quantitative trading environment. We trade across all major asset classes on
    multitudes of electronic exchanges around the world, with a strong track
    record of success through all market conditions.

    Our casual atmosphere, culture of continuous learning and innovation, and
    philosophy of rewarding outstanding performance based on merit rather than
    tenure or title has attracted brilliant people from around world. We value
    our people at Jump and pride ourselves on being a diverse set of individuals.
    Employees have notable backgrounds from the trading industry, Silicon Valley,
    tech companies, startups, world renowned research labs, top tier Universities,
    and PhD programs.

    **ABOUT THE FPGA ENGINEER TEAM**

    We’re looking for brilliant engineering talent to join our FPGA team in London
    that is building next-generation, ultra-low-latency systems to power trading
    with machine learning and other algorithms on a global scale.

    This is an opportunity to work on complex problems around networking, high
    performance computing, and real-time acceleration where we can't just use
    off-the-shelf hardware.

    You’ll work alongside a small team of experienced engineers, led by [Steve Perry](https://www.linkedin.com/in/stevenwperry/),
    who all came to Jump from leading companies in FPGAs, semiconductors,
    networking cards, and more… as well as PhDs from top FPGA research labs
    around the world.

    No prior knowledge of finance or trading is necessary. We’ll give you the
    training that you’ll need.

    **WHAT YOU’LL NEED**

    - **Undergraduate or Graduate** concentration in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, or related areas
    - **Experience** with FPGA or other hardware/systems design and development
    - **Experience** with RTL (SystemVerilog/Verilog/VHDL)
    - **Previous internship** experience in hardware or low-level software engineering
    - **Experience** with C, C++, or Python
    - **Passion for** solving complex problems and ability to draw upon knowledge
    and experience from a variety of technical areas to produce extremely high-performance solutions

    **OTHER HELPFUL AND RELATED EXPERIENCE**

    -	Excellent marks in courses such as computer architecture, digital design,
    design verification
    -	Any programming close to the metal with CPU, GPU, microprocessors, etc.
    -	Linux kernel and driver programming
    - lowRISC or RISC-V
    - CocoTB, Chisel, Opencore, or Bluespec
    - HLS or OpenCL
    - Robotics, Telecommunications, or High Speed Networking
    - Raspberry Pi or Arduino

    ---

    Questions? Email bmcnamara@jumptrading.com

  </text>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
