<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/b13LgID.jpg"
    alt="Stack of biscuits on a plate"
    title="I can't think of an alt text for this one" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome to another digest!

    Last week was yet another busy week for DoCSoc, with over _100_ members
    attending the LSEG talk and 80 members attending the G-Research Coding
    Challenge. As usual, thanks to everyone who attended and a special thanks
    to our volunteers!

    One thing to note from us: if you're attending an event, be sure to click
    _Going_ on Facebook so we can order enough food and drinks in advance.

    Over the next week, we will be holding an ice skating trip, hosting a cybersecurity
    talk from Facebook and releasing tickets for a trip to watch The Book of Mormon.
    With DevFest on the 1st of December too, the next fortnight will be busy
    and exciting. And don't forget: Liquidnet are hosting a talk and an _office
    visit_, which will be great casual event for those looking to network over
    a few drinks. Read on for more details!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DevFest Volunteers and IC Hack 19 Organisers</heading>
  <text>
    This academic year, we're not only hosting our flagship hackathon, IC Hack 19
    (26/27th Jan 2019), but also Google DevFest London (1st Dec 2018)!

    For IC Hack in particular, we're looking for organisers taking on
    responsibilities beyond the standard volunteering role. We held our initial
    volunteers' meeting last week, with minutes available on the IC Hack 19 Slack
    (joinable via DoCSoc: Operations). On the Slack channel, you'll be able to
    choose whether you want to take part in Logistics, Finance, Marketing and
    Hacker Experience.

    To get involved, join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    Facebook group and learn more about organising IC Hack [here](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/permalink/2300633930262198/).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Careers Service: Start-Up and SME Week</heading>
  <text>
    The Careers Service is hosting a series of events related to SMEs and start-ups
    from 19th - 23rd November. For more information, see the PDF attached and
    be sure to book the events on [JobsLive](http://www.imperial.ac.uk/careers/services/jobslive/).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Goes Ice Skating</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qcLvVWW.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-20T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-20T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Natural History Museum, Cromwell Road, London, SW7 5BD">
    <text>
      Get out your scarf and gloves, and join us at the Natural History Museum
      for our annual ice skating spectacular on Tuesday 20th November at 6:30pm
      and Wednesday 21st November at 5:30pm, followed by one free drink at the end.

      Please ensure that you only attend the session that you have bought tickets for.

      If you were lucky enough to secure a ticket last week, we hope to see you
      there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2194365650777056/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Cyber Security at Facebook</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/HHVbNsD.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-22T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-22T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      RSVP here: https://cybersecurityfacebook.splashthat.com/

      Interested in becoming a Security Engineer? Want to help us catch the bad
      guys? We are excited to invite you to an information session and an evening
      of pizza and drinks with the Facebook Security Engineering team!

      More than two billion people around the world use Facebook to connect with
      their friends, family, and communities. Facebook Security understands the
      importance of keeping those interactions secure, and the team strives each
      day to create and maintain the safest environment possible for the people
      on Facebook and their data.

      You will have an opportunity to hear from Engineers in our Product Security
      Assessment &amp; Analysis and Computer &amp; Emergency Response teams, as well
      as representatives from the University Recruitment team. You can hear more
      about our 2019 Security Internship opportunities and we will give you
      information for the application process. The evening will finish off with
      pizza, swag giveaways and networking!

      If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few days
      beforehand. **Don't forget to click 'Going' on Facebook so we can order
      enough pizza!**
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/725303204514407/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://cybersecurityfacebook.splashthat.com/">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Goes to the Book of Mormon</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Ei9AKcL.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-26T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-26T22:30:00+00:00"
    location="Prince of Wales Royal Theatre, 31 Coventry Street, London W1D 6AS">
    <text>
      Due to popular demand, DoCSoc is going for a trip to the multi award-winning
      musical, The Book of Mormon, on Monday 26th of November at 7pm.

      Tickets will be heavily subsidised to £20 so join us in a fun evening of
      music and comedy!

      Tickets for this event will go on sale on Thursday 22nd November at 1pm.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/193126784904232/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <event startDate="2018-11-23T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-23T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="King's Business School, Bush House, 30 Aldwych, WC2B 4BG London, United Kingdom"
    external="true" >
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/JMiMmQB.png" />
    <text>
      **Blockchain Idea Competition, >£80k in cash prizes**

      **3rd and 4th year projects may be entered into this competition and are
      actively encouraged. This competition is also open to MSc Projects being
      entered.** If you would like to enter your assessed project into this competition,
      make sure your supervisor is happy to let you do so beforehand!

      Applications are now open for the Winter Cohort of the **Future of Blockchain**
      3 month idea competition. Build out an idea from to demo to a panel of
      leading VCs at the finale in March 2019. Be supported by a mentor and
      bi-weekly workshops during the term on how to build a blockchain startup.

      Prizes include 24 x £2,000 bounties, £20,000 top prize, £10,000 2nd prize,
      £5,000 3rd prizes and seed investment for viable projects that want to go
      full time.

      You can **register interest** and find more information at http://www.futureofblockchain.co.uk/ and
      **RSVP for the launch event** [here](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/future-of-blockchain-london-launch-and-drinks-tickets-50175230465).

    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/future-of-blockchain-london-launch-and-drinks-tickets-50175230465">RSVP (Launch Event)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2488542318038708/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="http://www.futureofblockchain.co.uk/">Website</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Liquidnet In-Office Interactive Session: Trading, AI and Augmenting Behavior</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9yqANVy.png" width="80" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-27T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-27T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 21st Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London, EC2A 2EW"
    external="true">
    <text>
      JOIN LIQUIDNET CHIEF DATA SCIENTIST TOM DORIS, PHD. to discuss challenges
      in adoption and adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct
      the methods that were effective in overcoming the obstacles, and review
      similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology
      team, our Recruitment Team and Product Team once the interactive session
      has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-trading-ai-and-augmenting-behavior-tickets-51867766887">Eventbrite</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Google DevFest London 2018</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-12-01T09:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-01T18:30:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London (South Kensington Campus)">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/yHopaE6.jpg" />
    <text>
      DoCSoc is proud to be hosting Google DevFest London on our very own campus
      this year! Read on for more information.

      **Learn the latest in web, mobile, cloud, machine learning and more at the
      UK's largest community organised free conference.**

      GDG London, Google and DoCSoc present GDG Devfest London - a multi-track
      event covering: cloud and machine learning; web; mobile; assistant; codelabs
      and demos.

      To find out more about speakers, topics and agenda, visit devfest.gdg.london

      Don’t miss out on a fun, interesting and informative day of expert speakers,
      demo stands coding labs and much much more.

      You’ll also get the chance to network with experts from Google, Imperial
      College and beyond and learn more from some of the amazing developer
      communities we have in London.

      There will be people taking photographs and potentially filming the event.
      By attending you agree to the possibility of being photographed and filmed
      once inside the venue.

      Thank you for your interest in GDG DevFest London and we look forward to seeing you there!

      (Tickets are sold out, so if you have a ticket but are unable to attend,
      please let us know so we can release your ticket to our waitlist!)
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/gdg-devfest-london-2018-tickets-50723931645">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/255733691798751">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG WIN Breakfast Sessions for Young Female Talents</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg" />
  <event startDate="2018-12-05T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-05T10:00:00+00:00"
    location="LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London, EC4M 7LS"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Limited spaces available!**

      The **LSEG WIN (Women Inspired Network)** Community aims to provide a
      platform to celebrate female talents within and outside the Group. As part of the
      WIN Campus Taskforce, we’d like to invite a small group of elite female
      students from four top London universities (LSE, UCL, KCL, and Imperial
      College London) to attend our breakfast sessions to understand and explore the
      financial industry with the help of industry leaders and senior executives.

      We are excited to offer this opportunity to young talented female students to
      help them to gain more exposure to financial markets, whilst networking with
      like-minded peers.

      Our last breakfast session is **Alternative Career Options in Finance**, on
      Wednesday, 5 December, 9:00am – 10:00am. For more details, see the PDF attached.

      Location: LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London EC4M 7LS

      If you're interested, email DoCSoc at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and they'll pass your
      details onto us!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
