<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image width="70"
         src="https://i.imgur.com/skyMLSx.jpg"
         alt="Photo of Oreos on a plate"
         title="Let's kick off the year with some Oreos!" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome (back) to the Department of Computing!

    Whether you're a returning student or a recently-joined fresher, this first
    weekly digest of the year contains a whole lot of useful information, so
    keep on reading!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>What is DoCSoc?</heading>

  <text>
    **Returning student?** If you aren't a fresher, feel free to skim through this
    section. If you're new to DoCSoc, there's lots of useful information here so
    read on!

    **DoCSoc is the Department of Computing Society**. We run multiple events through
    the year with our sponsors. We invite notable tech speakers, connect our
    students with different opportunities and run a number of social events to
    bring together the community of students who are interested in Computing.

    **Committee -** This year, DoCSoc is brought to you by:

    - **President**: Inara Ramji
    - **Vice President**: Alessandro Bonardi
    - **Treasurer**: Rachel Mekhteiva Lee
    - **Industrial Events Director**: Rohan Pritchard
    - **Social Events Director**: Jayati Sarkar
    - **Academic Events Director**: Jack Pordi
    - **Secretary**: Kelvin Zhang
    - **Events Officers**: Szilveszter Szekely, Serene Chongtrakul, Anindita (Andy) Ghosh
    - **Marketing &amp; Publicity Officer**: Fawaz Shah
    - **Webmaster**: George Soteriou
    - **GameDev Officer**: Athi Dharma

    **Dep Reps -** In addition to the DoCSoc committee, we have three departmental representatives
    (dep reps) this year responsible for representing the student body to the department:

    - **Computing**: Martin Zlocha ([email](mailto:dep-rep@doc.ic.ac.uk))
    - **Joint Maths and Computing (JMC)**: Rachel Mekhtieva Lee and Fawaz Shah ([email](mailto:dep-rep@doc.ic.ac.uk))
    - **Electronic and Information Engineering (EIE)**: Willem van der Schoot (Academic, [email](willem.van-der-schoot16@imperial.ac.uk)) and Mayank Surana (Wellbeing, [email](mayank.surana16@imperial.ac.uk))

    If you have any academic or wellbeing related queries, your dep reps are people
    you can talk to.

    **Events -** DoCSoc runs a huge number of events every year. Our main events
    include:

    - **Talks and Workshops** - Not to be confused with the department's lunchtime
    ACI talks, DoCSoc runs engaging talks and workshops with our sponsors, usually
    in the evening with pizza (with dietary requirements catered for) and soft
    drinks provided. In the past, we've run workshops such as capture the flag competitions
    with Netcraft, an _Extreme Startup_ event with Palantir and Bloomberg's _CodeCon_.

    - **Bar Nights** - Our most well-known events include our bar nights which
    usually occur every month during term time. Bar nights are a chance for you to
    socialise with your coursemates, make new friends and occasionally network with
    recruiters sponsoring our bar nights. Bar nights are _free entry_ to our members
    and you will be given tokens for _free_ drinks (both alcoholic and non-alcoholic)
    to use at the bar!

    - **Sponsors' Exhibition** - This is DoCSoc's Careers Fair, where our sponsors
    come together to present their companies and interact with you. See below for
    more details about this year's Sponsors' Exhibition!

    - **Revel and End of Year Dinner** - The two formal events hosted by DoCSoc.
    Held before exams and at the end of the summer term respectively, both events let
    you celebrate with your coursemates with a unique atmosphere you will remember
    even after you have graduated!

    - **IC Hack** - Every year, we hold our flagship hackathon, IC Hack, the largest
    student-run hackathon in the country. Last year, attendees hacked away for
    twenty-four hours building their competition entries, while we kept them
    engaged with workshops from five sponsors, a meditation and sleep class with
    NextJump, games rooms, karaoke and much more! Check out the montage from the
    last year [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hngr7ts45Dc).

    Throughout the year we also host a wide range of social events (go-karting,
    cinema and theatre trips) and academic events. Do you have suggestions for
    events? We're always looking for feedback so feel free to email us with anything
    you have in mind!

    **Sponsors -** DoCSoc would not be possible without the support of our sponsors.
    Sponsors fund the events we run, including our bar nights, IC Hack and our workshops.

    Why do sponsors fund us? The reason is simple: they want to hire _you_. That's
    why we host a yearly Sponsors' Exhibition (details below) exclusive to our
    members and send you opportunities in the weekly digest.

    **Membership -** Our membership base is mostly comprised of Computing, JMC,
    and EIE students who are automatically members of DoCSoc at no cost. For
    those _not_ on these courses, membership can be purchased on the [Union website](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/activities/a-to-z/computing).
    Why not get your friends on other courses to become members too?

    **Keeping Updated -** Our weekly digest is one of two key ways to find out about
    events. The best place to stay updated about events is via our **[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ICDocSoc/)**
    page. You can also find us on [Twitter](https://twitter.com/icdocsoc/).

    Don't forget that we run **group chats for every academic year** on Facebook
    Messenger. Other than Piazza (run by the department), Messenger is a central
    place for discussions so if you aren't part of this group chat, get in touch
    with us and we'll add you!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Volunteering with DoCSoc</heading>
  <text>
    Running activities at DoCSoc's scale would not be possible without the help
    of volunteers. We have opportunities open for anyone looking to offer their
    technical skills or manpower.

    **Operations -** DoCSoc has a central [Facebook group](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    for when we need volunteers. If you're thinking of volunteering, join the group!
    Events we will need help for over the coming months include:

    - Google DevFest London - We're hosting Europe's largest free developer conference
    with over 1000 attendees on Saturday 1st December. We're looking for volunteers
    to help with organising both before and during the event.

    - IC Hack - With 300 attendees, our yearly hackathon won't be possible without
    our volunteers. If you aren't looking to compete in the hackathon, lending a
    helping hand is also a great way to participate in the hackathon!

    **Software Foundation -** We're reviving our open source initiative, the
    [Software Foundation](https://github.com/docsocsf) and are in need of
    volunteers and contributors. This year, we're planning lots of projects,
    from beginner-friendly to more advanced. If you'd like to get involved,
    either as a project owner or only to suggest ideas, please let us know!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>Now for the upcoming events:</text>

  <heading>Freshers' Fair</heading>
  <text>
    - **When:** **TOMORROW!** 11:00 - 16:00, Tuesday 2nd October 2018
    - **Where:** Main Entrance (ICME) Stall 5

    Come and visit us at our stall at the Freshers' Fair to learn more about us,
    chat with the committee and compete in a (yet to be announced) competition to
    win some prizes! We'll be there all day so make sure to check out all of the
    other fantastic opportunities as well. You can find us by consulting the official
    map.
  </text>

  <heading>Mums &amp; Dads Lunch</heading>
  <text>
    - **When:** 12:30 - 14:00, Monday 8th October 2018
    - **Where:** HXLY 341/342

    As a fresher, you will have already heard of our Mums and Dads (MaD) programme.
    If you don't have parents assigned yet or haven't heard of this programme, please
    reach out to your departmental representatives above.

    We'll be kicking off the Mums and Dads programme with an opportunity for you
    to meet your MaD parents and have lunch with them! We will be offering free
    food and drinks, as well as issuing a number of challenges. You might even win
    a prize!

    Mums and Dads parent? Be sure to turn up to this event to meet your children!
  </text>

  <heading>Sponsors' Exhibition</heading>
  <text>
    - **When:** 17:00 - 20:00, Tuesday 9th October 2018
    - **Where:** QTR

    Looking for an internship, placement or graduate role? Want to find out more
    about industry and chat with out sponsors? Come join us in Queen's Tower Room
    (Sherfield Building) for our main industrial event of the year to have a chat
    with companies ranging from Facebook to Palantir and from Netcraft to Microsoft.
    Bring lots of questions and be prepared to go home with a lot of swag!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>Some notes from our sponsors:</text>

  <heading>Liquidnet ACI Talk</heading>
  <sponsor company="liquidnet">
    Liquidnet will be holding an Applications of Computing in Industry (ACI) talk
    at **1:45pm** on **Tuesday 2nd October** in **HXLY 308**.

    Titled "**Trading, AI and augmenting behaviour**", the talk revolves around
    the challenges of applying technology and predictive analytics to tasks performed
    by human experts.

    Abstract: Traders in financial markets perform tasks that require
    them to absorb large amounts of data in limited time and make rapid decisions.
    It is relatively easy to show that their performance is sub-optimal and costs
    firms hundreds of millions of dollars a year. Our company’s product augments
    the human expert with a variety of technologies, from anomaly detection pattern
    recognition algorithms to natural language generation and visualizations. In
    this talk I will review the challenges we experienced in adoption and adherence
    of new technologies by human experts, deconstructing the methods that were
    effective in overcoming the obstacles, and review similarities across other
    industries.
  </sponsor>

  <heading>Netcraft Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="netcraft">
    Netcraft is a world-leading security services company, providing penetration
    testing and cybercrime disruption services to critical institutions throughout
    the world.

    We're currently looking to recruit software developers to our offices in Bath,
    England. We are keen to receive applications for graduate positions, industrial
    placements, or summer internships from high performing Computing students.

    Projects involve working on a range of commercial services extending Netcraft's
    network exploration and internet security services.

    To find out more, take a look at our recruitment booklet:
    https://www.netcraft.com/about-netcraft/jobs/NetcraftGraduateBooklet.pdf

    Interested? Send a CV to cv@netcraft.com.
  </sponsor>

  <hr />

  <text>
    That's all for this week! We have a lot more events planned for this month,
    so stay tuned for the next digest.
  </text>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
