<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/5rJTZsq.jpg"
    alt="Photo of digestive biscuits on a plate"
    title=""/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi again! It's time for another digest.

    In the past week, we held four events: the Mums and Dads meeting, Linux talk,
    Sponsors' Exhibition and the Bloomberg Decentralised App Development workshop.
    These events were an overwhelming success with a total attendee count over all
    four events of 1000. Thanks to everyone who participated and a special thanks
    to all of our volunteers!

    If you have any feedback about our events, feel free to [get in touch](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk).
    Additionally, if you want to help out at our events, be sure to join our
    [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/) Facebook group.

    In the coming week, we have our first inaugural bar night of the year, the
    Welcome Bar Night, so stay tuned for more information and opportunities from
    our sponsors.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Welcome Bar Night</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2018-10-18T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-18T23:00:00+01:00"
    location="Metric">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/TPhybmZ.jpg" />
    <text>
      It's time for DoCSoc's first bar night of the year: The Welcome Bar Night!

      Come along for free drinks and to say hi to our new freshers or catch up
      with friends - it's sure to be a night you don't want to miss out on.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to all DoCSoc members.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2180649362174437/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Next Jump Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="next_jump"/><text>
    It was great speaking to many of you at the DoCSoc careers fair on Tuesday.
    Hope you managed to swipe some orange sunglasses before they ran out 🕶️! Our
    fast track applications for intern/placement and full time software developers
    are still open – use the link below to apply to come to our Super Saturday.

    https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/UWulrrsRCG/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications?source=socmedpost

    Next Jump is a global e-commerce company and work with 70% of the Fortune 1000,
    generating $2.5B a year. We build coders who lead. This means not just building
    awesome products (in React Native, Golang and PHP), our developers lead teams
    to design, build and market to our 3mil UK customers – from their first day
    on the job. Check out the video below to find out more about being a developer
    at Next Jump https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xEYu7kOsRWI

    You can also email us at teamukrecruitment@nextjump.com if you have any questions.
  </text>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/fqjRgbw.jpg" />

  <hr />

  <heading>Schlumberger Meet &amp; Engage Event</heading>
  <sponsor company="schlumberger"/>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/eDTOQFE.png" />
  <text>
    We have selected DoCSoc's members to participate in an exclusive live video
    chat on the World Alliance for Efficient Solutions!

    Many innovative solutions exist that can reduce our impact on the environment
    while enabling economic development.

    Join Bertrand Piccard, the man who flew 26,000 miles around the world with a
    plane powered only by the sun and find out how he is contributing to improve
    the world’s energy efficiency and have economy and ecology work hand-in-hand.
    Learn more about his [#1000 Efficient Solutions initiative](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3RkXldC2nJI&amp;feature=youtu.be), why innovative
    companies like Schlumberger are partnering with him, and how you can apply
    your engineering and science skills to help this important project.

    **WHEN:** October 19th, 11.00 (UK time)

    **HOW:** Register on line @ https://meetandengage.com/g3c6h9h3t

    **Please kindly confirm your availability by registering on the above link.**
  </text>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
