<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image width="50"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/V1032UM.jpg"
    alt="Snow Globe Biscuit"
    title="The digest is now 'totally different yet basically the same'(tm), generated with a new custom tool :D." />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Happy new year!

    Hopefully everyone has had an enjoyable break. Welcome to 2018: Filled with
    more coursework, more exams, and of course, more DoCSoc events! Keep reading
    to find out what's happening...
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Hack 18</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="138720960119278" alias="https://docsoc.co.uk/ichack18" />
    <links>
      <link href="http://ichack18.eventbrite.com/">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://ichack.org">Website</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      Guess who's back, back again?

      Running for its seventh consecutive year, we're bringing over 300 of the
      UK's most creative and talented students to South Kensington for 24 hours
      of learning, building, fun, and networking on the weekend of 27th-28th
      January 2018.

      This year, IC Hack will once again be hosted at Imperial College London's
      South Kensington campus!

      Don't miss out - we will be releasing the **LAST batch of tickets on
      Wednesday 10th at 17.00 GMT**. The previous batch was sold in under 10
      SECONDS so make sure you're ready! Tickets will be released on Eventbrite
      (link above). There will be two separate tickets - one for Imperial
      students and one for other universities. *If you are an Imperial student
      please select Imperial Ticket and register with your ic.ac.uk or
      imperial.ac.uk email*.

      Please note that because of venue policies this event is only for students
      aged 18+.
    </text>
  </event>
  <hr/>

  <heading>Felix Seeking Tech Contributors</heading>
  <text>
    Felix, Imperial's weekly newspaper, is planning to expand its tech section
    after a successful first term and they figured Computing students might be
    interested in joining. The tech section covers popular science topics
    ranging from Formula 1 aerodynamics to gene drives, with the plan this term
    being to get involved with established electronics giants and review their
    upcoming gadgets and devices. Of course, the usual op-eds will make their
    appearance as well.

    If this is something that interests you, send an email to
    tecfelix@imperial.ac.uk
  </text>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
