<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest" agenda="false" >

  <image width="70"
         src="https://i.imgur.com/f9Rr2j2.jpg"
         alt="Digestive Biscuit"
         title="No biscuit found :(" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hello everyone,

    Exams are finally over and summer is in the air! We hope that you are having
    a blast with your summer projects, placements, or whatever you might be up
    to right now. I sure love WebApps.

    Since there hasn't been much going on, you haven't been seeing these emails
    much. But now there is:

    To mark the end of the year, we'll be holding our annual formal dinner. More
    details below!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc End Of Year Dinner 2018</heading>
	<event startDate="2018-06-21T19:00:00+01:00"
				 endDate="2018-06-22T00:30:00+01:00"
				 location="The Ivory Vaults, Ivory House, St Katharine Docks, E1W 1BP">
    <image src="https://scontent-lht6-1.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t1.0-9/34511500_2185187851497752_545841969104945152_o.jpg?_nc_cat=0&amp;oh=0dd5ed00e5f2757eb1ff7d7978f2c33d&amp;oe=5BA8E2F1" />
    <text>
      The time has come for the final DoCSoc event, the End Of Year Dinner. Join
      us to the Ivory Vaults, on Thursday 21st June for a glamorous evening of
      dinner, drinking, and dancing.

      The festivities shall begin with a champagne reception, followed by a
      three-course meal together with half a bottle of wine/soft drinks.

      A sophisticated evening calls for sophisticated dress - please arrive in
      black tie. We hope to see you all there for a memorable night!

      For details about tickets, please see the
      [Facebook event](https://www.facebook.com/events/1815337052108607/).
    </text>
		<links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1815337052108607/">Facebook</link>
		</links>
  </event>

  <text>
    # Farewell

    It looks like my term is coming to a close. Whether you've enjoyed my
    "weekly" emails or not, my place will be inherited by someone who is sure to
    bring you even better digests next year.

    Thanks to everyone who participated in the random stuff that I sent out
    every now and then, such as when I ran a survey on the future of the
    biscuit.
    By the way, I picked the biscuit this week because the number of respondents
    to the biscuit choosing survey was rather lacking.
  </text>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now -- I think!

    Until next term?
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Anonymous.
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
