<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

	<image width="50"
				 src="https://i.imgur.com/1YmCqwM.jpg"
				 alt="Custard Cream"
				 title="" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    It's Monday!

    We're kicking the week off with a whopping TWO events, happening TODAY!
    First is the Docker workshop, which you might find useful if you're either
    taking Distributed Algorithms or will use Docker during a summer internship.
    Following that is our Valentine's Bar Night, taking place from 19.00 in
    Metric. Tomorrow (Tuesday) we're holding our Internship 101 event, where you
    can find out about internships at companies that are still hiring from past
    interns. And on Thursday we're running a Kotlin workshop at 18.30, which
    follows the lunchtime iPr0gram talk on the same day.

    Definitely a packed week! Check out below for more details and keep the
    biscuit suggestions coming!
  </text>

  <hr/>

	<heading>Docker Workshop</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="935309229966009" />
    <text>
      &lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="red"&gt;HAPPENING
      TODAY!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Docker is a tool designed to make it
      easier to create, deploy, and run applications by using containers.
      Containers allow a developer to package up an application with all of the
      parts it needs, such as libraries and other dependencies, and ship it all
      out as one package.

      This workshop is targeted to those who want to learn about the basics of
      Docker. If you are taking Distributed Algorithms (CO347), this workshop
      will definitely help you with the course. You may also encounter Docker in
      some format during a placement or internship this summer..

      This workshop will be hosted by Abhinav Mishra.
    </text>
  </event>

	<heading>The Valentine's Bar Night</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1607380125981757" />
    <text>
      &lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="red"&gt;HAPPENING
      TODAY!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; It's time for the first Bar Night of
      2018! Once again, we'll be meeting in Metric at 7pm for an evening of free
      drinks and great conversation.


      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to any member of DoCSoc.
      Tokens are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>Internship 101</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="140931969937020" />
  </event>

  <heading>JetBrains: Kotlin Hands-On</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="166048430696844" />
  </event>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Anonymous.
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
