<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image width="80"
         src="https://i.imgur.com/Q2FvTYv.jpg"
         alt="Photo of a snickerdoodle"
         title="Snickerdoodles are crispy outside and chewy inside. Would recommend!" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Here's the second weekly digest of the year!

    First off, thanks to everyone who came to Freshers' Fair. It was great seeing
    both old and new faces and if you're a fresher, we hope you managed to learn
    more about what we do as a society and meet our committee members.

    We have a lot of events going on in the coming week and in the longer term,
    so read on for more information!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>Let's start off with our events coming up over the next week:</text>

  <heading>Mums &amp; Dads Lunch</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-08T12:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-08T14:00:00+01:00"
    location="HXLY 341/342">
    <text>
      As a fresher, you will have already heard of our Mums and Dads (MaD) programme.
      If you don't have parents assigned yet or haven't heard of this programme, please
      reach out to your departmental representatives above.

      We'll be kicking off the Mums and Dads programme with an opportunity for you
      to meet your MaD parents and have lunch with them! We will be offering free
      food and drinks, as well as issuing a number of challenges. You might even win
      a prize!

      Mums and Dads parent? Be sure to turn up to this event to meet your children!
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>An Introduction to Linux &amp; the Command Line</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-08T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-08T19:00:00+01:00"
    location="HXLY 144">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/5LRGebA.jpg" />
    <text>
      If you're a first year and are new to Computer Science, then this is the
      talk for you!

      Familiarity with the Linux/Unix environment and the command line is arguably
      one of the most important skills a software engineer today can have. Many
      often find it difficult and intimidating at first - even if they've got
      quite a bit of coding experience under their belt, but DoCSoc is here to help!

      We'll be covering important fundamental command line skills and Linux-related
      knowledge that will be useful for you sometime down the road, as well as
      looking at package managers and different text editors. You'll also have a
      chance to ask any questions you may have at the end of the talk.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1914035272235179/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <heading>Sponsors' Exhibition</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-09T17:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-09T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Queens Tower Rooms">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/ptAlUIl.jpg" />
    <text>
      Come to the Queens Tower Rooms on Tuesday 9th October between 5pm - 8pm to
      have a chance to meet all of DoCSoc's Silver and Gold sponsors this year
      and grab some swag.

      This year's exciting sponsors that will be attending include Facebook,
      Palantir, Bloomberg, Samsung, Netcraft, Microsoft, Next Jump, Entrepreneur
      First, NewVoiceMedia and Artificial Labs.

      Whether you are looking for an internship or graduate role, or simply want
      to know more about industry, we really recommend you come along as it's a
      great way to get in direct contact with recruiters and engineers from highly
      regarded companies and should provide invaluable insight into the recruitment
      process.

      This event is open to all DoCSoc members (automatically includes Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students).
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1873849222722225/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <heading>Bloomberg Extreme Decentralised App Development</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-11T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-11T21:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      Join Bloomberg on Thursday 11th October at 6pm for a session of Extreme
      Decentralised Application Development on the Ethereum blockchain. We will
      present to you the tools you need to develop, test and deploy smart contracts
      on the Ethereum blockchain. Then you will be given the chance to work in
      groups to develop and deploy a series of smart contracts that will allow you
      to create a toy social network on Ethereum.

      We hope that you will leave the session knowing where to start with
      decentralised app development and with a basic understanding of the issues
      such apps face and why they haven't been widely adopted yet.

      Note that if you're a first year and are new to programming, you may find
      this event a little intense.

      Drinks at the Union to follow.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2163782050561037/">RSVP (Facebook)</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>Next, here's a couple of events coming up in the longer term:</text>

  <heading>CGCU Annual Welcome Dinner</heading>
  <event external="true"
    startDate="2018-10-27T18:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-28T01:00:00+01:00"
    location="Millennium Gloucester Hotel">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/LXIr2lJ.jpg" />
    <text>
      The City and Guilds College Union (CGCU), the constituent union responsible
      for Imperial's engineering courses (which DoCSoc belongs to!) is holding
      their annual welcome dinner. Details below:

      One of the BIGGEST EVENTS of our year - start your year the right way!
      JOIN US at the CGCU Annual Welcome Dinner!

      Imagine entering through the courtyard on a red carpet, dazzling everyone
      with your outfit as the paparazzi snap photos. At the drinks reception,
      you receive a complimentary welcome drink and chat with your friends, before
      heading to the main room for a 3-course meal with wine. Speeches, music,
      and dancing follow as the Techtonics (world A Cappella champions) perform,
      before the DJ comes on and the after party begins! Who wouldn't want to come?!

      **Details**

      - Location: Millennium Gloucester Hotel (next to Gloucester Road Station) -
      less than a 10 minute walk away from Imperial!
      - Date: Saturday 27th October
      - Time: 6.30 pm
      - Dress Code: Black Tie
      - Student priced Card/Cash bar available too!

      **Ticket includes**
      - Glass of prosecco
      - 3 course meal
      - 1/2 bottle of wine
      - Techtonics performance
      - After party
      - Free Cloakroom all night
      - Professional photographer (photos posted online after)

      Open to all, but non-engineers must accompany a plus-one! Under 18s can also attend.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/club-society-project-products/city-guilds-union-products/23894/final-release-welcome-dinner-tickets-">Tickets (Union website)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/538834613239338/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Google DevFest London 2018</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-12-01T09:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-12-01T18:30:00+01:00"
    location="Imperial College London (South Kensington Campus)">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/yHopaE6.jpg" />
    <text>
      DoCSoc is proud to be hosting Google DevFest London on our very own campus
      this year! Read on for more information.

      **Learn the latest in web, mobile, cloud, machine learning and more at the
      UK's largest community organised free conference.**

      GDG London, Google and DoCSoc present GDG Devfest London - a multi-track
      event covering: cloud and machine learning; web; mobile; assistant; codelabs
      and demos.

      To find out more about speakers, topics and agenda, visit devfest.gdg.london

      Don’t miss out on a fun, interesting and informative day of expert speakers,
      demo stands coding labs and much much more.

      You’ll also get the chance to network with experts from Google, Imperial
      College and beyond and learn more from some of the amazing developer
      communities we have in London.

      There will be people taking photographs and potentially filming the event.
      By attending you agree to the possibility of being photographed and filmed
      once inside the venue.

      Thank you for your interest in GDG DevFest London and we look forward to seeing you there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/gdg-devfest-london-2018-tickets-50723931645">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/255733691798751">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>CGCU 5-a-side Football</heading>
  <text>
    CGCU 5-a-side football is back, better than ever! The CGCU Football League,
    'Unsullied by sponsorship since 2018.'

    This year promises more games, goals and greatness! Teams play in a league
    games in one of two departmental conferences (TBC depending on teams responding),
    then afterwards fighting for the newly created CGCU Cup in an inter-conference.
    The winners get the trophy displayed in the union or their department with their
    colours for all to see. This new format enables teams to pay a number of guaranteed
    league games, but still delivers on an exciting knockout tournament, world cup style!

    The first game is likely to be in October, in order to allow freshers to make
    teams too, but a further email will follow to team captains with more information
    closer to the time.

    Team captains: could you send an email with your name and team's name to say
    you are interested, so that I can sign you guys up into the league and start
    putting together the conferences and schedule! As early as possible would help
    me out big time. Email: rh1616@ic.ac.uk.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>Finally, messages from our sponsors:</text>

  <heading>Netcraft Job Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="netcraft"/>
  <text>
    Netcraft is a world-leading security services company, providing penetration
    testing and cybercrime disruption services to critical institutions throughout
    the world.

    We’re currently looking to recruit software developers to our new offices in
    London for graduates and students in at least Year 2, as well as our offices
    in Bath for all years.

    We are keen to receive applications for graduate positions, industrial
    placements, or summer internships from high performing Computing students.

    Projects involve working on a range of commercial services extending
    Netcraft’s network exploration and internet security services.

    To find out more, take a look at our recruitment booklet: https://www.netcraft.com/about-netcraft/jobs/NetcraftGraduateBooklet.pdf

    Interested? Send a CV to cv@netcraft.com.
  </text>

  <heading>J.P. Morgan Events</heading>
  <sponsor company="jpmorgan">
    Paste J.P. Morgan email from Alice (5th Oct 2018) here (contains lots of links).
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
