<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/5rJTZsq.jpg"
    alt="Photo of digestive biscuits on a plate"
    title="/Digest/ives!"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi again! It's time for another digest.

    In the past week, we held four events: the Mums and Dads meeting, Linux talk,
    Sponsors' Exhibition and the Bloomberg Decentralised App Development workshop.
    These events were an overwhelming success with a total attendee count over all
    four events of 1000. The Sponsors' Exhibition in particular saw an incredible
    500 members attending. Thanks to everyone who participated and a special thanks
    to all of our volunteers!

    It would be very appreciated if you could provide your feedback for the Sponsors'
    Exhibition through this [link](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSe5Yl4yNZcXLr8x6gdjC5mLl8K_zU0UFQXWaO23iI1lIUqh6w/viewform) so that
    we can improve our main industrial event next year!

    All of our industrial events are catered (usually with pizza). If you have
    any dietary requirements and if you are planning on attending an event,
    please make sure you [get in touch](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk) at least
    two days before the event to tell us. You can use the same email address to
    give us any feedback about our events as well! Additionally, if you want to
    help out at our events, be sure to join our [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    Facebook group.

    In the coming week, we have our first inaugural bar night of the year, the
    Welcome Bar Night, so stay tuned for more information, more industrial events
    and opportunities from our sponsors.

    Finally, make sure you submit your vote for the Union Autumn Elections at
    https://vote.union.ic.ac.uk/ before Friday 12pm!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    We have released the DoCSoc Sponsors Portal, our website where you can find
    out more details about our sponsors, read their blog posts and see their open
    internship/placement positions. You can also upload your CV and directly
    apply to all of our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Welcome Bar Night</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2018-10-18T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-18T23:00:00+01:00"
    location="Metric">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/TPhybmZ.jpg" />
    <text>
      It's time for DoCSoc's first bar night of the year: The Welcome Bar Night!

      Come along for free drinks and to say hi to our new freshers or catch up
      with friends - it's sure to be a night you don't want to miss out on.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to all DoCSoc members.

      At the event we will also announce the winners of our End of Year Survey,
      Speed Typing competition at the Freshers' Fair and the Mums and Dads Checklist!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2180649362174437/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir - Interpreting Law and Policy as Technologists</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qkZxAgO.jpg" />
  <image src="" width="70" />
  <event startDate="2018-10-22T18:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-22T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      In May 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) became one
      of the most important reforms of data protection law worldwide. Strangely,
      this law did not come with technical specifications. Join Paula Kift, of
      the Privacy and Civil Liberties team at Palantir, for a workshop that aims
      to highlight for those interested in the intersection of law and technology
      how they can shape it in practice, while tackling some of the most important
      privacy challenges of our time.

      Food and drinks provided!

      **Please RSVP using the link provided** before clicking 'Going' on Facebook.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://imperialpcl1022.splashthat.com/">RSVP</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/337105763726925/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Netcraft - Cryptocurrencies for Fun and Profit</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qImfYjE.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-10-25T18:15:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-25T20:30:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      Rolling your own cryptocurrency: what could possibly go wrong?

      Over the past few years, the popularity and value of cryptocurrencies,
      such as Bitcoin, has soared. Bitcoin has also spawned a number of spinoff
      currencies, known as 'altcoins'. Some altcoins provide genuine technical
      improvements over Bitcoin; however, most are forks with minimal changes -
      designed to be pump and dump schemes to enrich their creators.

      In July 2018 Imperial College jointly published a report written by Prof
      William Knottenbelt with eToro, a cryptocurrency exchange. The report was
      widely regarded by the press to be a puff piece promoting cryptocurrencies,
      poorly disguised as academic research. The Financial Times dubbed it "cryptopuff".

      Not wanting to miss out on the fun (or profit!), Netcraft has designed its
      own cryptocurrency and named it Cryptopuff in tribute to Prof Knottenbelt's
      report. However, Cryptopuff was written in a rush during a single weekend -
      who knows what vulnerabilities may be lurking in its depths?

      Your challenge, after a short talk illustrating the concepts, is to compete
      against your peers to earn as much Cryptopuff as possible.

      You'll need to find and exploit vulnerabilities to steal coins from your
      peers, while also defending your own node against attack to protect your
      own coins. Or perhaps you could sell 'zero-day' vulnerabilities to other
      teams rather than doing the dirty work of exploiting them yourself.

      The team with the greatest number of coins at the end of the event will be
      declared the winner.

      To take part, bring your own laptop with a web browser and an SSH client
      (e.g. Putty http://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/putty/ for Windows
      users; OpenSSH for Linux/Mac users)

      **There will a free bar night at the Union Bar after the competition.**
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2190799097619225/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Next Jump Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="next_jump"/><text>
    It was great speaking to many of you at the DoCSoc careers fair on Tuesday.
    Hope you managed to swipe some orange sunglasses before they ran out 🕶️! Our
    fast track applications for intern/placement and full time software developers
    are still open – use the link below to apply to come to our Super Saturday.

    https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/UWulrrsRCG/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications?source=socmedpost

    Next Jump is a global e-commerce company and work with 70% of the Fortune 1000,
    generating $2.5B a year. We build coders who lead. This means not just building
    awesome products (in React Native, Golang and PHP), our developers lead teams
    to design, build and market to our 3mil UK customers – from their first day
    on the job. Check out the video below to find out more about being a developer
    at Next Jump https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xEYu7kOsRWI

    You can also email us at teamukrecruitment@nextjump.com if you have any questions.
  </text>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/fqjRgbw.jpg" />

  <hr />

  <heading>Schlumberger Meet &amp; Engage Event</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/eDTOQFE.png" />
  <event startDate="2018-10-19T11:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-19T12:00:00+01:00"
    location="N/A">
    <text>
      We have selected DoCSoc's members to participate in an exclusive live video
      chat on the World Alliance for Efficient Solutions!

      Many innovative solutions exist that can reduce our impact on the environment
      while enabling economic development.

      Join Bertrand Piccard, the man who flew 26,000 miles around the world with a
      plane powered only by the sun and find out how he is contributing to improve
      the world’s energy efficiency and have economy and ecology work hand-in-hand.
      Learn more about his [#1000 Efficient Solutions initiative](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3RkXldC2nJI&amp;feature=youtu.be), why innovative
      companies like Schlumberger are partnering with him, and how you can apply
      your engineering and science skills to help this important project.

      **Please kindly confirm your availability by registering on the above link.**
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://meetandengage.com/g3c6h9h3t">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Algothon 2018 at BlackRock</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-20T09:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-21T17:00:00+01:00"
    location="BlackRock, Drapers Gardens, 12 Throgmorton Avenue, London, EC2N 2DL"
    external="true">
    <text>
      Algothon 2018 in partnership with BlackRock is the inaugural event of the
      2018/19 academic year organised by the Imperial College Algorithmic Trading
      Society. We’re excited to bring you 24 hours of intense hacking, bringing
      200 of the brightest minds together to produce incredible new financial technology.

      This will be an incredible weekend, producing amazing new technologies,
      learning from some of the best minds in the field, and overall having a
      great time!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://algothon.org/">Website</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>2018 Milner Award Lecture - When to trust a self-driving car</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-11-20T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-20T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="The Royal Society, London, 6-9 Carlton House Terrace, London, SW1Y 5AG"
    external="true">
    <text>
      2018 Milner Award Lecture given by Professor Marta Kwiatkowska.

      How can we ensure system correctness in the presence of uncertainty?

      Computing devices support us in almost all everyday tasks, from mobile
      phones and online banking to wearable and implantable medical devices.
      We are now experimenting with self–driving cars and robots.

      Since embedded software at the heart of these devices must behave correctly
      in presence of uncertainty, probabilistic verification techniques have been
      developed to guarantee their safety, reliability and resource efficiency.

      Using illustrative examples, this lecture will give an overview of the role
      that probabilistic modelling and verification can play in a variety of
      applications, including security, medical devices, self-driving cars and
      DNA computing. It will also describe recent developments towards model
      synthesis, which aims to build these systems so that they are correct by
      construction. Finally, it will explore the problems of ensuring that systems
      that rely on learning will behave correctly, both in situations that they
      have seen in training, and in situations that they haven’t.

      The prize lecture will be webcast live and the video recording of the
      event will be available shortly after the event.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://royalsociety.org/science-events-and-lectures/2018/11/milner-lecture/">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
