<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="DoCSoc Digest" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hope your summer holidays are going well!

    We're getting in touch with two opportunities from our sponsors. Be sure to
    check them out!
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <heading>Facebook Hack-a-Project 2018</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Aqczu56.png"/>
  <text>
    Facebook is launching Hack-a-project!  Consider it an extended hackathon
    with learning and mentoring attached to it!

    This is a 6 - 8 week programme kicking off in October 2018, designed for 2nd
    and 3rd year students, looking to apply for a Software Engineering
    internship with Facebook.

    Selected students will come to the Facebook office, once a week in the
    evening to focus on understanding the whole development cycle, and build a
    project.  Each session will consist of a talk, and practical applications
    with group mentoring support. Dinner will also be provided!

    *Facebook will not be providing this project; students will be coming up
    with the project.

    In addition, we will be sharing tips on “how to crush your coding interview”,
    and also do a mock interview with you, where feedback will be provided to
    help you improve.

    All selected participants will be guaranteed an interview for the Facebook
    internship!

    **If you would like to sign-up please follow this link https://hackaprojectseptember2018.splashthat.com/**

    **Password: HAP2018**

    **You will be sent a link to complete a “HackerRank” (a coding challenge).
    Upon passing this, you will be asked to provide your CV, and this will be
    screened for this programme. To be considered, you will have to complete all
    of these steps by 31st August!**
  </text>
  <hr />

  <heading>Netcraft Final Year Project Kickstarter Hackathon</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-09-07T17:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-09-09T16:00:00+01:00"
    location="Bath, Somerset">
    <text>
      Netcraft is running a hackathon in Bath for final year students over the
      weekend of 8th September.

      Over the past few years, students working with Netcraft have produced some
      of the best final year projects at the top UK universities, including
      winning the Best Project Prize at each of Imperial, Bath and Bristol, and
      securing firsts for all of the projects attempted.

      If you're interested, check out the event description with instructions on
      how to take part here: https://www.facebook.com/events/1684249138351948/
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1684249138351948/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
