<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image width="50"
    alt="Zoomey Biscuit, HTTP/1.1 404 Not Found"
    title="Or just no biscuit. Hmm. So many options."
    src="https://i.imgur.com/cNHFOpW.png" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome back to another edition of the DoCSoc digest!

    IC Hack 18 is over! Thank you so much to all our sponsors and to everyone
    who participated and volunteered - it has been an incredible weekend! If you
    haven't already (and even if you have), watch the event montage [here on
    YouTube](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hngr7ts45Dc).

    While everyone is recovering, we're glad to finally announce a couple of
    events see below.

    Lastly, I've been delibrating the place and relevancy of the weekly biscuit.
    Over the weeks that I've written the digest, coming up with a biscuit every
    week has become quite a burden. Therefore I propose several options
    pertaining to the future of the biscuit:

    - Weekly biscuit, chosen by YOU.
    - No biscuit. Just nothing.
    - Some other kind of confectionery.
    - Something else?

    [Please submit your votes here so that we may democratically decide the future of the biscuit.](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfuJkKLu6KQPJMJpHEd8wJyRFqWvRf9IH8Q3pZYZ4quGvmoIQ/viewform)
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc hosts Google Hash Code</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="397017594079193" />
    <links>
      <link href="https://hashcode.withgoogle.com">Tickets</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2018</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1698424526881229" />
  </event>

  <heading>Diversity@Imperial Lunchtime Lecture</heading>
  <event external="true"
    startDate="2018-02-01T12:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-02-01T13:30:00+00:00"
    location="RSM 131 - Sutton Lecture Theatre, South Kensington Campus">
    <links>
      <link href="http://www3.imperial.ac.uk/newsandeventspggrp/imperialcollege/administration/equality/eventssummary/event_17-1-2018-10-12-41">Event Information</link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/a-sense-of-belonging-in-engineering-by-nike-folayan-tickets-41696046999">Tickets</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      This week Thursday (1st Feb), as part of the College's
      'Diversity@Imperial' campaign, the Equality, Diversity and Inclusion
      Centre will be hosting a lunchtime lecture on 'A Sense of Belonging in
      Engineering', given by Dr Nike Folayan.

      Dr Folayan is the Chairperson of the Association for Black and Minority
      Engineers (AFBE-UK), a national organisation to support and promote BAME
      engineers and engineering students through their careers in their
      respective industries. She will be discussing what diversity and the drive
      towards a more inclusive STEM workforce really mean, with a particular
      focus on the importance of diversity and inclusion in engineering.
    </text>
  </event>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
