<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Networking Evening at the Liquidnet Offices - Food and Drinks Provided"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi all!

    Liquidnet are getting in touch to advertise their networking event at their
    offices. This will be great casual event for those looking to network over
    a few drinks. Read on for more details!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9yqANVy.png" width="80" />
  <text>
    JOIN LIQUIDNET CHIEF DATA SCIENTIST TOM DORIS, PHD. at the Liquidnet Offices,
    with views of London, to discuss challenges in adoption and adherence of new
    technologies by human experts, deconstruct the methods that were effective in
    overcoming the obstacles, and review similarities across other industries.

    There will be an opportunity to network **informally** with members of Tom's
    Technology team, their Recruitment Team and Product Team once the interactive
    session has ended.

    Pizza and a mixture of alcoholic and non-alcoholic refreshments will be served.

    Liquidnet will be using this event to actively recruit graduates, and will
    have a team of recruiters there on the night. They are recruiting on a rolling
    basis, with interviews ongoing. Some strong candidates may have an offer as
    early as January! Liquidnet also have internships across their business this
    summer – applications closing on 31 January!

    This is not your standard corporate event. Liquidnet want you to dress casually,
    ask questions and truly embrace their non-corporate, flat structure right from
    your initial visit to their offices!

    The event will run from **7 - 9pm on 27th November** and will take place at
    their offices in the heart of The City and on the edge of Shoreditch!
    Please click [here](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-51867766887) to find out more and sign up!
  </text>
  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
