<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/rsRbmH2.jpg"
    alt="Bowl of biscuits"
    title="Homemade biscuits! "/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Another week another digest!

    First off, we had another great week with the Palantir Workshop, Netcraft
    Workshop (and Bar Night) and Netcraft Breakfast. Thanks to everyone who
    attended and a special thanks to those who volunteered. Also, photos from
    our [Sponsors' Exhibition](https://www.facebook.com/pg/ICDocSoc/photos/?tab=album&amp;album_id=2408111322538736)
    and [Welcome Bar Night](https://www.facebook.com/pg/ICDocSoc/photos/?tab=album&amp;album_id=2419005084782693) are up on Facebook, so be sure
    to check them out!

    This week, we bring you internal events with our sponsors, a Board Games
    Night and a few sponsor messages, so read on.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    Searching for internships or placements? Check out our Sponsors Portal, where
    you can find out more details about our sponsors, read their blog posts and
    see their open internship/placement positions. You can also upload your CV
    and directly apply to all of our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Facebook - Search &amp; Machine Learning</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/OXpHTFp.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-10-30T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-10-30T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Blackett LT1">
    <text>
      Facebook is coming to Imperial to present a talk on search systems and how
      they can utilise machine learning.

      Search systems are very complex pieces of software and, in order to be effective,
      must combine techniques coming from different branch of computer science,
      math, and statistics. Despite the fact that search systems have been around
      since just after the Web was created, search is still far from being a
      closed problem. This is even more true, if we consider searching through
      information that is produced every-day on social media systems. In this
      talk we will introduce search at FB and we will show some examples of very
      recent solutions to problems that we have addressed in the search team at FB.

      Food and drinks will be provided! If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1159268450889918/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Next Jump - Getting Started With React Native</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/jq7D80x.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-01T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-01T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Learn how to get from “npm install” to releasing your first app with React
      Native – a JavaScript framework to build cross-platform native mobile apps.
      At Next Jump we’ve been learning React Native to build a suite of apps across
      our business, scaling to 3 million users. We’ll share our own onboarding
      program for new engineers at Next Jump, sharing what libraries, coding standards
      and patterns we use internally - so you can get off Stack Overflow and get
      on the App Store!

      Food and drinks will be provided! If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1924319411195676/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Board Games Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/L9EaJGh.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-02T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-02T22:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217/218">
    <text>
      Come and take a break from your studies with some coursemates at our board
      games night!

      Snacks and drinks will be provided!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2338076339555663/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Introduction to AI in Games</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DcfMVdC.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-06T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-06T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Curious about Artificial Intelligence and its practical applications in games?

      Join DoCSoc GameDev as we learn about Artificial Intelligence in modern games
      with a short talk followed by a workshop on the application of the Monte Carlo
      Tree Search Algorithm through coding a Connect 4 game in Python.

      The workshop will be run by Daniel Hernandez and Peter York who are both on
      course for PhDs in AI applied to videogames at the University of York.

      The only thing you will need is a laptop with Python 3 installed and the
      workshop is open to programmers of all skill levels.

      Food will of course be provided, with informal drinks following the session at the
      Union afterwards! If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let
      us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/359358464805044/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Discover FinTech @ BlackRock</heading>
  <sponsor company="blackrock"/>
  <event startDate="2018-11-06T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-06T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="BlackRock Edinburgh Offices"
    external="true">
    <text>
      BlackRock combines the best of being a technology pioneer and financial leader.
      Since our inception in 1988, we’ve grown from an entrepreneurial start-up into
      the world’s largest investment manager by putting technology - and continuous
      innovation - at the heart of our business.

      Join us in Edinburgh on the 6th November 2018, 18:00 – 20:00 GMT

      We’ve invented our own global enterprise investment system, ‘Aladdin’: a technology
      ecosystem that empowers our colleagues to do better business every day. It is an
      unmatched operating platform - and central nervous system - that unites all the
      information, people and technology needed to manage money in real time and at
      every step in the investment process.

      Join us in our Edinburgh office to find out more about BlackRock, the opportunities
      available, gain hints &amp; tips on making a successful application, plus an opportunity
      to network with representatives from HR and the teams.

      This event will run from 18:00 - 20:00 BST. Economy travel expenses from outside
      Edinburgh (above £25 and up to £100) will be covered. Registration will close
      1 week before the event date so early application for this event is encouraged.

      Please visit https://careers.blackrock.com/campusrecruitment to apply.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://careers.blackrock.com/campusrecruitment">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG WIN Breakfast Sessions for Young Female Talents</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg">
    **Limited spaces available!**

    The **LSEG WIN (Women Inspired Network)** Community aims to provide a
    platform to celebrate female talents within and outside the Group. As part of the
    WIN Campus Taskforce, we’d like to invite a small group of elite female
    students from four top London universities (LSE, UCL, KCL, and Imperial
    College London) to attend our breakfast sessions to understand and explore the
    financial industry with the help of industry leaders and senior executives.

    We are excited to offer this opportunity to young talented female students to
    help them to gain more exposure to financial markets, whilst networking with
    like-minded peers.

    The three breakfast sessions will cover the below topics respectively:

    - **Understanding the Financial Market Structure** - Friday, 2 November, 9:00am - 10:00am
    - **Fintech and LSEG Initiatives** - Thursday, 22 November, 9:00am - 10:00am
    - **Alternative Career Options in Finance** - Wednesday, 5 December, 9:00am – 10:00am

    For more information on what each session is about, take a look at the PDF attached.

    Location: LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London EC4M 7LS

    These breakfasts are _mutually exclusive_ and we are taking five students from
    Imperial per session.

    If you're interested, email DoCSoc at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and they'll pass your
    details onto us!

    _Please note that this event is not organised by DoCSoc._
  </sponsor>
  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>London Stock Exchange Group Internship and Graduate Scheme</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg">
    Joining London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) is a unique opportunity to test yourself while working
    in a variety of roles with one of the world’s most influential and innovative markets infrastructure
    businesses.

    We provide valuable services for a wide range of customers, focusing on Intellectual Property, Risk
    and Balance Sheet Management and Capital Formation. The Group plays a vital economic and social
    role in enabling companies to access funds for growth and development. Over recent years, we have
    expanded our operations to become one of the leading global organisations of our kind, employing
    approximately 4,500 people around the world.

    As we’ve evolved, technology has become an increasingly crucial component of our global
    operations. LSEG Technology is the power behind many of the world’s financial markets, delivering
    robust, scalable, high-performance technologies; including broker, exchange, market data, risk
    management, surveillance and clearing and settlement products.

    **A rotational graduate programme like no other**

    We have a number of vacancies remaining within our Technology graduate programme. This
    programme is an opportunity for our graduates to rotate across a number of the Group’s key
    business areas within Technology.

    Over the course of your graduate programme, you’ll come to discover how diverse and far-reaching
    our operations really are. You could find yourself working with emerging technologies such as
    Blockchain, for example, or guiding clients through regulatory challenges – and towards new
    opportunities – in a constantly shifting financial landscape.

    You’ll also have every opportunity to develop your technical abilities, whilst broadening your
    commercial awareness and wider skillset. At the end of the programme, you’ll be matched with the
    business area that’s most closely aligned with your talents and interests, whilst best supporting the
    wider needs of the Group.

    **The LSEG Internship – a glimpse of what’s to come**

    Our summer internship programme, for penultimate-year students, is designed to mirror LSEG’s
    graduate programme, and provides a solid grounding in the Group’s operations and the many
    markets in which we operate. So, whether you see your future in Business or Technology, you’ll get
    to discover what life is really like as an LSEG graduate.

    The programme is a great opportunity for us to spot talent, and many of our interns go on to join
    LSEG in a permanent role on completing their studies.

    **Help shape the future of our business**

    We are looking for individuals who will help us embark on the next phase of our growth: graduates
    from all disciplines who are motivated by a fast-paced environment, and who thrive on working in a
    variety of roles as part of a critical business project. As a multinational organisation, our workforce is
    extremely diverse, and we are committed to maintaining an open, inclusive environment that is
    welcoming of employees from all backgrounds.

    Now that the LSEG graduate and internship programme runs right across the Group, it is a
    particularly exciting time to join us. While the City of London is the global hub for our programmes,
    there are increasing opportunities for new joiners to support our expanding operations overseas.
    This may be in the form of project work from our London office, though some of our graduates have
    had the opportunity to complete rotations within our different global offices.

    However you look at it, this is a unique springboard for a varied, challenging and impactful career in
    the financial markets.

    To find out more about the broad range of opportunities on offer at London Stock Exchange Group,
    visit https://www.lseg.com/graduates. **Applications close on December 23rd 2018**.
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
