<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

	<image width="70"
				 src="https://i.imgur.com/KVPpM6S.png"
				 alt="Revel Bar"
				 title="nth week of biscuit complaints" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    It's that time of the week again that I send an email.

    We're gearing up for the candidate reveal and elections starting NOON,
    FRIDAY 2ND MARCH! Don't forget to vote at vote.union.ic.ac.uk from Friday
    onwards! There'll also be a 'Meet the Candidates' event, more on that below!

    The other big thing happening this week is
    [Fiesta del Revel](https://revel.london). If you have a ticket that
    you wish to transfer to someone else, please email docsoc@ic.ac.uk for help.

    Otherwise, see not so much below and have a nice week :).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc: Meet the Candidates</heading>
  <text>
    We are currently planning to run a 'Meet the Candidates' event at the start
    of next week, where all of the candidates for DoCSoc (and DoC
    Departmental Representative) positions have a chance to deliver a short
    speech.

    This is your chance to ask any questions you may have, and hear more about
    what each candidate is campaigning for!

    The exact date, time, and location will be confirmed later this week, but
    this will probably happen around lunchtime in one of the lecture theatres.

    Look out for further information on our
    [Facebook Page](https://www.facebook.com/pg/ICDocSoc/events/).
  </text>

  <heading>Status of Hoodies, T-Shirts, and Beanies</heading>
  <text>
    Hoodies and T-shirts have finally been ordered and are on their way. They
    will be arriving later this week, so you should be informed about
    distribution shortly if you ordered a Hoodie, T-shirt, or Beanie.
  </text>

  <heading>DoCSoc Hosts Google Hash Code</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="397017594079193" />
    <links>
      <link href="https://hashcode.withgoogle.com">Register</link>
    </links>
    <text>
      **Registration deadline: 11.00 TOMORROW, 28th FEBRUARY!**

      Hash Code is a team programming competition organised by Google for
      students and industry professionals across Europe, the Middle East and
      Africa. You pick your team and programming language, we pick a Google
      engineering problem for you to solve.

      *Remember that you will have to to sign up on the Hash Code website to
      participate.*
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>IC Health Hack 18</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1698424526881229" />
    <text>
      **Registration will open in two batches: Thursday, March 1st at 20:00,
      Saturday, March 3rd at 12:00.**

      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society and
      ICSM Coding Society present the IC HealthHack 2018!

      Combining bioengineering, coding skills and domain-specific medical
      knowledge, this Hackathon is aimed at developing serious games in the
      public health sector. Over the weekend, teams will compete to develop
      solutions to real-life healthcare challenges, before pitching to a panel
      of experts.
    </text>
  </event>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Nik.
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
