<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="G-Research Coding Challenge"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi all!

    **Today**, we have an amazing event with G-Research, open to students of all
    skill levels! This event is not one you want to miss, so head down to
    Skempton 060 today around 18:15 for a prompt 18:30 start. Have fun!
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/kgo5FRo.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-15T18:15:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-15T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      Calling all software engineering enthusiasts that enjoy a bit of healthy
      competition!

      G-Research is a leading quantitative research and technology company. By
      using the latest scientific techniques, we produce world-beating predictive
      research and build advanced technology to analyse the world's data.

      Join us for the G-Research Coding Challenge where you will compete in
      teams in a series of progressively difficult challenges. Open to absolutely
      anyone, you will be competing in teams of 2-3 to build a natural language
      calculation engine (no prior NLP experience required). The challenges will
      cover things like evaluation of arithmetic expressions to unit conversions
      and equation solving.

      We will allocate teams when you arrive, you don't need to find a team
      beforehand - but feel free to bring your own team if you would like. To
      take part, you will need to bring at least one laptop per team.

      There will be a live leaderboard up on the projector to give all teams the
      opportunity to see where they are placing throughout the challenge. 1st,
      2nd and 3rd place (decided by a point system) will win prizes!
      Following the event there will be pizza and a chance for you to informally
      talk with our employees about internships, graduate roles and life at G-Research.

      Languages for the challenges - .NET Core 2 , Java and Maven or Python 3
      with client starter kits provided when you login.

      Registration beforehand is optional. To register, please email graduates@gresearch.co.uk
      detailing whether you are registering as an individual or a team.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/277450032912641/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
