<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

	<image width="50"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/EHrhWOw.png"
    alt="Macarons"
    title="To the person last week, you have too much imagination." />
  <hr/>

	<text>
    Hi all,

    To be honest there's not much this week, since we're all gearing up for IC
    Hack! Still, if you have a few moments, have a look at the SACAS, Felix's
    Tech Contributor opportunity and maybe apply for a Spring Insight Week at
    BlackRock!
	</text>
  <hr/>

  <heading>SACAs Nominations Open</heading>
  <text>
    The Student Academic Choice Awards - or SACAs for short - are Imperial
    College Union's flagship event for empowering students to recognise, reward
    and celebrate excellence among College staff.

    Every student at Imperial will have the chance to recognise the innovation,
    skill, engagement and energy of the staff that they interact with on a daily
    basis.  This is your chance to say 'Thank You' to the lecturers,
    supervisors, demonstrators and administrators who have helped you through
    tough times or gone above and beyond to explain a concept or support your
    research. If there's anyone who stands out to you, then let them know - by
    nominating them for a SACA.

    Eight awards in total cover all faculties, departments and campuses, as well
    as all modes of study – undergraduate, taught postgraduate and doctoral
    research.

    The eight Student Academic Choice Awards available are:

    - Best Supervision
    - Best Tutoring
    - Best Graduate Teaching Assistant
    - Best Teaching for Undergraduates
    - Best Support Staff
    - Best Innovation
    - Best Feedback
    - Best Teaching for Postgraduates

    Every nominee will receive a famous 'We Think You're Great' SACA mug - and
    the shortlistees will be invited to the SACAs Ceremony in May 2018.

    You can nominate as many people as you would like, across all categories-
    and if your nominee is shortlisted, you might win a free ticket to the
    Ceremony!

    [Nominate someone now](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/student-academic-choice-awards)
  </text>

  <heading>Felix Seeking Tech Contributors</heading>
  <text>
    Felix, Imperial's weekly newspaper, is planning to expand its tech section
    after a successful first term and they figured Computing students might be
    interested in joining. The tech section covers popular science topics
    ranging from Formula 1 aerodynamics to gene drives, with the plan this term
    being to get involved with established electronics giants and review their
    upcoming gadgets and devices. Of course, the usual op-eds will make their
    appearance as well.

    If this is something that interests you, send an email to
    tecfelix@imperial.ac.uk
  </text>
  <hr/>

  <heading>BlackRock Technology – Spring Insight Week Opportunity</heading>
  <sponsor company="blackrock">
    Want to have a career that's exciting, rewarding and full of possibilities?

    At BlackRock, we challenge ourselves – and each other – to collectively
    raise our game. Our people are passionate about what they do and are
    dedicated to bringing new and innovative approaches to their work.

    BlackRock combines the best of being a technology pioneer and financial
    leader. Over the past 29 years, we've grown from an entrepreneurial startup
    into the world's largest investment manager by putting technology - and
    continuous innovation - at the heart of our business.

    ## The Opportunity

    Our Spring Insight Programme offers an immersive
    experience within the Technology division in our London office. You'll
    participate in work shadowing, a group project, networking and social
    events, whilst gaining valuable work experience at a globally recognised
    brand.

    This opportunity is a week-long initiative (taking place 16 – 20 April 2018)
    for motivated students graduating in 2020.

    ## Next Steps
    If you'd like to be considered for this programme, please
    [apply online](https://blackrock.tal.net/vx/brand-0/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/1/opp/2381-Spring-Insight-Programme-EMEA/en-GB)
    with your CV by Sunday, 4th February 2018.

    **Once you have applied, you will receive a link to complete a short coding
    assessment – please complete this assessment within 4 days of applying.**

    For more information on BlackRock and our Technology, please visit our
    [Engineering Blog](http://rockthecode.io/).

    Ready to make an impact? Start your journey with BlackRock and apply today!
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
