<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dFBKqHp.jpg"
    alt="Granola bars on a plate"
    title="Nature Valley granola bars are great until they start crumbling apart." />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Last week was yet again another busy week with Facebook's talk on Search and
    Machine Learning, NextJump's workshop on React Native and a wholesome Board
    Games night. In the coming week, we're bringing you even more events, including
    a Game AI workshop, escape room, sponsor event and more. Keep on reading for
    more info!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    Searching for internships or placements? Check out our Sponsors Portal, where
    you can find out more details about our sponsors, read their blog posts and
    see their open internship/placement positions. You can also upload your CV
    and directly apply to all of our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>CGCU Mascotry</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/kVlZUUF.jpg" />
  <text>
    Last Wednesday, seven members of the City and Guilds Union (CGCU), including
    five from DoCSoc, undertook the incredible feat of stealing the Davy Lamp
    from the Royal School of Mines Union (RSMU). Tensions were high as Memeperial [misleadingly reported](https://www.facebook.com/memeperial/photos/a.1243171632387880/1982226031815766)
    that it was CGCU which instead succumbed to the hands of the Royal College of
    Science Union (RSCU) at mascotry. However, with an unexpected twist, the
    true identities of the mascot's kidnappers [were revealed](https://www.facebook.com/memeperial/photos/a.1243171632387880/1982393761798993).

    On Thursday the CGCU struck again, raiding the RCSU office to capture their
    mascot Theta. This time out of the 13 rescuers, a whopping 10 were members of
    DoCSoc! Great job, and looking forward to the Medics' mascot being stolen!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Introduction to AI in Games</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DcfMVdC.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-06T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-06T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Curious about Artificial Intelligence and its practical applications in games?

      Join DoCSoc GameDev as we learn about Artificial Intelligence in modern games
      with a short talk followed by a workshop on the application of the Monte Carlo
      Tree Search Algorithm through coding a Connect 4 game in Python.

      The workshop will be run by Daniel Hernandez and Peter York who are both on
      course for PhDs in AI applied to videogames at the University of York.

      The only thing you will need is a laptop with Python 3 installed and the
      workshop is open to programmers of all skill levels.

      Food will of course be provided, with informal drinks following the session at the
      Union afterwards! If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let
      us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/359358464805044/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Gets Locked In A Room</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/8FZ7WRA.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-07T15:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-07T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Locked In A Room, 1 Western Gateway, Royal Victoria Docks, ExCeL London, E161X">
    <text>
      It is finally time for the first social event of the year! Congratulations
      to all of you who managed to get tickets for Locked In A Room. Join DoCSoc
      in an evening full of solving puzzles, discovering clues and trying your
      best to escape a locked room in 60 minutes. You will get the option to form
      your own teams of 5 and if you don’t have a team, you can always find one
      once you reach there.

      Be sure to arrive by 3:30pm so we can begin promptly.

      There's exciting news **for those of you who didn’t manage to get a ticket**:
      there will another session on the 14th of November! Make sure to keep an
      eye out for the tickets for this session, which will go live on Tuesday 6th
      November at 1PM.

      Have fun escaping!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/676199486113604/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Bloomberg CodeCon Qualifiers</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/USp4vxv.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-09T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-09T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      Face off against your classmates at CodeCon, a live coding competition hosted by Bloomberg.

      Push your programming and problem solving skills to the limit against the clock!

      The top finishers from each university will be invited to Bloomberg's London
      headquarters for a showdown against finalists from schools across the globe
      and a chance to win amazing prizes!

      Food and drinks will be provided! If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.

      Be sure to **RSVP and register** for CodeCon [here](http://tinyurl.com/yb6ugj36).
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://tinyurl.com/yb6ugj36">RSVP/Register</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/329054374310881/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Liquidnet In-Office Interactive Session: Trading, AI and Augmenting Behavior</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9yqANVy.png" width="80" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-27T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-27T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 21st Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London, EC2A 2EW"
    external="true">
    <text>
      JOIN LIQUIDNET CHIEF DATA SCIENTIST TOM DORIS, PHD. to discuss challenges
      in adoption and adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct
      the methods that were effective in overcoming the obstacles, and review
      similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology
      team, our Recruitment Team and Product Team once the interactive session
      has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-trading-ai-and-augmenting-behavior-tickets-51867766887">Eventbrite</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG WIN Breakfast Sessions for Young Female Talents</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg" />
  <event startDate="2018-11-22T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-11-22T10:00:00+00:00"
    location="LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London, EC4M 7LS"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Limited spaces available!**

      The **LSEG WIN (Women Inspired Network)** Community aims to provide a
      platform to celebrate female talents within and outside the Group. As part of the
      WIN Campus Taskforce, we’d like to invite a small group of elite female
      students from four top London universities (LSE, UCL, KCL, and Imperial
      College London) to attend our breakfast sessions to understand and explore the
      financial industry with the help of industry leaders and senior executives.

      We are excited to offer this opportunity to young talented female students to
      help them to gain more exposure to financial markets, whilst networking with
      like-minded peers.

      The three breakfast sessions will cover the below topics respectively:

      - **Fintech and LSEG Initiatives** - Thursday, 22 November, 9:00am - 10:00am
      - **Alternative Career Options in Finance** - Wednesday, 5 December, 9:00am – 10:00am

      For more information on what each session is about, take a look at the PDF attached.

      Location: LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London EC4M 7LS

      These breakfasts are _mutually exclusive_ and we are taking five students from
      Imperial per session.

      If you're interested, email DoCSoc at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and they'll pass your
      details onto us!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Google DevFest London 2018</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-12-01T09:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-01T18:30:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London (South Kensington Campus)">
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/yHopaE6.jpg" />
    <text>
      DoCSoc is proud to be hosting Google DevFest London on our very own campus
      this year! Read on for more information.

      **Learn the latest in web, mobile, cloud, machine learning and more at the
      UK's largest community organised free conference.**

      GDG London, Google and DoCSoc present GDG Devfest London - a multi-track
      event covering: cloud and machine learning; web; mobile; assistant; codelabs
      and demos.

      To find out more about speakers, topics and agenda, visit devfest.gdg.london

      Don’t miss out on a fun, interesting and informative day of expert speakers,
      demo stands coding labs and much much more.

      You’ll also get the chance to network with experts from Google, Imperial
      College and beyond and learn more from some of the amazing developer
      communities we have in London.

      There will be people taking photographs and potentially filming the event.
      By attending you agree to the possibility of being photographed and filmed
      once inside the venue.

      Thank you for your interest in GDG DevFest London and we look forward to seeing you there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/gdg-devfest-london-2018-tickets-50723931645">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/255733691798751">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <sponsor company="facebook">
    We have a number of new 2019 Security Engineering Summer internship opportunities
    open for applications. Please see further details below:

    - Our programme will start on 24th June and last for 12 weeks
    - We are open to Bachelors, Masters and PhD students who are in their penultimate
    year of study/graduating in 2020
    - We are specifically interested in students that are studying Computer Science,
    Cyber Security, Information Security, Information Forensics or other related degrees.
    We are also particularly interested in students that partake in Cyber Security activities
    and events such as CTF (Capure the Flag), bug bounty participation or something similar

    Please find more info and application links below:

    - 2019 Security Engineer, Intern (Product) - London - https://www.facebook.com/careers/jobs/285333835643814/
    - 2019 Security Engineer, Intern (CERT &amp; Detection Infra) - London - https://www.facebook.com/careers/jobs/710700472618593/
    - 2019 Security Analyst, Intern (Dublin) - https://www.facebook.com/careers/jobs/553516991773728/
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
