<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/M1avYQf.png"
    alt="Desserts from the DoCSoc and CGCU Diversity Event"
    title="A selection of dessert canapes fom the diversity event last week!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    The past week was hectic with two major events: our joint diversity panel
    and networking event (photo of desserts above) with CGCU and Google DevFest
    London. Both events were great fun, and thanks to everyone who attended and
    helped out!

    As the Department of Computing goes into December exams (or in the case of
    second years, their final week of Pintos), the next week will be quieter.
    Despite the super-short digest, we have some exciting things to announce,
    including a festive Christmas party, Pintos glasses and DoCSoc swag!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Pintos Glasses</heading>
  <text>
    If you're a second year, join DoCSoc in celebrating the end of Pintos! We're
    handing out Pintos pint glasses at 7pm on Friday around labs. If you can't
    make it, don't worry! There will be another collection the week after
    (details TBC).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Swag</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/XFjBZW5.png" />
  <text>
    This Wednesday, DoCSoc's 2018-19 selection of branded swag will go online on
    the Union's online store, with DoCSoc hoodies (in black/yellow, heather/navy
    and burgundy/charcoal), T-shirts (mens and womens sizes available) and
    beanies (one size fits all, perfect for the winter!).

    More details will follow in a separate email later this week!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Organisers</heading>
  <text>
    With DevFest over (thanks to everyone who volunteered!), our focus is now
    on IC Hack 19. This year, we're back bigger than ever, targeting 400 attendees.
    With help needed in Logistics, Hacker Experience, Sponsorship, Marketing
    and more, IC Hack 19 is an opportunity to go beyond the standard role of a
    volunteer and become a _core organiser_ of a major hackathon. For more information,
    join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/)
    group.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Christmas Party</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Kh0oZqD.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-12-04T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-04T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217/218">
    <text>
      Come put on your Santa hat and Christmas jumper, and join us for a night
      of festive fun! There'll be mince pies, Christmassy snacks, mulled wine,
      hot chocolate, and more. We'll also be playing some party games, so come
      get into the holiday spirit with us at the end of a busy term!

      If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few
      days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/256520188364519/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>LSEG WIN Breakfast Sessions for Young Female Talents</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg" />
  <event startDate="2018-12-05T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2018-12-05T10:00:00+00:00"
    location="LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London, EC4M 7LS"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Limited spaces available!**

      The **LSEG WIN (Women Inspired Network)** Community aims to provide a
      platform to celebrate female talents within and outside the Group. As part of the
      WIN Campus Taskforce, we’d like to invite a small group of elite female
      students from four top London universities (LSE, UCL, KCL, and Imperial
      College London) to attend our breakfast sessions to understand and explore the
      financial industry with the help of industry leaders and senior executives.

      We are excited to offer this opportunity to young talented female students to
      help them to gain more exposure to financial markets, whilst networking with
      like-minded peers.

      Our last breakfast session is **Alternative Career Options in Finance**, on
      Wednesday, 5 December, 9:00am – 10:00am. For more details, see the PDF attached.

      Location: LSEG City of London Global Headquarters, 10 Paternoster Square, London EC4M 7LS

      If you're interested, email DoCSoc at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and they'll pass your
      details onto us!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
