<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Haskell and Serverless Internships at Artificial"
  logos="false">

  <sponsor company="artificiallabs">
    ​

    _Already applied to us? Email us and let us know if you haven't yet expressed
    interest and/or prior experience in Haskell or serverless technologies._

    **[Artificial](https://artificial.io/)** is hiring engineering interns with
    a specific interest in either functional programming or serverless technologies
    for two of our teams:

    - **Build** - with challenges including modelling complex insurance contracts where correctness is key, the Build team is looking for candidates with a keen interest in **functional programming, type theory/type systems and Haskell**;
    - **Serverless** - with a need to rapidly scale a wide range of features for our clients, our insurance platform is compromised of **rapidly scalable microservices**, where technologies required include using Go, Node.js and Python to build serverless functions.

    **Artificial**'s mission is to make insurance frictionless. From building the
    foundation to scalable, market leading insurance software with ArtificialOS,
    to leading the future of pricing and claims with machine learning, we're
    building market leading tools to radically improve the efficiency and
    profitability of insurance companies.

    We're looking for students who have demonstrated an interest in the
    technologies we use and push their skills by working on our platform. If
    you're an undergraduate who has worked with Haskell beyond the first year
    course (perhaps choosing Haskell for your WACC project) or have gained experience
    working with serverless and cloud technologies, we think you'd be a great fit
    for us.

    Interested in our **engineering roles**? To apply, click [here](https://artificial.workable.com/j/88F255BEEC)
    and let us know your specific field of interests in the cover letter section.

    We're also looking for **machine learning interns**. If you're interested in this
    area, you can apply for a machine learning internship [here](https://artificial.workable.com/j/D7F425D4C0).
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
