<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="70"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/L2vMIuM.png"
    alt="Pie Chart of Last Week's Biscuit Vote"
    title="Thanks for voting, people who care about the biscuit &lt;3!" />

  <hr />

  <text>
    Hello everyone,

    Welcome to another week of the DoCSoc digest! It's even more-on-time this
    week!

    This week, we bring you a Microsoft Cognitive Services workshop!

    **Also, you can sign up for our very own Valentine's Service, only until
    Thursday 8th February. If here is someone special who you would like to send
    a rose and message to,
    [sign up here](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdeGAXfxl-DBHFd1xDdP3vMIRcP7oEWZWgJWSYt51-MdayGgw/viewform).

    Last week, over 70 of you voted and decided the future of the biscuit.
    From now on, the bottom of the digest will include a link to a form where
    biscuits for the next week may be suggested. The biscuit that we send out
    remains at the discretion of the DoCSoc committee, but your suggestions
    should really help. Plus, we'll credit you for the suggestion next to the
    biscuit form link!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Microsoft Cognitive Services: Hands On Workshop</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="451262598634020" />
    <text>
      Come along to learn about Microsoft Cognitive Services, including the
      Custom Vision AI Service. After learning about these services, there will
      be a hands on workshop so you can see for yourself how easy it is to build
      and deploy your projects using these services!

      All experience levels welcome and please make sure you bring your laptop
      with you. Food and drink will be provided at the event and there will also
      be giveaways!
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>The Valentine's Bar Night</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1607380125981757" />
    <text>
      It's time for the first Bar Night of 2018! Once again, we'll be meeting in
      Metric at 7pm for an evening of free drinks and great conversation.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to any member of DoCSoc.
      Tokens are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.
    </text>
  </event>

  <heading>Internships 101</heading>
  <text>
    <!-- TODO: Pending Information -->
    TODO: PENDING
  </text>

  <heading>UROP 101</heading>
  <text>
    <!-- TODO: Pending Information -->
    TODO: PENDING
  </text>

  <heading>JetBrains: Kotlin Hands-On</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="166048430696844" />
  </event>

  <heading>DoCSoc hosts Google Hash Code</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="397017594079193" />
    <links>
      <link href="https://hashcode.withgoogle.com">Tickets</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2018</heading>
  <event>
    <facebook id="1698424526881229" />
  </event>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>

  <text>
    This week's biscuit brought to you by: Biscuit Voters!
    [Submit Biscuit](https://docsoc.co.uk/suggest-biscuit).
  </text>
</email>
