<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image width="50"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/V3kxYPg.png"
    alt="Amaretti Biscuits"
    title="Motion to stop biscuit images? Seriously, coming up with unique biscuits is actually quite hard, finding a good picture is even harder. Why not some sweet treats?" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Another week, another digest!&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;Yeah it's
    Wednesday..&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;

    Check out our DoCSoc Education volunteering initiative below to teach
    Python to life sciences students. It's a great way to get experience in
    teaching students!

    If you managed to get a ticket, also look forward to participating in IC
    Hack 18, the largest student-run hackathon in the UK, this weekend. It's
    bound to be a blast! If you suddenly can't make it, please cancel your
    ticket on Eventbrite so that someone else currently on the waitlist can
    attend in your place.

    Without further ado...
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Volunteers Needed for DoCSoc Education</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/VKAshFk.png" alt="Coding 101 Banner" />
  <text>
    *As you may have heard, we're starting a new initiative called DoCSoc
    Education aiming to teach students from other courses to code.*

    Our first venture will be [teaching Python to students from life sciences
    courses](https://www.facebook.com/events/333505960463269/), and we could
    definitely use some volunteers to help. You don't have to be amazing at
    Python - if you're interested in helping, let us know by either sending us
    an email (docsoc@imperial.ac.uk), or PMing us on
    [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ICDocSoc/).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Accenture Powerful Minds Competition</heading>
  <sponsor company="accenture">
    Discovering an insight into the way your mind works can be interesting. Food
    to boost your brain can also be tasty. And a little competition can be fun?
    We've combined all of these together to bring you a brand new initiative
    beginning in January.

    ## What's in it for you?
    - Chance to win cash prizes towards your society/club. First prize a massive
    £1,000! Second £250 and third £100.
    - Each society/club that signs up will also receive an assortment of
    delicious breakfast bars for your members to enjoy! *(editor's note: we'll
    figure out how to distribute these later)*
    - Individual weekly spot prizes: Accenture branded hoodies to keep you warm
    and Clifton StrengthsFinder assessment codes to help you discover more about
    yourself with an in-depth report of your strengths.

    If you would like to participate, use [this
    link](https://ad.doubleclick.net/ddm/clk/411273196;211960615;a).
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Nik Vangerow"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary"
    facebook="nik.vangerow">
    That's all for now!

    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
