<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="American Express - Student and Graduate Jobs"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi all!

    American Express have got in touch to advertise their student and graduate
    jobs. Read on to learn more about the company and how to apply!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <sponsor company="amex">
    There’s a difference between having a job and making a difference.

    American Express has been making a difference in people’s lives for over 160
    years, backing them in moments big and small, granting access, tools, and
    resources to take on their biggest challenges and reap the greatest rewards.

    Because we believe that the best way to back our customers is to back our people.
    Here at American Express, we’ve made a difference in the lives of our people,
    providing a culture of learning and collaboration, and helping them with what
    they need to succeed and thrive.

    We have their backs as they grow their skills, conquer new challenges, or
    even take time to spend with their family or community.

    When they’re ready to take on a new career path, we’re right there with them,
    giving them the guidance and momentum into the best future they envision.

    Students will work building enterprise scale Java and JavaScript applications
    with a host of tools and frameworks. You’ll find all sorts of things across
    our software products, like Spring Cloud and Webflux for reactive Java services,
    or Node.js driving React web applications and even polyglot microservices.
    We’re often experimenting with new technology; it’s all about picking the
    right tool for the right job.

    Are you up for the challenge?

    -	We need creative, collaborative and curious thinkers
    -	Can identify opportunities for innovation and change
    -	Have a passion for technology and desire to learn
    -	Ability to effectively communicate with non-technical business partners
    -	Capable of working well in a team environment and contributing

    The powerful backing of American Express.

    Don’t make a difference without it.

    Don’t live life without it.

    https://jobs.americanexpress.com/jobs?page=1&amp;tags=UKUndergrad
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
