<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<email title="Welcome from DoCSoc - Mums and Dads Information Inside!">
  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Welcome to your first year at Imperial! For those of you who missed our
    induction talk, we're the Department of Computing Society and we run over
    fifty events per year, both social and careers-related, to make sure you
    get the most out of uni.

    Here's some **important information** for you to keep in mind for the
    coming weeks.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Mums and Dads</heading>
  <text>

    Every first year is assigned a college family. Next Monday, your Haskell
    lecture with Tony Field will end early so you can be at the Mums and Dads
    Lunch (12:30 - 13:30) in HXLY 341/342 for you to meet your family, collect
    your DoCSoc swag bags (with loads of goodies inside) and have sandwiches
    and snacks on us!

    **Not yet signed up to Mums and Dads?** If you haven't signed up to Mums
    and Dads, you will be automatically signed up to a family without your
    hobbies/preferences being taken into account. Be sure to sign up **before
    the end of this Friday 4th October** by going here: http://mad.docsoc.co.uk/fresher.
    Don't forget to check your email to verify your sign-up after!

    **Haven't got your family allocation yet?** We'll be releasing final
    allocations over the weekend.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Facebook/Messenger Group</heading>
  <text>

    Every year group has a dedicated Facebook group and Messenger group chat.
    This is the primary way for DoC students to communicate. To join these
    groups, see the links below:

    - Facebook Messenger group chat: https://docsoc.co.uk/y1chat
    - Facebook group: https://docsoc.co.uk/y1fb
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>How do I find out about events?</heading>
  <text>

    The primary way DoCSoc advertises events is via our weekly digest emails,
    sent to your email addresses every Sunday. These contain lots of information,
    but be sure to read through every email carefully.

    We also publicise events over Facebook, so be sure to like and follow our
    page here: https://www.facebook.com/ICDoCSoc/. Our evening events almost
    always have **free pizza and soft drinks** (usually one box between two attendees)
    and we ask that you **RSVP on Facebook** if you're interested in an event so
    we can order enough pizza for everyone.

    We will also communicate last-minute changes to events over year group
    Messenger chats linked above.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Intro to Linux</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/jXzJVPf.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2019-10-07T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-07T19:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Are you a first year who is new to the world of computing? Then come and join
      us at our first academic event of the year!

      Familiarity with the Linux/Unix environment and the command line is arguably
      one of the most important skills a software engineer today can have. Many
      often find it difficult at first - even if they've got quite a bit of coding
      experience, but DoCSoc is here to help!

      We'll be covering fundamental command line skills and Linux-related knowledge
      that will be useful for you, as well as some more advanced tricks and looking
      at some different text editors. You'll also have a chance to ask any questions
      you may have at the end of the talk.

      This event is aimed at people who have never had any experience with Linux or
      the Linux terminal.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.docsoc.co.uk/intro-to-linux">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Other Stuff</heading>
  <text>

    A few other things to give a heads up on:
    - Be sure to check out the Computing/JMC common room on the same corridor
    as the labs entrance and Student Tea Point.
    - The Student Tea Point's facilities are provided courtesy of DoCSoc. We
    have provided students with a coffee machine and buy coffee beans throughout
    term time (with the next delivery coming soon!). All we ask is that you
    keep the tea point tidy and clean up after yourselves!

    If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to ask us on your year
    group chat or email us at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.

    Looking forward to seeing you around!

    Sincerely,\
    DoCSoc Committee '19/20

  </text>
</email>