<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="Reading Groups Kick-Off Next Monday!"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">

  <text>
    Are you interested in learning more about research in academia? Are you looking for project
    ideas
    in the area of Computer Science?

    If you're the inquisitive type, come along to our first Reading Groups of the year next **Monday
    the 28th of October**!
    Reading Groups are targeted at higher year students (postgraduates especially) who are
    interested
    in the kind of research that happens in Computer Science.

    For more details take a look at the event information below and RSVP on Facebook!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Reading Groups by Nuri Cingillioglu and Dr. Antoine Cully</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/rR75XiS.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-28T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-28T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217">
    <text>
      We are happy to announce that the Reading Groups are back! Reading Groups are lectures/panels
      where researchers talk about their current work, aimed at final and penultimate year
      undergraduate, as well as and postgraduate students. Our main goal for organising such talks
      is to expose students to different types of research in Computer Science. Our first 2 Reading
      Groups will be by Nuri Cingillioglu and Dr. Antoine Cully.

      Reading Group by Dr. Antoine Cully 1 - 1.30pm

      Title: Creative Learning algorithms for Resilient Robots

      Abstract: Reinforcement learning algorithms are tightly linked with the optimisation of
      functions to find the best solution according to one or several objectives. Recently, we
      developed a new family of optimisation algorithms, named Quality-Diversity optimisation, that
      contrasts with classic algorithms. Instead of searching for a single solution,
      Quality-Diversity algorithms are searching for a large collection of both diverse and
      high-performing solutions. With this approach, robots are capable of finding creative
      solutions to overcome complicated situations, like loss of a leg. During this seminar, I will
      show several examples of applications of these algorithms.

      Reading Group by Nuri Cingillioglu 1.30 - 2pm

      Title: Computational Neuro-Symbolic Reasoning and how machines can learn elements of logical
      thinking

      Abstract: "Can machines think?" - asked Alan Turing in his 1950 seminal paper "Computing
      Machinery and Intelligence". Recent advances in deep learning are yielding great results
      across practical applications such as natural language processing, image recognition and
      reinforcement learning; however, how machines can incorporate elements of logical thought and
      learn to reason are open to research. Combining machine learning with logic-based expert
      systems in order to get the best of both worlds are becoming increasingly more popular. In
      this talk, I’ll give a brief overview of my involvement in the field of neuro-symbolic
      reasoning and discuss how the future of Artificial Thought is evolving.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/519302712237572/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>
</email>