<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/25DNbII.jpg"
    alt="Tea and biscuits"
    title="Happy Sunday!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    We hope everyone had a good week! From holding a website building talk to trips to
    the V&amp;A exhibition, as well as fulfilling rose deliveries and song requests
    on Valentine's Day, the past week was certainly a busy week for us and we hope
    you enjoyed it as much as we did.

    Next week we have an event with Entrepreneur First's CEO and two EF startup
    founders, so if you're interested in entrepreneurship, be sure to give the
    event details a read! We're also in the run-up to the next Union elections, so
    if you're interested in running, you can find more details below.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Run for DoCSoc's 2019/20 Committee</heading>
  <text>
    **Leadership Elections 2019** are now open and nominations are now open for
    DoCSoc's 2019/20 committee. Nominations will run **until 12:00 on Friday 1st
    March**.

    For more information, check out our email dated 4th February 2019. We'll
    also be sending out a detailed blog post shortly and will be sure to let
    everyone know. In the meantime, there will be a fortnightly **general meeting
    tomorrow** (Monday 18th February) in 217/218. **All prospective candidates
    are strongly encouraged to attend** to get an small insight into what
    goes on behind the scenes.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <heading>EF x DoCSoc: The Founder Mindset with Matt Clifford and guests</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DuO9Hdh.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-02-21T18:15:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-21T21:15:00+00:00"
    location="Clore Lecture Theatre, Huxley Building">
    <text>
      **Matt Clifford is the co-founder and CEO of Entrepreneur First**, the world's
      leading talent investor on a mission to kick-start the next generation of
      globally important deep-tech companies. How? By finding exceptional individuals
      before they’re founders and supporting them to find a co-founder, develop
      an idea and raise investment. Since starting EF seven years ago, he has
      worked with over 1,000 people to build over 200 companies around the world,
      collectively valued at $1.6bn.

      From all the individuals he's met, Matt has had the chance to observe the
      most important, and often hidden, traits that the most successful entrepreneurs
      have in common. In this guest lecture, he will share five mindsets that are
      critical to successful founders, and what you can do to develop them.

      EF will be **inviting TWO ATTENDEES, selected at RANDOM, to visit their offices**
      and meet with Matt or Alice (EF's co-founders), and the team! All you have
      to do is register for a ticket, and sign-in on the day.

      After his lecture, Matt will interview two founders who are at different
      points in their startup journey, **Mostafa ElSayed, CEO and co-founder of
      robotics startup Automata** and **Georgina Kirby, CTO and co-founder of
      Vine Health**.

      More details on Facebook. Please be sure to **RSVP on [Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ef-x-docsoc-the-founder-mindset-with-matt-clifford-georgina-kirby-and-mostafa-elsayed-tickets-56180916634)**!

      Food and drinks will be provided! If you have any **specific dietary requirements**,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ef-x-docsoc-the-founder-mindset-with-matt-clifford-georgina-kirby-and-mostafa-elsayed-tickets-56180916634">Eventbrite (RSVP)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/304995220371967/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Hosts Google Hash Code 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bobaBYY.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-28T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-28T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="RSM G01 ">
    <text>
      DoCSoc is hosting a hub for the Online Qualification Round of Hash Code,
      a team programming competition organized by Google.

      The Online Qualification Round takes place on **February 28th, 2019 at 17:00 UTC**
      and registered teams for **Imperial College London Hub United Kingdom**
      are invited to participate from our hub, which will take place at **RSM G01**.

      Top scoring teams from the Online Qualification Round will then be invited
      to Google’s office to compete in the Final Round of the competition in April.

      If you’re interested in joining our hub, find a team (2 to 4 people) and
      be sure you all register at g.co/hashcode. You’ll then need to select **Imperial
      College London Hub United Kingdom** from the list of hubs in the Judge System
      *after you create your team!*
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/472520253277578/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/YL0vmzT.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-09T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-10T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society and
      ICSM Coding Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2019!

      Combining your skills in bioengineering, coding, and medicine, this
      Hackathon will bring together talented students from each field and will
      be aimed at addressing current medical challenges through technology. Over
      the weekend of 9-10th March 2019, teams will bring their awesome ideas
      to life and develop solutions to real-life healthcare challenges.

      Registration and ticketing will start in the next two weeks following our
      sponsor announcements! Stay tuned and follow our event and page for our
      latest updates!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/293101718230640/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Schlumberger Women in Technology Day</heading>
  <sponsor company="schlumberger">
    Schlumberger are holding a **Women in Technology Day** on **Thursday 28th February**
    and **Friday 1st March**.

    ## What is this event about?

    The Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is an annual INSIGHT EVENT
    designed for future female leaders in engineering sciences.

    The fully-hosted program (see FAQs for more details) allows you to come and
    see for yourself what it's like to work at Schlumberger. In one comprehensive
    day you will get an in-depth view of the diverse career paths an engineer or
    scientist can have in our company, from oil rigs to software technology centres
    to research facilities.

    This event is a phenomenal opportunity for anyone who is looking to get a
    wider view of their career opportunities.

    ## On the schedule:

    Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is a unique chance to explore
    worldwide career opportunities and meet face-to-face with professionals you
    would not meet otherwise. The agenda will include:

    - a welcome drink and dinner on the Thursday
    - a full day at the Schlumberger Cambridge Research Centre on the Friday
    - detailed insights into the different activities and jobs offered
    - an exciting technical challenge
    - a roundtable and Q&amp;A session with International Senior Management

    Register your interest by [applying here](https://www.eiseverywhere.com/womenintechnologyuk).
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
