<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/rF1XCfo.jpg"
    alt="Chocolate chip biscuits and a glass of milk"
    title="Chocolate chip biscuits go very well with a glass of milk!" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome to your second digest of the year!

    Thank you to everyone who came to meet us at the Welcome Fair! We had a great
    time talking to you guys, as well as enjoying some Beat Saber and typing
    competitions together. We'll be announcing the winners and prizes of the
    typing competition in the next digest email... stay tuned for that!

    Now let's dig in some important announcements for the upcoming week.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Autumn Elections - Year Rep Nominations Open</heading>
    <text>
      Nominations in the Union Autumn elections are **NOW OPEN** and close at
      **Midnight on Monday 14 October**!

      It is an opportunity to make your voice heard within the College and the Union.

      Every year students vote for an Academic Year Representative and Wellbeing Year
      Representative.

      The Academic Year Representative receives and collates feedback from their cohort,
      passing this information to the Departmental Representatives or staff as appropriate.
      Academic Representatives have made long-lasting improvements in many areas such as
      the content of curricula, feedback quality and timeliness, exam timetables and formats,
      online learning resources, and the physical facilities available.

      Wellbeing Year Representatives are part of the Wellbeing Representation Network,
      which aims to tackle issues such as stress and pressure, mental health, the quality of
      personal tutoring, how students are supported to be resilient and independent,
      transitioning back into study after time off, and more. Wellbeing Representatives
      will work with College staff, Welfare Officers, and Academic Representatives.

      Year reps make **real change within the department**, with a place on regular Staff
      Student Committee meetings, voicing their concerns to teaching fellows and staff.

      To nominate yourself and for more information on the mentioned and other roles available,
      visit the Union's [Autumn Elections page](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/autumn-elections-2019).
    </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>CGCU Town Hall</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-08T17:00:00+01:00"
  endDate="2018-10-08T18:00:00+01:00"
  location="CAGB 200">
    <text>
      Interested in representing student voice in faculty decisions to how your
      course is ran?

      As an Academic or Wellbeing Year Rep, you're on the forefront of influencing
      what changes to policies the Department of Computing makes during the
      academic year, whether that be issues with teaching staff, usage of student
      space, or improving department support services.

      The CGCU are hosting a Town Hall to help explain the responsibilities
      involved, how to apply, and network with current representatives to understand
      how you can impact student experience, on Tuesday 8th of October from
      5pm - 6pm in CAGB 200 (City &amp; Guilds Building just next to the Main Reception).
      Pizza will be provided during networking, so do come along!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2206124359679290/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Mums &amp; Dads Lunch</heading>
  <event startDate="2018-10-07T12:30:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-07T13:30:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 341/342">
    <text>
      We'll be kicking off the Mums and Dads programme with an opportunity for you
      to meet your MaD parents and have lunch with them! We will be offering free
      food and drinks, as well as issuing a number of challenges. You might even win
      a prize!

      If you're a fresher and you don't have parents assigned yet or have not
      registered, please let us know.

      Mums and Dads parent? Be sure to turn up to this event to meet your children!
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Intro to Linux</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/jXzJVPf.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2019-10-07T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-07T19:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Are you a first year who is new to the world of computing? Then come and join
      us at our first academic event of the year!

      Familiarity with the Linux/Unix environment and the command line is arguably
      one of the most important skills a software engineer today can have. Many
      often find it difficult at first - even if they've got quite a bit of coding
      experience, but DoCSoc is here to help!

      We'll be covering fundamental command line skills and Linux-related knowledge
      that will be useful for you, as well as some more advanced tricks and looking
      at some different text editors. You'll also have a chance to ask any questions
      you may have at the end of the talk.

      _This event is aimed at people who have never had any experience with Linux or
      the Linux terminal._
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.docsoc.co.uk/intro-to-linux">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Game Development Taster</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/wxgRIy9.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2019-10-08T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-08T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 341">
    <text>
      A warm welcome to everyone who is new to Imperial and welcome to the IC Game
      Development Society!

      We will be holding our first weekly session on Tuesday 8th of October from
      18:00 - 20:00 located in Huxley, room 341 run in collaboration with DoCSoc.

      In this session we will try give you a flavour of game development at Imperial
      through a game ideation workshop followed by a gaming social at the end.

      If this hasn't whetted your appetite, hopefully the free pizza will!

      If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few days
      beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/515745679205499/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Sponsors' Exhibition</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1aPxKCI.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2019-10-09T14:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-09T17:00:00+01:00"
    location="Great Hall">
    <text>
      Come to the Great Hall on Wednesday 9th October between 2pm - 5pm to have a
      chance to meet all of DoCSoc's Silver and Gold sponsors this year and grab some swag.

      Whether you are looking for an internship or graduate role, or simply want
      to know more about industry, we really recommend you come along as it's a
      great way to get in direct contact with recruiters and engineers from highly
      regarded companies and should provide invaluable insight into the recruitment process.

      This event is open to all DoCSoc members (automatically includes Computing, JMC, and EIE students).
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2357745387873182/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Next Jump Workshop</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/mejiIuS.png"/>
  <event startDate="2019-10-10T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-10T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060 A/B/C">
    <text>
      Details to come soon in an email in the coming week!

      As usual, this event will be catered with lots of pizza and soft drinks.
      If you're a first year, don't miss out on the first sponsor event of the academic year!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/3056707901011343/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Postgraduate Drinks</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/UoBjyZI.png"/>
  <event startDate="2019-10-11T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-11T23:00:00+01:00"
    location="Eastside Bar">
    <text>
      (If you are an undergraduate, i.e., BEng/MEng Computing/JMC, unfortunately this
      event isn't for you! Otherwise, read ahead!)

      Come join us for our first ever postgraduate social and get to know each other
      over food and drinks, complimentary of DoCSoc. For this event, we have reserved
      a number of tables in Eastside Bar.

      Bar tokens will be provided, eligible for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.
      A limited amount of canapés will be served at the start of the event.

      Please note Eastside Bar (unlike our usual bar venue, Metric) has limited space,
      shared with other bookings, and we will not be able to accommodate all postgraduates
      this time round! We will be returning to Metric for future postgraduate drinks over
      the academic year.

      This event is open to all DoCSoc postgraduates (MScs [not MEng], PhDs, postdocs, etc.).\
      Membership can be purchased for £30 at docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/551673548909850/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Netcraft Introduction</heading>
  <sponsor company="netcraft">
    Netcraft is an innovative internet services company, with offices in central Bath,
    Hammersmith in London and central Manchester from July 2020. Netcraft conducts
    internet research and provides a range of security services, including cybercrime
    disruption, application security testing and automated penetration testing.

    Netcraft provides anti-cybercrime services for hundreds of customers around the world,
    including large Internet companies (e.g. Microsoft, Netflix), banks (e.g. Metro Bank,
    BNP Paribas, Deutsche Bank), retailers (e.g. Gumtree) and the UK Government. It also
    provides similar services to smaller companies at the sharp end of internet financial
    crime, including leading cryptocurrency exchanges and wallet providers (e.g. Coinbase),
    and many banks in developing countries where cybercrime is more prevalent.

    Netcraft has a variety of roles available—including Graduate positions, summer placements,
    and industrial years—at its offices in Bath and London. We are keen to receive applications
    from high performing Computer Science students, although applicants must be able to
    demonstrate the right to work in the United Kingdom. More information on the roles and
    what it's like to work with Netcraft can be found in our recruitment brochure:
    https://www.netcraft.com/NetcraftGraduateBooklet.pdf

    Come and join our talented and growing software development team! Projects involve
    working on a range of our anti-cybercrime services and extending our network
    exploration and internet security services.

    We're looking for:
    - a broad knowledge of internet technology, including a keen interest in network
    security, data mining, machine learning, and web-based user interfaces;
    - attention to detail, and a desire to find things out empirically rather than
    relying on conjecture;
    - demonstrable programming ability and experience.
    - evidence of conspicuous achievement and a strong computing background, equivalent
    to a first-class degree in Computer Science or similar subjects;
    - expressive verbal and written communications skills in English. Skills in other
    languages are also welcomed;
    - a well-developed sense of precaution: someone who likes to plan for the future
    with suitable programming abstractions, automated test suites and version control.

    Prior experience with any of the following technologies and programming languages
    would be helpful, but not essential:
    - Scripting languages like Perl, Python and PHP;
    - Database engines like MySQL;
    - Web languages like JavaScript and TypeScript, and HTML and CSS;
    - Automation tools like Puppet and cloud computing services like AWS;
    - Unix systems programming and administration, and tools like git.

    To apply, email [cv@netcraft.com](mailto:cv@netcraft.com) with your CV.
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Bloomberg - Ada Lovelace Day</heading>
  <sponsor company="bloomberg">
    Join us to celebrate Ada Lovelace Day with a
    special women in technology themed quiz. Put your
    knowledge to the test, get inspired and meet our
    Software engineers from the Bloomberg Women
    in Technology &amp; Allyship Communities.
    Sign up here: http://tinyurl.com/y69erchg

    _More information in the PDF attached._
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Radostin Petrov"
  role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
  facebook="radostin.petrov99">
  Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
