<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/TE1451i.jpg?1"
    alt="Macaroons"
    title="It's finally sunny outside!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Thanks to everyone who came to our talk and panel last week with Entrepreneur
    First's CEO, Matt Clifford, and two startup founders. The event was engaging
    and insightful and we hope those attending found it equally as interesting!

    In the coming week, we'll be holding a **Games Night with G-Research** and
    a hub for for Google Hash Code 2019. We also have a **Revel ticket release
    tomorrow**, so be sure to read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Run for DoCSoc's 2019/20 Committee</heading>
  <text>
    **Leadership Elections 2019** are now open and nominations are now open for
    DoCSoc's 2019/20 committee. Nominations will run **until 12:00 on Friday 1st
    March**.

    We have written a **detailed blog post** which includes the responsibilities for
    every role and other information you should know when running for a committee position.
    If you are looking to run for a DoCSoc committee position, we strongly recommend
    you read this.

    Read the blog post here: https://docsoc.co.uk/elections

    If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk
    or get in touch with a current committee member!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Games Night with G-Research</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/BvlB2x3.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-26T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-26T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 341/342">
    <text>
      Join us and G-Research as we hold our second **games night** of the academic
      year, so come along and relax.  We'll have **board games, games consoles
      and lots of food and drinks**!

      If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few days
      beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2230342137005319/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Hosts Google Hash Code 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bobaBYY.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-28T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-28T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="RSM G01 ">
    <text>
      DoCSoc is hosting a hub for the Online Qualification Round of Hash Code,
      a team programming competition organized by Google.

      The Online Qualification Round takes place on **February 28th, 2019 at 17:00 UTC**
      and registered teams for **Imperial College London Hub United Kingdom**
      are invited to participate from our hub, which will take place at **RSM G01**.

      Top scoring teams from the Online Qualification Round will then be invited
      to Google’s office to compete in the Final Round of the competition in April.

      **Our hub is now fully booked**, but you can still sign up at [g.co/hashcode](https://g.co/hashcode)
      and join the competition with your team from your own location, such as from
      labs or home!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/472520253277578/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Vive la Revelution - Late Release Tickets</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/s0h3ptL.png" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-04T20:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-05T02:00:00+00:00"
    location="Café de Paris, 3 Coventry Street, London, W1D 6BL">
    <text>
      This is your last chance to grab tickets for Vive la Revelution!

      In order to purchase tickets for the event you first need to secure
      **Eventbrite placeholder tickets** at https://revel-london.eventbrite.co.uk.
      Once you have secured a ticket on Eventbrite please head to the **Union website** [here](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/club-society-project-products/computing-products/26254/vive-la-revelution)
      to complete the purchase of your ticket **before 3pm**. Purchases without
      an Eventbrite placeholder ticket will be cancelled.

      If you would like to bring a +1 to the event, then you must buy TWO Eventbrite
      tickets and pay for TWO Union tickets (maximum of 2 tickets per person). If
      you have bought two tickets, then please fill your Imperial shortcode for
      the first ticket and the email address of your +1 for the second ticket on
      Eventbrite.

      Please remember to read the terms and conditions of your ticket after purchasing.
      You must have been a DoCSoc member before 18th February to be eligible for the tickets.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/370168953714798/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/YL0vmzT.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-09T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-10T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society and
      ICSM Coding Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2019!

      Combining your skills in bioengineering, coding, and medicine, this
      Hackathon will bring together talented students from each field and will
      be aimed at addressing current medical challenges through technology. Over
      the weekend of 9-10th March 2019, teams will bring their awesome ideas
      to life and develop solutions to real-life healthcare challenges.

      Registration and ticketing will start in the next two weeks following our
      sponsor announcements! Stay tuned and follow our event and page for our
      latest updates!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/293101718230640/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Schlumberger Women in Technology Day</heading>
  <sponsor company="schlumberger">
    Schlumberger are holding a **Women in Technology Day** on **Thursday 28th February**
    and **Friday 1st March**.

    ## What is this event about?

    The Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is an annual INSIGHT EVENT
    designed for future female leaders in engineering sciences.

    The fully-hosted program (see FAQs for more details) allows you to come and
    see for yourself what it's like to work at Schlumberger. In one comprehensive
    day you will get an in-depth view of the diverse career paths an engineer or
    scientist can have in our company, from oil rigs to software technology centres
    to research facilities.

    This event is a phenomenal opportunity for anyone who is looking to get a
    wider view of their career opportunities.

    ## On the schedule:

    Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is a unique chance to explore
    worldwide career opportunities and meet face-to-face with professionals you
    would not meet otherwise. The agenda will include:

    - a welcome drink and dinner on the Thursday
    - a full day at the Schlumberger Cambridge Research Centre on the Friday
    - detailed insights into the different activities and jobs offered
    - an exciting technical challenge
    - a roundtable and Q&amp;A session with International Senior Management

    Register your interest by [applying here](https://www.eiseverywhere.com/womenintechnologyuk).
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
