<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/Jwzkb5T.jpg"
    alt="Round biscuit with heart jelly in centre"
    title="Valentine's Day!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Does anybody miss skimming through action-packed digest emails from first
    term, hoping that one of your friends _actually_ read the whole thing so you
    can decide what to go to?

    There's tons in this digest for both this week and beyond! Be sure to check out
    our events especially - with upcoming committee elections, Valentine's Day (did someone
    say bar night? 👀🍺), a website building workshop and a V&amp;A trip, perhaps something
    will grab your attention! If you still aren't convinced, perhaps a **20% Nando's
    discount** will encourage you to read through the entire thing?
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Photos Now Available!</heading>
  <text>
    **Photos for IC Hack 19** are now available! Check them out on Facebook [here](https://www.facebook.com/pg/ICDoCSoc/photos/?tab=album&amp;album_id=2589206401095893).
    Get tagging! Photos can also be found in higher quality on [Flickr](https://www.flickr.com/photos/paulmonishbalaji/sets/72157706623151464/).

    _Photos courtesy of our amazing photographer, [Paul Balaji](https://www.instagram.com/thepaulbalaji/)._
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Run for DoCSoc's 2019/20 Committee</heading>
  <text>
    **Leadership Elections 2019** are now open and nominations are now open for
    DoCSoc's 2019/20 committee. Nominations will run **until 12:00 on Friday 1st
    March**.

    For more information, check out our email dated 4th February 2019. We'll
    also be sending out further information and **holding a talk** about our
    positions next Friday. See below for more information!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>20% Nando's Discount</heading>
  <text>
    Craving Nando's? Or thinking of going for a _Nandate_ next week? Don't worry -
    DoCSoc has got you covered!

    We've negotiated a 20% discount at the Nando's High Street Kensington branch
    for our members for in-store purchases. This offer is redeemable by showing
    your College ID card and letting them know you're with DoCSoc.

    _Offer only valid in-store at the Nando's HSK branch with a valid Imperial
    College student ID._
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Learn to Build Your Own Personal Website!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/SxQ7NRx.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-12T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-12T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      _(This event is aimed at non-DoC members. Please share this with any of your
      friends who might be interested!)_

      Ever wanted to create your own website, but didn't know where to start?
      Well, now's your chance!

      We at DoCSoc are hosting a free workshop that will take you through the
      basics of HTML, CSS, and using frameworks and tools like Bootstrap and
      Netlify to get your very own personal website up and running in an hour!

      This event is FREE and open to anybody, however there are limited spaces
      in the lecture room, so if you want a seat, please come on time!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/148709422683450/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>The Yap-Bower Valentine's Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/YwIzsrD.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-14T20:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-15T00:00:00+00:00"
    location="Metric">
    <text>
      You've made it halfway through term - come celebrate with us at the
      Valentine's Bar Night! Whether you've been bitten by the love bug or you're
      living life carefree, everyone's welcome for some free drinks!

      We're also dedicating this bar night to Maurice Yap and Tom Bower, the
      President and Vice President of DoCSoc for the 2017-18 academic year.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to DoCSoc members. Tokens
      are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks. We have the right
      to refuse tokens to members at our discretion.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/240161160195674/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Committee - All You Need To Know</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/vmtlKTY.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-15T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-15T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217/218">
    <text>
      Thinking of running for DoCSoc committee in this year's Leadership Elections?
      Come along to this talk, presented by current members of the committee,
      where we'll be detailing what exactly goes into DoCSoc and what each role entails.

      Read more about the Leadership Elections here: https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/leadership-elections-2019

      Nominate yourself here: https://vote.union.ic.ac.uk/

      Don't forget to read the Candidates' Pack &amp; Election Rules:
      https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/leadership-elections-2019/information-for-candidates.
      Breaking election rules can result in disqualification.

      See you there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/324371091537210/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Goes To The V&amp;A</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/OMNtXiH.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-16T12:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-16T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Victoria &amp; Albert Museum">
    <text>
      DoCSoc is going to the Victoria &amp; Albert Museum for the [Videogames: Design / Play / Disrupt](https://www.vam.ac.uk/exhibitions/videogames)
      exhibition.

      Tickets are free and will be released on Monday 11th February at 13:30 on Eventbrite.

      The tickets will be allocated in two slots entering the exhibition at 12:15
      and 12:45 so choose the tickets accordingly.

      Please meet at the Exhibition Road entrance to the V&amp;A five minutes
      before your slot and remember to bring your Imperial College ID for entry!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1169315143225479/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Hosts Google Hash Code 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bobaBYY.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-28T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-28T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="RSM G01 ">
    <text>
      DoCSoc is hosting a hub for the Online Qualification Round of Hash Code,
      a team programming competition organized by Google.

      The Online Qualification Round takes place on **February 28th, 2019 at 17:00 UTC**
      and registered teams for **Imperial College London Hub United Kingdom**
      are invited to participate from our hub, which will take place at **RSM G01**.

      Top scoring teams from the Online Qualification Round will then be invited
      to Google’s office to compete in the Final Round of the competition in April.

      If you’re interested in joining our hub, find a team (2 to 4 people) and
      be sure you all register at g.co/hashcode. You’ll then need to select **Imperial
      College London Hub United Kingdom** from the list of hubs in the Judge System
      *after you create your team!*
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/472520253277578/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hxpP0Yp.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-09T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-10T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society and
      ICSM Coding Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2019!

      Combining your skills in bioengineering, coding, and medicine, this
      Hackathon will bring together talented students from each field and will
      be aimed at addressing current medical challenges through technology. Over
      the weekend of 9-10th March 2019, teams will bring their awesome ideas
      to life and develop solutions to real-life healthcare challenges.

      Registration and ticketing will start in the next two weeks following our
      sponsor announcements! Stay tuned and follow our event and page for our
      latest updates!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/293101718230640/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>ACI Talk - Automated Victim: Final Year Projects at Internet Scale</heading>
  <sponsor company="netcraft" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-12T12:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-12T13:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      **Abstract:** Netcraft operates an industry-leading feed of validated phishing websites,
      which is licensed by all leading web browsers to protect their users. Over
      56 million unique phishing sites have been detected and blocked by Netcraft
      to date. The scale of the problem is vast: every day Netcraft processes
      millions of suspect URLs in order to identify new threats. URLs found to be
      phishing are included in the feed, whilst harmless URLs are discarded. Prompt
      classification of each site is essential in order to protect users from new
      attacks as soon as possible. To this end, Netcraft automates its classification
      of suspected phishing sites to the fullest extent.

      The "Automated Victim" approach to classification began as a DoC final year project, and now runs in
      production at Netcraft. It automatically mimics the behaviour of a human
      interacting with a phishing site - filling form fields, scrolling, and
      uploading files - in order to perform an accurate classification.
      We demonstrate the effectiveness of this approach, whilst outlining the
      challenges of scaling up from an undergraduate project to a distributed
      production system.

      **Speaker:** Tom Szyszko is a Computer Scientist at Netcraft, where he works
      on the development of automated phishing site classification techniques.
      He graduated from Imperial College London in 2018 with an MEng in Computing.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.imperial.ac.uk/computing/industry/aci/2018-19/netcraft/">ACI Talk Details</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Schlumberger Women in Technology Day</heading>
  <sponsor company="schlumberger">
    Schlumberger are holding a **Women in Technology Day** on **Thursday 28th February**
    and **Friday 1st March**.

    ## What is this event about?

    The Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is an annual INSIGHT EVENT
    designed for future female leaders in engineering sciences.

    The fully-hosted program (see FAQs for more details) allows you to come and
    see for yourself what it's like to work at Schlumberger. In one comprehensive
    day you will get an in-depth view of the diverse career paths an engineer or
    scientist can have in our company, from oil rigs to software technology centres
    to research facilities.

    This event is a phenomenal opportunity for anyone who is looking to get a
    wider view of their career opportunities.

    ## On the schedule:

    Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is a unique chance to explore
    worldwide career opportunities and meet face-to-face with professionals you
    would not meet otherwise. The agenda will include:

    - a welcome drink and dinner on the Thursday
    - a full day at the Schlumberger Cambridge Research Centre on the Friday
    - detailed insights into the different activities and jobs offered
    - an exciting technical challenge
    - a roundtable and Q&amp;A session with International Senior Management

    Register your interest by [applying here](https://www.eiseverywhere.com/womenintechnologyuk).
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
