<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/UXACn8D.jpg"
    alt="Picture of a cup of tea with two cigarette biscuits leaning against the tea plate"
    title="Cigarettes Russes"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone! Here's yet another digest.

    We hope you enjoyed our events this past week and thank you for coming. We have many more
    industrial events planned this month, as well as our first social event of the year - the
    Welcome Bar Night!
    Read on for more information!

    To reiterate from the last digest, all of our industrial events are catered
    (usually with pizza). If you have any dietary requirements and if you are
    planning on attending an event, please make sure you [get in
    touch](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk)
    at least two days before the event to tell us. And please don't forget to **RSVP to the events
    you plan to attend by hitting Going on the Facebook event**!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Careers Service Pi-metrics &amp; Online Assessments</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-25T13:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-25T14:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      Many companies use online assessments and games as part of their recruitment process; these
      are
      often called pi-metrics or pymetrics (short for psychometrics). The formats vary but the
      underlying principles are the same. Come along to this session to find out how to prepare and
      hopefully pass them!
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    Searching for internships or placements? Check out our Sponsors Portal, where
    you can find out more details about our sponsors, read their blog posts and
    see their open internship/placement positions. You can also upload your CV
    and directly apply to all of our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk/
  </text>


  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>CV Tutorial by Nic Prettejohn, a former Computing student</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Rwq8j6I.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-21T13:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-21T14:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      CV is a great chance to make a good impression on a potential employer as it is the first
      thing they receive from you. That is why it is important to put enough time and effort into
      perfecting your resume.

      Join us at the CV Tutorial talk where you will be given tips and tricks on how to write a
      resume that reflects all your relevant skills and abilities for a software engineering
      internship/job. You will also have a chance to ask any questions from our speaker at the end
      of the event.

      The talk will be hosted by Nic Prettejohn who graduated from Imperial with a BEng in Computing
      in 2016 and was the former DoCSoc President.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1173847982809957/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Welcome Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/GMVIPh3.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-21T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-21T23:00:00+01:00"
    location="Metric">
    <text>
      It's time for DoCSoc's first bar night of the year: The Welcome Bar Night!

      Come along for free drinks and to say hi to our new freshers or catch up with friends - it's
      sure to be a night you don't want to miss out on.

      Two drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to all DoCSoc members.

      We may decide to head to Belushi's after the event; if this is the case, DoCSoc often buys
      attendees a round of drinks, so if you're unable to come to the bar night, bear in mind there
      is still a chance members will go out after!

      ----------------------

      You must be a member of DoCSoc by Friday 18th October in order to be admitted. Computing, JMC,
      and EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30. Strictly 18+ only -
      we will be checking IDs.

      Please send an email to us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk if you intend to bring a non-Imperial plus one.
      Any Imperial plus-ones must have purchased membership, otherwise they will be denied entry.

      Our full barnight policy is linked here: http://docsoc.co.uk/barnightpolicy

      Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/479850222612082/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Microsoft - Fast, Fuzzy Prefix Search</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/I2uMi6S.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-22T18:15:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-22T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      Daniel Slocombe from Microsoft will talk about People and Entity search in Outlook and
      Exchange.

      He will explain some the problems faced, and techniques used to solve, online spell correction
      and fuzzy lookup with experience from serving billions of requests a week.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/437470870210931/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Bloomberg - The Soul of the Beast</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/UCxezR3.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-24T18:15:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-24T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      What makes Python so easy to learn and read? Other languages also have a robust community and
      a compelling ecosystem and standard library, but Python somehow stands out on how easy it is
      to understand existing code and how quickly and pleasantly people can learn it. In this talk,
      we learn everything about the Python Grammar:
      - How the Python parser is automatically generated and how it works
      - How the technical details of the grammar translate into the properties of the language we
      all know and love
      - What are the limitations that prevent some grammar rules you would think are trivial from
      being implement
      - And finally, how to include new grammar rules in CPython in the form of a new operator with
      an associated protocol.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2506364892733979/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Reading Groups by Nuri Cingillioglu and Dr. Antoine Cully</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/MzuvCF9.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-28T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-28T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217">
    <text>
      We are happy to announce that the Reading Groups are back! Reading Groups are lectures/panels
      where researchers talk about their current work, aimed at final and penultimate year
      undergraduate, as well as and postgraduate students. Our main goal for organising such talks
      is to expose students to different types of research in Computer Science. Our first 2 Reading
      Groups will be by Nuri Cingillioglu and Dr. Antoine Cully.

      Reading Group by Nuri Cingillioglu 1 - 1.30pm

      Title: Computational Neuro-Symbolic Reasoning and how machines can learn elements of logical
      thinking

      Abstract: "Can machines think?" - asked Alan Turing in his 1950 seminal paper "Computing
      Machinery and Intelligence". Recent advances in deep learning are yielding great results
      across practical applications such as natural language processing, image recognition and
      reinforcement learning; however, how machines can incorporate elements of logical thought and
      learn to reason are open to research. Combining machine learning with logic-based expert
      systems in order to get the best of both worlds are becoming increasingly more popular. In
      this talk, I’ll give a brief overview of my involvement in the field of neuro-symbolic
      reasoning and discuss how the future of Artificial Thought is evolving.

      Reading Group by Dr. Antoine Cully 1.30 - 2pm

      Title: Creative Learning algorithms for Resilient Robots

      Abstract: Reinforcement learning algorithms are tightly linked with the optimisation of
      functions to find the best solution according to one or several objectives. Recently, we
      developed a new family of optimisation algorithms, named Quality-Diversity optimisation, that
      contrasts with classic algorithms. Instead of searching for a single solution,
      Quality-Diversity algorithms are searching for a large collection of both diverse and
      high-performing solutions. With this approach, robots are capable of finding creative
      solutions to overcome complicated situations, like loss of a leg. During this seminar, I will
      show several examples of applications of these algorithms.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/519302712237572/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Next Jump Application Deadline</heading>
  <sponsor company="next_jump">

    \
    Next Jump is hiring!

    Next Jump is a ‘Deliberately Developmental Organisation’, on a mission to create high-performing
    workplace cultures across the globe. People development is at the heart of everything we do, and
    we follow this simple mantra: Better Me + Better You = Better Us. Next Jumpers train and improve
    themselves at work (Better Me) and use that knowledge to help others (Better You): together we
    create a better world (Better Us).

    With offices in New York, Boston, San Francisco and London, our cutting-edge e-commerce platform
    is used by 30 million employees across Fortune 1000 companies and generates $3 billion in sales
    every year. This fuels our social movement: changing workplace culture. We run immersive
    ‘Leadership Academies’ for C-suite leaders across all industries, such as, GCHQ, RBS and JP
    Morgan Chase, to help them build adaptive learning teams. We are rapidly scaling our HR
    technology to large organisations, with the help of a $10 million contract with the US Navy.

    As our core and social businesses continue to grow exponentially, we are looking for
    individuals, who are driven and willing to learn, to join us! If you want responsibility and a
    job that will challenge you and grow you, then Next Jump’s the place for you! We offer 3, 6, and
    12-month internships to penultimate-year students, as well as full-time roles to graduates.

    The application deadline for our 2nd November Super Saturday (assessment centre) is **midnight
    this Monday 21st October.**

    Make your application here now http://nxj.me/hiring_uk_eng !
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>LSEG - Make your mark at a world-leading financial technology business</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg">
    London Stock Exchange Group (LSE.L) has a long, prestigious heritage that few organisations
    around the world can rival, dating back to 1698. We have grown to become one of the world’s
    foremost financial market infrastructure and capital markets groups, and a global leader in new
    financial technology (FinTech).

    Joining the Technology programme at London Stock Exchange Group is a chance to work with the
    essential systems and platforms that drive the world’s markets. From Artificial Intelligence, to
    Blockchain and beyond, our technologists are helping to shape the future of financial services
    technology, improving efficiencies, reducing risk and creating new business models.

    Both our graduate and internship programmes offer real responsibility from day one. This means
    the opportunity to work on critical projects with leading individuals from the world of finance
    and technology. Underpinning this is a friendly and supportive working environment where
    work-life balance is both respected and encouraged.

    If you have a STEM degree, a passion for technology and are ready for a challenge, we’ll provide
    roles that will stretch you and enable you to develop your skills and knowledge.
    Apply before **1 December 2019** to help shape the future of LSEG’s dynamic and growing global
    technology operation. We recruit on a rolling basis and encourage early application.

    **Apply at [lseg.com/graduates](https://lseg.com/graduates)**

  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Future of Blockchain Speaker and Launch Event</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/zvdcFFB.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-24T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-24T21:00:00+01:00"
    location="WeWork 10 York Road">
    <text>
      Join us for the Launch Event of our Blockchain Competition with talks from space leaders:
      Algorand, Tezos, Near, Atlas, Graph and Oasis.

      Future of Blockchain is a 3 month competition to build a project with blockchain. You can
      either enter/build a startup or answer a technical challenge. Be rewarded with over £100k
      worth of prizes and potentially receive investment for your idea.

      This event will include:

      - Talks from our partners: Algorand, Tezos, Atlas, Graph and Oasis

      - Information about the competition

      - Q/A with the partners about their companies and challenges

      - Free Pizza and beer

      If you want to enter the Future of Blockchain competition, enter via
      www.futureofblockchain.co.uk
    </text>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>