<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="Entrepreneur First Women's Office Hours"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Entrepreneur First have reached out to us with this awesome opportunity for everyone
    interested in entrepreneurship. If you're thinking of transferring your skills or background in
    academia to the world of startups, then join EF in their offices for a mentoring session,
    followed by drinks!

    Tickets can be found here: https://ef-women-openoffice.eventbrite.co.uk.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Entrepreneur First Women's Office Hours
  </heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/8YasGVe.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-11T17:45:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-11T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Entrepreneur First, Lincoln Block, The Biscuit Factory, Drummond Road, London, SE16 4DG">
    <text>
      Entrepreneur First is hosting office hours for women seeking advice on their careers or
      startup journey.

      Join us for a one-to-one mentoring session with one of our team members and a chance to grab a
      drink with other women considering taking the plunge into entrepreneurship. This will be an
      opportunity to discuss entrepreneurial ambitions and goals, get career advice and learn about
      the EF program.

      Whether you are considering moving from academia to the start-up world, you're thinking about
      quitting your day job to start your own thing or you're simply curious about the opportunity,
      if you've got ambition we want to speak to you.

      Sign up to the event and we will send you a link to book in your one-to-one session.

      ---

      About Entrepreneur First: We fund exceptional individuals to build their own companies at a
      very early stage. We were recently backed by Reid Hoffman, founder of LinkedIn, who lead a
      $12m investment in Entrepreneur First, alongside Lakestar, and the founders of Google
      DeepMind.

      Read more: https://techcrunch.com/2017/09/11/ef-greylock/
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/entrepreneur-first-womens-office-hours-tickets-83953458053">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

</email>