<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="Bank of America - Discover Technology Event 17th Oct"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">
  <text>
    Are you interested in learning more about technology operations in a financial institution as
    big as Bank of America?\
    Then make sure to sign up for Discover Technology - a great opportunity to hear first-hand from
    Bank of America's technology division!
    The event will be followed by drinks and canapés and has limited spaces available, so if you're
    interested **check the details below and RSVP
    [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/mobile-0/brand-9/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/4757-UK-London-Discover-Technology-Event/en-GB)**.

  </text>
  <hr/>


  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/MAW05of.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-17T17:20:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-17T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Received on invitation">
    <text>
      **Every day is another chance to learn.**

      Technology touches everything we do and underpins each deal we make. In fact, our mainframe
      environment is the third largest in the world. That said, we don’t believe that there is a
      tech ‘type’. You don’t need finance experience to join us and D&amp;I is at our core. Our
      Global
      Technology and Operations (GT&amp;O) division gives our business the competitive edge to solve
      business problems by delivering high quality and practical solutions. And after our training,
      you could be contributing to that.

      We know you’ll want to hear from our own Technology people. They’ll be there to demystify tech
      at an investment bank, and an interactive activity will help you test your skills. It’ll be
      followed by drinks and canapés with people from across our technology divisions. So share your
      career aspirations with them, and discover how we can help you find the career you want.

      Places are limited, so please register as soon as possible by clicking
      [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/mobile-0/brand-9/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/4757-UK-London-Discover-Technology-Event/en-GB).

      **Get Started. Apply Now at:** campus.bankofamerica.com
    </text>
  </event>
  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>