<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="UROP Bursary Scheme"
  agenda="false"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone! This is a quick email about the College UROP Bursary scheme.
    (This would normally be explained in our UROP 101 talk but we've been overwhelmed
    by IC Hack 19 and the funding deadline is earlier than usual, hence sending an email!)
    Read on if you're interested in/planning a UROP.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    You might already know that the deadline for the bursary applications is **February 13**.

    **Scheme overview**

    The Department of Computing has a norm/rule that all students should be paid
    £300 per week – the supervisor will need to cover the extra £200 per week
    from their own research funds.

    This funding is guaranteed only under certain conditions:

    - (0) students apply through the College UROP Bursary scheme (http://www.imperial.ac.uk/students/fees-and-funding/undergraduate-funding/loans-and-grants/funding-for-placements/urop/) –
    if successful that’s great, if not, DoC will cover £100 per week;
    - (1) supervisors asking for funding for 3 or more students need to talk to Paul
    Kelly,
    - (2) students should plan to spend a solid chunk of the summer on the
    UROP internship – 8 weeks or more,
    - (3) the scheme is essentially open only to Imperial students.

    **I am already talking to a supervisor. What do I do?**

    In this case your supervisor might already be aware of the deadline. If not,
    make sure they are and submit your application on time. Filling in the form
    itself should not take too long.

    **I do not yet have a supervisor. What do I do?**

    If your area/supervisor of interest are specifically in the Department of
    Computing, reach out to them ASAP and schedule a meeting to discuss UROP
    possibilities. Reach out to multiple supervisors, as rejections are common.

    **My chances to find a supervisor before the funding deadline are not looking
    good. What do I do? Does that mean I cannot do a UROP?**

    You should still try to find a supervisor and apply before the deadline.
    However, if you do not, it does not mean that you can't do a UROP. (1) Your
    supervisor might be able to fund you without the support from the college
    (relatively rare). (2) If your UROP is not in the Department of Computing
    (e.g. EEE or Maths or any other department) they might not have the same rule
    in place as DoC. So even if you miss the funding deadline, you might be able
    to do a UROP over the summer if your supervisor's department does not require
    compulsory funding. Someone has found a funded UROP in June which, although
    a huge exception, is nevertheless a possibility.

    **I have questions about UROP that need to be addressed before the deadline
    (/I just have questions about UROP).**

    Feel free to contact me ([Rachel Mekhtieva Lee](https://www.facebook.com/rakhilyamlee))
    or [email DoCSoc](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk).
  </text>

  <sign
    name="Rachel Mekhtieva Lee"
    role="DoCSoc Treasurer '18/19"
    facebook="rakhilyamlee">
  </sign>
</email>
