<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dFBKqHp.jpg"
    alt="Granola bars on a plate"
    title="Nature Valley granola bars are great until they start crumbling apart."/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Last week was informative and fun with lots of different events starting from our BAML breakfast,
    all the way to the Netcraft Bar Night!\
    For next week we have prepared just as much events, as well as two off-campus ones, so make
    sure to read on!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    Searching for internships or placements? Check out our Sponsors Portal, where
    you can find out more details about our sponsors, read their blog posts and
    see their open internship/placement positions. You can also upload your CV
    and directly apply to all of our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoC Privacy Hack Day/Workshop This Wednesday</heading>
  <text>
    The [Computational Privacy Group](https://cpg.doc.ic.ac.uk/) and [Data Science
    Institute](https://www.imperial.ac.uk/data-science/) are organising a Privacy Hackathon on 6th
    November 2019 from 5pm tom 8pm in Huxley 418.
    The goal of the hack day is to discover the public datasets that are vulnerable to
    re-identification attacks.

    There will be talks from researchers and practitioners on re-identification and privacy from
    privacy engineers and researchers, including a talk about a tool which can
    [tool](https://cpg.doc.ic.ac.uk/individual-risk/) which can re-identify individuals from as
    minimal demographic and survey data.

    Sign up here:
    https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSc5iHq6UcIW2UQ6SBAaAgOscn1NusIef78En2JeID_o--RR1w/viewform
    For questions, contact sjain@imperial.ac.uk.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Tea Point Coffee Machine Update</heading>
  <text>
    As it's been a month into the term, undoubtedly many of you have needed the support of coffee
    and what better place than the tea point coffee machine! As this is entirely funded by DoCSoc
    (we are a very generous Departmental Society) we would like to point out some instructions for
    the future.

    Please make sure to read the instructions when using the coffee machine and remember to always
    keep it clean, ideally in the condition in which you found it. Being funded by the society, the
    people who handle the machine are all volunteers (and students just like you!), so we would like
    to keep things tidy.

    We would also like to notify that we do not provide milk or other forms of sweeteners. We only
    fund the coffee beans, so we kindly remind you to use your own coffee supplements if you would
    like to.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Intenship 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/wxXSgb2.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-04T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-04T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      If you're currently looking for an internship, or simply want to know more about the
      internship process, come along to Internship 101 to find out about companies that are still
      hiring from past interns.

      Gain an exclusive honest insider opinion, learn about the types of projects interns worked on
      and the interview process to give you the best chance of getting an offer!

      This event will be held as a panel discussion with past interns from Google, Bloomberg and
      other companies. We tried to gather a diverse group of panellists who interned not only at
      banks and big tech companies but also smaller firms and startups.

      If you have any questions that you would like to be answered during the panel, please submit
      them using this form: docsoc.co.uk/internship101-questions

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/417525138959228/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DRW Tech Talk</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1zmokpn.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-05T18:15:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-05T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      DRW is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at
      our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial
      markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 26 years, so has DRW –
      maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over
      1,000 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to
      solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of
      high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration. DRW will be hosting a tech
      talk where students will hear from one of our Senior Software Developers and Traders and learn
      more about their roles within the company. Students will also be able to learn more about job
      opportunities, both full-time and internships, and discuss the hiring process with recruiters.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/812918489137660/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>An Evening with the Group COO &amp; CIO of LSEG</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/HasrUpM.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-07T18:15:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-07T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="CAGB LT 300">
    <text>
      Chris Corrado Group COO &amp; CIO invites you to join him for an evening event looking at the
      vision of Technology within FinTech. Chris was appointed Group COO and Group CIO in November
      2015. Chris was previously Managing Director at MSCI, CIO/CTO, responsible for technology,
      data services and program management from 2013. Chris has more than thirty years of global
      experience in managing technology platforms and transformational change in the financial
      services industry. Prior to joining MSCI, Chris held a variety of senior CTO roles in leading
      banks, including Morgan Stanley, Deutsche Bank, Merrill Lynch and UBS. He has also worked for
      high growth technology companies as CTO at eBay, CIO at AT&amp;T Wireless, and SVP of
      Technology,
      Strategic Initiatives and Business Architecture at Asurion, the mobile technology protection
      company. He began his career at IBM. He graduated with a B.S. in Management Information
      Systems &amp; Business Administration from the University of New York at Albany.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk
      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1179855152214016/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Postgraduate Drinks 2</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/HOejF6H.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-08T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-08T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="Eastside Bar">
    <text>
      The time has come for the second DoCSoc Postgraduate bar night!

      Come along to grab some free drinks and to chat to our sponsors: for this night we will host
      Stake Zero Ventures and EF (Entrepreneur First), who are especially interested in our
      postgraduate members (you!). As usual, two drink tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to
      all DoCSoc postgraduate members.

      Please note, that only DoCSoc postgraduate members will be admitted into the event - this
      includes MSc, MRes, and PhD students.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/779622592458039/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Reading Group by Sophia Drossopoulou</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1CtC1B4.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-12T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-12T13:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217">
    <text>
      Come and join us at our bi-weekly Reading Groups. This time we have Sophia Drossopoulou who
      will talk about her research "Holistic specifications for robust code". This talk is aimed at
      penultimate/4th year undergraduate as well as postgraduate students.

      Abstract
      Functional specifications of program components describe what the code can do — the sufficient
      conditions to invoke the component’s operations: a client who supplies arguments meeting that
      operation’s preconditions can invoke it, and obtain the associated effect. While
      specifications of sufficient conditions may be enough to reason about complete, unchanging
      programs, they cannot support reasoning about components that interact with external
      components of possibly unknown provenance. In this open world setting, ensuring that your
      component is robust even when executing with buggy or malicious external code is critical.
      Holistic specifications — as their name implies — are concerned with the overall behaviour of
      a component, in all possible interleavings of calls to the component’s operations with those
      of the external code. Thus, holistic specifications are concerned with sufficient conditions,
      i.e. what is enough to cause some effect, as well as with necessary conditions, i.e. what are
      the conditions without which an effect will not happen. By adopting holistic specification
      techniques, programmers can explicitly define what their components should not do, making it
      easier to write robust and reliable programs.

      In this work we argue for the need for such holistic specifications, propose a language
      Chainmail for writing specifications, give a formal semantics, and discuss several examples
      from the literature.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/437009023668599/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <sponsor company="lseg">

  </sponsor>

  <heading>LSEG WIN Afternoon Session: Technology and Innovation</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-06T14:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-06T16:30:00+00:00"
    location=" 10 Paternoster Row, London EC4M 7LS">
    <text>
      LSEG is at heart of the UK’s financial industry and is home to one of the oldest stock
      exchanges in the world. The Women Inspired Network harnesses’ the power and reputation of this
      renowned organisation to inspire, educate and pave the way for the next generation of
      graduates.

      This unique panel event showcases LSEG’s pivotal role within the global financial market and
      the impact of leveraging innovative technology.

      **If you would like to RSVP for this opporunity to visit the LSEG offices, please email
      docsoc@imperial.ac.uk stating your interest and giving your full name.**\
      This opportunity is limited to only 10 students, so make sure to let us know ASAP to make sure
      you reserve your spot!

      For more information, check out the event below and the PDF attached.
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>#AMEXTECH (Inter) University Challenge: Heats</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-06T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-06T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="The Prince Pub, 14 Lillie Road, West Brompton Crossing Earls Court, London, SW6 1TT">
    <text>
      Looking for a fun event to cool off from classes? Or an activity for you Mums and Dads family?

      American Express will be hosting an inter university pub quiz **on the 6th of November**. The
      challenge will be split into two rounds with the first one taking place next Wednesday at The
      Prince in West Brompton crossing Earls Court.

      7 universities for all over the country will be competing for the chance to win an ultimate
      Amex Experience from Brighton to London and send a winning team to the Grand Final in
      London.

      If you're looking to show off your trivia knowledge or just have some fun over a drink,
      **email
      scott.hardie1@aexp.com** to sign up your team of 4.

      Need help finding a team? Why not go with your Mums and Dads family or ping us a quick email
      at
      docsoc@imperial.ac.uk and we'll match you to a team.

      **This event is open to non-members.**\
      Check the attached flyer for more information!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2180570715580190/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Bank of America | GIS Summer Analyst Programmes - Camberley &amp; Chester</heading>
  <sponsor company="baml">
    Our Summer Analyst programme is designed to offer you a broad and exciting experience of work as
    a full time Technology Analyst. During the summer you will be placed within one team and have
    the opportunity to participate in real delivery of technology solutions.

    Your training and development is our top priority with extensive formal training offered at the
    start of the program in addition to on the job support, educational speaker events and
    mentorship throughout.

    As a Summer Analyst, your key tasks and responsibilities may include but are not limited to:

    - Work with the cyber forensics team to identify policy violations, compliance incidents or
    malicious acts

    - Ensuring third party vendor processes are in accordance with bank policies

    - Be involved in the infrastructure and application exception process

    - Develop and produce metrics to track remediation activities

    - Work with the cyber security defence team as the first response to cyber security incidents

    - Being part of the GIS team offers you the opportunity to be part of a world-class information
    security workforce. These teams cover all aspects of Information Security including the
    development of strategy and policy; vulnerability identification and management; monitoring,
    detecting and responding to cybersecurity incidents.

    **To apply for our GIS Summer Analyst Programme (Camberley) please click [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-5/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/1/opp/4319-EMEA-Camberley-Global-Technology-Summer-Analyst-Programme-Global-Information-Security/en-GB)**

    **To apply for our GIS Summer Analyst Programme (Chester) please click [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-5/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/1/opp/4324-EMEA-Chester-Global-Technology-Summer-Analyst-Programme-Global-Information-Security/en-GB)**

    **Application Deadline 8th November 2019**
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jump Trading Internship/Placement Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="jump_trading">
    **APPLY BY November 18, 2019 for most roles**\
    _Only a resume is needed_

    **London job vacancies**

    - FPGA Hardware/Software Engineer | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550517

    - Web Dev / UI Software Engineer | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550590

    - Tech Ops Engineer | Summer Internship - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550559

    - Production Engineer | Summer Internship - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550525


    **Bristol job vacancies**

    - FPGA Hardware/Software Engineer | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1803025

    - FPGA Hardware/Software Engineer | Full-Time / Graduate Placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1902736

    - Software Engineer (Python or C++) | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1862851

    - Software Engineer (Python or C++) | Full-Time / Graduate Placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1815371

    _Follow the links above for information regarding each opportunity. Only a resume is needed to apply!_

    ---

    **About Jump Trading**

    Jump Trading is a leading global trading firm that combines sophisticated quantitative research,
    cutting-edge technology, and an entrepreneurial culture.

    Jump has 20 years of experience investing in superior infrastructure, including custom hardware,
    software, wireless networks, and a world-class supercomputer. We leverage our proprietary
    technology to analyze massive data sets and identify trends in global markets across asset
    classes.

    Jump is privately owned and funded, fostering a culture of intellectual curiosity, learning and
    experimentation.

    With offices around the globe, Jump has more than 700 employees, many with backgrounds in
    trading, Silicon Valley tech companies and startups, top PhD programs, and research labs.
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>

</email>