<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="70"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/sDUoHX0.jpg"
    alt="Oreos"
    title="" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We have an exciting week ahead with IC Hack 19 and the committee is super-busy
    preparing for it. In the meantime, we have one on-campus event this week,
    _Internship 101_. Additionally, Facebook and Bloomberg have got in touch to
    advertise their events. For more information, read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Volunteers</heading>
  <text>
    If you didn't manage to get a ticket to IC Hack 19, you can still take part
    by volunteering on the day! It isn't easy making an event go smoothly for
    400 attendees and every volunteer counts.

    To volunteer, come along to our **Volunteers' Meeting** on **Wednesday 23rd January
    at 1pm** in Huxley 145. Be sure to also read our [DoCSoc: Operations post](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/permalink/2356588118000112/).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Internship 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/lcO7fU0.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-01-21T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-01-21T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      If you're currently looking for an internship, or simply want to know more
      about the internship process, come along to Internship 101 to find out about
      companies that are still hiring from past interns.

      Gain an exclusive honest insider opinion, learn about the types of projects
      interns worked on and the interview process to give you the best chance of
      getting an offer.

      Although it's now relatively late in the cycle, these companies offer
      interesting projects and past interns have gone on to work/intern at top
      companies including Google and Facebook so it's definitely worth coming
      along to hear more about their experiences!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1263390987169298/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Facebook Hack-a-project</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NxONDEd.png" />
  <text>
    Facebook is launching their 3rd run of Hack-a-project!

    This is a 5-week mentoring programme kicking off in February 2019, designed
    for 1st years of a three year degree and 2nd years of a fourth year degree,
    looking to apply for a Software Engineering internship with Facebook. Selected
    students will come to the Facebook office, once a week in the evening to learn
    about the whole development cycle and build a project as a team via a hackathon!

    In addition, we will be sharing tips on “how to crush your coding interview”,
    and also do a mock interview with you, where feedback will be provided to help
    you improve.

    Each session will also be catered, so come hungry (to learn and to eat!)

    **If you are interested, please sign-up by following [this](https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=https-3A__hackaproject2019.splashthat.com_&amp;d=DwMF-g&amp;c=5VD0RTtNlTh3ycd41b3MUw&amp;r=4Ht1aWc8IssynPN9692iKw&amp;m=3QnJFgqZ2ln3T1h10vEd1PXGLEETEPLoEWP_HRlZc9k&amp;s=rGe1mlmZqLK51_y0Ld3_wzqoa2xekf0TsLzs_VBIJ2E&amp;amp;e=)
    link AND send your CV to LucyKemp@fb.com with the subject headline ‘Hack-a-project – applicant 2019’.**

    **The deadline for applications is the 1st of Feb.**
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Discover Bloomberg</heading>
  <sponsor company="bloomberg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-06T15:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-06T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Bloomberg LP, 3 Queen Victoria Street, London, EC4N 4TQ"
    external="true">
    <text>
      Bloomberg Women in Technology are pleased to invite you to '**Discover Bloomberg**'
      on **6th February**.

      **Bloomberg Women in Technology (BWIT)** is an employee network focused on
      encouraging increased participation of women and other underrepresented
      groups in technology. The goal of the community is to offer a strong support
      network, encourage community members to continuously pursue technical
      advancement and leadership, helping to inspire the next generation of
      girls in STEM.

      Starting at 3pm, you will get a **tour of our fantastic office space**, gain
      insight into our Software Engineering department, and learn more about life
      at Bloomberg through **1-2-1 shadowing** with an engineer and our **panel discussion**.
      And, if this sparks your interest in a career at Bloomberg, our recruitment
      team will be on hand to talk to you about the Software Engineering positions
      available to you.

      Spaces for this event are limited. We therefore ask you to complete the
      registration form by **28th January**. Spots will be confirmed on **31st January**
      and we will then reach out to you to arrange any travel assistance that you may need.

      Please sign up via http://tinyurl.com/ydy8aaj4.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://tinyurl.com/ydy8aaj4">Sign-up</link>
    </links>
  </event>


  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time
  </sign>
</email>
