<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/v8AVmr9.jpg"
    alt="Stack of purple cookies"
    title="This is what Thanos would look like if he was a cookie."/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    The past week week was another fun week, with ice skating by the
    Natural History Museum and a mini golf session at Puttshack.

    In the coming week, we have another ice skating event, as well as bar night for your
    entertainment. Later in the week will be CGCU's Faces of Engineering - a joint diversity panel
    with speakers from Bloomberg and American Express. Also, Liquidnet have an open
    office on Monday, involving casual networking drinks open to all DoCSoc
    members, so if you're looking for a relaxed evening in the City of London,
    this would be a good opportunity to take. Read on for more information!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Conf42 - Chaos Engineering Conference - Special DoCSoc Tickets</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2020-01-23T08:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-01-24T16:30:00+00:00"
    location="1a Oxendon St, London SW1Y 4EE">
    <text>
      Learn how companies such as Netflix and PagerDuty intentionally break their systems at scale
      to build more resilient, scalable systems.
      Conf42 (https://conf42.com) is giving away heavily discounted tickets to DoCSoc members and
      Imperial College students. Conf42 will take place on 23rd January 2020 at The Comedy Store in
      Soho, with a day of talks from industry leaders in chaos engineering, followed by networking
      drinks at The Comedy Pub.
      The following special tickets are available for all Imperial College students (bring your
      friends!):
      all students can purchase a conference ticket for a heavily discounted price of £39 (standard
      price £339);
      students from underrepresented groups in technology who are unable to attend without financial
      assistance can apply for free tickets. (DoCSoc is also able to subsidise the cost of travel
      for attendees who are eligible for this category.)
      To obtain a special ticket, email docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>LGBT Leaders STEM - Careers Conference at Amazon Headquarters</heading>
  <text>
    PinkNews is the world's most-read LGBT+ publication, reaching nearly 32 million unique users
    each month. We organise a series of events called LGBT Leaders, which are now the UK's largest
    careers conferences for LGBT+ undergraduates. Through these events, we aim to encourage LGBT+
    students to meet role models, explore their career options, and feel comfortable being openly
    LGBT+ wherever they choose to work.

    This year we are launching the first **LGBT Leaders STEM**, taking place on the **15th of
    February
    2020 at Amazon headquarters** in London. We will be running a variety of workshops covering
    topics
    such as being LGBT+ in the workplace, allyship, and women in STEM. We have the [complete
    agenda](http://lgbtleaders.co.uk/lgbt-leaders-stem/agenda/)
    available to view on the LGBT Leaders website.

    The conference will feature sessions on coding, data analysis, fintech, engineering and AI, as
    well as sessions on trans allyship in tech and the role of diversity in AI. Students will hear
    from sponsors such as Amazon, LinkedIn, the Financial Times and many others.

    **Please find a link to our quick application process
    [here](http://lgbtleaders.co.uk/lgbt-leaders-stem/apply-now/).
    We look forward to seeing you there!**

    If you have any questions, do not hesitate to contact ana@pinknews.co.uk.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Create the DoC Banner Competition!</heading>
  <text>
    Take a chance in winning a £20/£10 Amazon voucher and get a better banner for our department!

    Did you know that our department uses this banner below at all its public events? It looks quite
    outdated, right? That is why we decided to partner with the department to have the competition
    of creating a better DoC banner! All you need to do is design a banner that follows all the
    requirements below and submit your design here! The winner will get a £20 Amazon voucher, while
    the runner-ups will get £10 Amazon vouchers.

    [Click here to enter the competition!](https://forms.gle/cZP52Fx97N8JdN9t6)

    Additional credit will be given to banners with photos which represent our diverse student body.
    DoCSoc is giving permission for photos on our Facebook page from our events to be used for this
    competiton. Looking for inspiration? You can find a small number of examples
    [here](https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=1-XnBsc4xeBePap9JlROgjHFGasRJY_x4).

    **The deadline: 1st December 2019**
  </text>

  <hr/>


  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Reading Groups by Prof Lomuscio and Piyawat Lertvittayakumjorn</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1AFstgC.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-25T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-25T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 140">
    <text>
      Join us at our bi-weekly reading groups where researchers come and talk about their current
      work to expose current undergraduate students to research! These talks are open to everyone!

      Session 1 by Prof Alessio Lomuscio: 6-6.30 pm

      **Title**\
      Towards verifying neural autonomous systems

      **Abstract**\
      Forthcoming autonomous and robotic systems, including autonomous vehicles, are expected to
      benefit from recent advances in machine learning. Yet, by their own nature, machine learning
      methods are known to be fragile and difficult to understand.

      How can we give safety guarantees for a system in which some of the components, whether
      perception systems or controllers, are driven by neural networks? What guarantees should these
      be? In this talk I will report some initial steps taken in our Verification of Autonomous
      Systems research group at DoC towards answering these questions.

      I will introduce the concept of a Neural Agent-Environment system, as a closed-loop system
      composed of an agent executing a feed forward or a recurrent neural network interacting with
      an environment. I will then define a number of verification problems, report their
      computational complexity and present a method for solving them. I will then move on to discuss
      the topic of verification of CNN-based perception systems. In this context, I will present a
      notion of transformational robustness and present a technique for establishing this property
      in classifiers.

      The talk will report joint work with M. Akintunde, A. Kevorchian, P. Kouvaros, L. Maganti, and
      E. Pirovano

      Session 2 by Piyawat Lertvittayakumjorn: 6.30-7 pm

      **Title**\
      Investigating and mitigating infamous weaknesses of deep natural language processing

      **Abstract**\
      In the last ten years, we have seen several (black-box) deep learning models being proposed
      and achieving state-of-the-art performance in various natural language processing (NLP) tasks.
      In spite of the promising evaluation scores based on standard metrics and benchmarks, deep
      learning has some undesirable weaknesses which hinder its adoption in real-world applications.
      These include issues of bias, consistency, and reliability. Consequently, to build user trust
      and ensure that the models are working reasonably, many researchers have proposed explanation
      methods to make deep learning models less opaque so that the users can investigate the model
      behaviours and mitigate the problems found. In this talk, I will discuss (i) some infamous
      weaknesses of advanced deep NLP models (ii) explanation methods used to understand the model
      behaviours and (iii) examples of techniques to handle or fix the detected problems.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/435177127380276/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>End Of Decade Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/WO2BJ62.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-25T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-25T23:00:00+00:00"
    location="Metric">
    <text>
      This term is coming to an end, so as the decade... It's time to relax and celebrate with your
      friends. We bring you: End Of Decade Bar Night!

      Drink tokens will be available throughout the night for FREE to all DoCSoc members.

      We may decide to head to Belushi's after the event; if this is the case, DoCSoc often buys
      attendees a round of drinks, so if you're unable to come to the bar night, bear in mind there
      is still a chance members will go out after!

      ----------------------

      You must be a member of DoCSoc by Friday 18th October in order to be admitted. Computing, JMC,
      and EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30. Strictly 18+ only -
      we will be checking IDs.

      Please send an email to us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk if you intend to bring a non-Imperial plus one.
      Any Imperial plus-ones must have purchased membership, otherwise they will be denied entry.

      Our full barnight policy is linked here: http://docsoc.co.uk/barnightpolicy
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1046701555662020/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Postgraduate Drinks 2</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/QvXD1Mg.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-26T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-26T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="Eastside Bars">
    <text>
      The time has come for the second DoCSoc Postgraduate bar night!

      Come along to grab some free drinks and to chat to our sponsors: for this night we will host
      Stake Zero Ventures and EF (Entrepreneur First), who are especially interested in our
      postgraduate members (you!). As usual, two drink tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to
      all DoCSoc postgraduate members.

      Please note, that only DoCSoc postgraduate members will be admitted into the event - this
      includes MSc, MRes, and PhD students.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/779622592458039/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Goes Ice Skating 2</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NjYZD9l.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-27T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-27T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Natural History Museum">
    <text>
      Missed out on the last skating session due to work constraints? Have no fear because have a
      Second Session fresh out the oven, or should I say, the freezer just for you!!! ⛄️

      Get out your scarf and gloves, and join us at the Natural History Museum for an ice skating
      spectacular on Wednesday 27th November.

      DoCSoc will be heavily subsidising tickets to just £4.50! We only have a limited number of
      tickets for this session, so make sure to try and get one.

      The ice skating starts at 6pm, so we will be meeting at 5:30pm at the entrance of the Ice
      Skating Rink - stay tuned for more updates about this.

      TICKETS WILL BE RELEASED ON THURSDAY (21TH NOVEMBER) AT 1PM ON EVENTBRITE. With this please go
      to the Imperial College Union Shop to purchase your ticket, you have a 2 hour window in order
      to confirm your purchase! YOU CAN ONLY BUY A UNION SHOP TICKET IF YOU HAVE AN EVENTBRITE
      PLACEHOLDER TICKET.

      We hope to see you there!

      --------------------------------------------------------------
      You must be a member of DoCSoc by Tuesday 13th November in order to be admitted. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30.

      Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/519626528617172/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Faces of Engineering</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/fZC4bYL.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-28T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-28T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="CAGB 200">
    <text>
      Faces of Engineering is CGCU's annual engineering diversity event, bringing together students,
      industry professionals, and engineers from all walks of life. Over the past few years, we have
      had the privilege of hosting companies like Google, Microsoft, and P&amp;G, among others.

      This year, we are please to announce that we have confirmed the attendance of Bloomberg,
      American Express, Qualcomm, Shell and Cisco with more companies expected to attend! Do be sure
      to come down and get a chance to meet the panellists and understand more about different types
      of engineering professions.

      This year, we are renaming the event "Faces of Engineering"; with Imperial being one of the
      world's most diverse universities, we at the CGCU are continuously striving to fully engage
      staff, students, and the community. We warmly welcome people of all cultures, languages, and
      backgrounds to this event and hope to see a wonderful turnout!

      The event will be held in CAGB200, but in the mean time do sign up to the event using the link
      below so that we can make appropriate provisions for numbers. There will be a catered
      networking session after the panel discussion too (free pizza wooo)!

      We look forward to seeing you all there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/456177365252525/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Entrepreneur First London: November Open Office</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/mwcE4ck.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-25T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-25T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="Entrepreneur First, Lincoln Building, The Biscuit Factory, Drummond Road, London,
    SE16 4DG">
    <text>
      Hear from one of Entrepreneur First's cofounders and meet the EF team on Monday 25th November
      2019

      Over drinks and snacks, we'll be having conversations about:

      + Why entrepreneurship is the career path to scale your ambition
      + What we look for in future founders
      + Applying to EF &amp; the admissions process
      + What the programme looks like in detail

      WHEN: Monday 25th November 2019 from 6.00-7.30pm
      WHERE: The Entrepreneur First Office, Block L


      We look forward to helping you found the future.

      Applications are now open **for the London April cohort**.

      You can apply at joinef.com

      ---

      About Entrepreneur First: We fund exceptional individuals to build their own companies at a
      very early stage. We were recently backed by Reid Hoffman, founder of LinkedIn, who lead a
      $12m investment in Entrepreneur First, alongside Lakestar, and the founders of Google
      DeepMind.

      Read more: https://techcrunch.com/2017/09/11/ef-greylock/
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/entrepreneur-first-london-november-open-office-tickets-80217732397">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Liquidnet Interactive Session: Graduate Recruitment; Trading &amp; AI</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/anyZi0q.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-25T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-25T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 24 Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London EC2A 2EW">
    <text>
      Join Liquidnet for pizza and prosecco followed by a talk at their offices, 24 floors up in the
      heart of the City of London. It's a great way to network and learn more about the company,
      while
      having fun!

      Check out the event information below and RSVP **for free** in
      [Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-80036171343).

      _Please note this event is 18+ only._

      ---

      Traders in financial markets perform tasks that require them to absorb large amounts of data
      in limited time and make rapid decisions. Time is money and sub-optimal performance can cost
      firms hundreds of millions of dollars a year. Liquidnet augments the human expert with a
      variety of technologies, from anomaly detection pattern recognition algorithms to natural
      language generation and visualizations.

      **Join Liquidnet Chief Data Scientist Tom Doris, PhD.** to discuss challenges in adoption and
      adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct the methods that were effective in
      overcoming the obstacles, and review similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology team, our Recruitment
      Team and Product Team once the interactive session has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-80036171343">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text> ## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jane Street - Spring Insight Programme - SPiN</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/E270kzP.png"/>
  <text>
    Spring Insight Programme (SPiN) is a new three-day programme hosted by Jane Street. Participants
    will learn about the real world ways we use math, computer science and probability concepts in
    the work we do. We’ll also provide an in-depth look at the different roles that exist within our
    firm. Participants will hear from and interact with full timers to learn how they transitioned
    from studying STEM subjects at university to a career at Jane Street. In addition, there will be
    a few social events which will provide another great opportunity to speak with Jane Street
    employees and the other students attending the event.

    Selected students will arrive in London the evening of Tuesday 14th April and will depart the
    evening of Friday 17th April. Jane Street will provide all travel to and from London,
    accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food and drinks throughout
    the event.

    **[APPLY HERE](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-spin/?utm_campaign=spin-2020)**

    **Sign-ups will close on Sunday 5th January at 11:59pm.** Selected applicants will be notified
    after the 6th January regarding your status.

    Questions? Please don't hesitate to email [work@janestreet.com](mailto:work@janestreet.com). We
    look forward to meeting you!

    ---

    Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative technology, a scientific
    approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our business, working out of offices in
    New York, London, Amsterdam and Hong Kong. Founded in 2000, Jane Street employs over 1000
    people. We are always recruiting top students and the environment at Jane Street is open,
    informal, intellectual and fun. The dress code is casual, the kitchen is stocked and discussions
    are always lively. Teaching and learning are central activities through classes, mentoring and
    discussion.
  </text>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>

</email>