<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/N5zo1QB.jpg"
    alt="A selection of very festive biscuits"
    title="A festive selection of biscuits with Christmas around the corner!"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome to the last week of term (and the last digest for a while)!

    Congratulations to everyone on completing yet another term! No doubt an exciting term
    with over 30 events ranging from sponsor events to fun off-campus activities! Thank you all for
    attending and we hope that we have made your time here more enjoyable. Of course,
    we will back next term to bring you many more events, including the upcoming IC Hack 20!

    If you're a second year, congratulations on finishing Pintos! It's time to
    have some well-deserved rest. If you're a third or fourth year with the next
    week being the final hurdle of the term, we wish you good luck with your exams!

    Now for the last time this calendar year, let's dig into the digest!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Hack 20 Organisers</heading>
  <text>
    Speaking of IC Hack, we are currently in the midst of organizing it bigger and better than ever,
    targeting more than 400 attendees.
    With help needed in Logistics, Hacker Experience, Sponsorship, Marketing
    and more, IC Hack 20 is an opportunity to go beyond the standard role of a
    volunteer and become a _core organiser_ of a major hackathon.\
    We organized a volunteer onboarding meeting earlier this term and you can find all of the
    information from it at https://docsoc.co.uk/ichack20kickoffcatchup.\
    Make sure to join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://docsoc.co.uk/volunteer) Facebook group to
    keep yourself updated and you can also learn more about organising IC Hack
    [here](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/2621692211489700/).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Pintos Glasses</heading>
  <text>
    As is tradition, all Pintos survivors will be getting a special pint glass. We will be
    organizing a collection in the upcoming week. Details will be released soon™ so stay tuned!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Conf42 - Chaos Engineering Conference - Special DoCSoc Tickets</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2020-01-23T08:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-01-24T16:30:00+00:00"
    location="1a Oxendon St, London SW1Y 4EE">
    <text>
      Learn how companies such as Netflix and PagerDuty intentionally break their systems at scale
      to build more resilient, scalable systems.
      Conf42 (https://conf42.com) is giving away heavily discounted tickets to DoCSoc members and
      Imperial College students. Conf42 will take place on 23rd January 2020 at The Comedy Store in
      Soho, with a day of talks from industry leaders in chaos engineering, followed by networking
      drinks at The Comedy Pub.
      The following special tickets are available for all Imperial College students (bring your
      friends!):
      all students can purchase a conference ticket for a **heavily discounted price of £19**
      (standard
      price £339);
      students from underrepresented groups in technology who are unable to attend without financial
      assistance can apply for free tickets. (DoCSoc is also able to subsidise the cost of travel
      for attendees who are eligible for this category.)
      To obtain a special ticket, email docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Imperial Careers Service and JobsLive Events</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/tFXEIeD.png"/>
  <text>
    Are you an undergraduate still looking for an internship over the summer? Or maybe a
    graduating student looking for employment? With internship deadlines fast approaching, you're
    not too late to start applying with the help of Imperial Careers Service!

    From CV/cover letter workshops, mock interviews, to Employer Led sessions (past events include
    events run by Airbus, HSBC, Nestle and KPMG), there is a wealth of events available on JobsLive
    to help you get started with your internship/job pursuit.

    Make sure to follow Careers Service on social media to stay updated with events announcements,
    as well as different competitions they run (for a chance to win a prize!):
    [Facebook](https://facebook.com/imperialcollegecareers)
    [Twitter](https://twitter.com/imperialcareers)
    [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/ic_careers)
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Next Jump Technology Open House
  </heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/vrZYwM7.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-12T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-12T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="91 Waterloo Road, London, SE1 8RT, United Kingdom">
    <text>
      Come and visit our new office just outside of Waterloo Station!

      Our Head of Engineering, James, will be giving a talk about the awesome tech we use to run our
      e-commerce site that annually brings in $3 billion dollars of sales.

      Fun fact: Our platform serves over half a million users at peak during Black Friday week.

      Afterwards, we'll have some time for you to meet and chat with the amazing NxJers over free
      pizza and drinks.
      Can't wait to see you there!

      [**RSVP here -- tickets
      required!**](https://www.eventbrite.com/e/next-jump-technology-open-house-tickets-84780417511)
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/next-jump-technology-open-house-tickets-84780417511">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities Internships and Graduate Positions</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    **Citadel** is a leading investor in the world’s financial markets. For over a quarter of a
    century,
    we have sought to deliver industry-leading investment returns to clients including corporate
    pensions, endowments, foundations, public institutions, and sovereign wealth funds.

    **Citadel Securities** is an award-winning global market maker that helps meet the liquidity
    needs
    of asset managers, banks, broker-dealers, hedge funds, government agencies, and public pension
    programs.

    Applications open for both internships and graduate roles for the following positions:
    - Investment &amp; Trading
    - Quantitative Strategies
    - Software Engineering

    Apply via our websites citadel.com &amp; citadelsecurities.com
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jane Street - Spring Insight Programme - SPiN</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/E270kzP.png"/>
  <text>
    Spring Insight Programme (SPiN) is a new three-day programme hosted by Jane Street. Participants
    will learn about the real world ways we use math, computer science and probability concepts in
    the work we do. We’ll also provide an in-depth look at the different roles that exist within our
    firm. Participants will hear from and interact with full timers to learn how they transitioned
    from studying STEM subjects at university to a career at Jane Street. In addition, there will be
    a few social events which will provide another great opportunity to speak with Jane Street
    employees and the other students attending the event.

    Selected students will arrive in London the evening of Tuesday 14th April and will depart the
    evening of Friday 17th April. Jane Street will provide all travel to and from London,
    accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food and drinks throughout
    the event.

    **[APPLY HERE](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-spin/?utm_campaign=spin-2020)**

    **Sign-ups will close on Sunday 5th January at 11:59pm.** Selected applicants will be notified
    after the 6th January regarding your status.

    Questions? Please don't hesitate to email [work@janestreet.com](mailto:work@janestreet.com). We
    look forward to meeting you!
  </text>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>

</email>