<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="Faces of Engineering - Tomorrow at 6pm!"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">
  <text>
    Are you interested in how engineering professionals got to the position they are in? Thinking
    about what the culture is like in big companies in industry?

    We invite you to CGCU's annual event Faces of Engineering! Come and meet representatives from
    Bloomberg, American Express, Qualcomm, Shell and Cisco, who will talk about their careers,
    diversity in the workplace and much more!

    The session will start at **6pm tomorrow in CAGB 200**. There will also be a session after the
    panel with free food and drinks.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Faces of Engineering</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/fZC4bYL.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-28T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-28T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="CAGB 200">
    <text>
      Faces of Engineering is CGCU's annual engineering diversity event, bringing together students,
      industry professionals, and engineers from all walks of life. Over the past few years, we have
      had the privilege of hosting companies like Google, Microsoft, and P&amp;G, among others.

      This year, we are please to announce that we have confirmed the attendance of Bloomberg,
      American Express, Qualcomm, Shell and Cisco with more companies expected to attend! Do be sure
      to come down and get a chance to meet the panellists and understand more about different types
      of engineering professions.

      This year, we are renaming the event "Faces of Engineering"; with Imperial being one of the
      world's most diverse universities, we at the CGCU are continuously striving to fully engage
      staff, students, and the community. We warmly welcome people of all cultures, languages, and
      backgrounds to this event and hope to see a wonderful turnout!

      The event will be held in CAGB200, but in the mean time do sign up to the event using the link
      below so that we can make appropriate provisions for numbers. There will be a catered
      networking session after the panel discussion too (free pizza wooo)!

      We look forward to seeing you all there!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/456177365252525/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>
</email>