<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="DoCSoc Postgraduate Drinks THIS FRIDAY (TOMORROW!)"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">
  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    This email is a reminder for tomorrow's Postgraduate Drinks happening in **Eastside Bar at
    7PM!**\
    Come along for a nice atmosphere and relax with some drinks (alcoholic and non-alcoholic) and
    snacks on us. This event is _free_ and open to DoCSoc postgraduate members only (Department of
    Computing students are automatically members).

    If you would like to come, please **RSVP by pressing Going on the Facebook event below** and
    check it out for more details and updates.\
    We would love to see you there!
  </text>
  <hr/>


  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/UoBjyZI.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-11T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-11T23:00:00+01:00"
    location="Eastside Bar">
    <text>
      (If you are an undergraduate, i.e., BEng/MEng Computing/JMC, unfortunately this event isn't
      for you! Otherwise, read ahead!)

      Come join us for our first ever postgraduate social and get to know each other over food and
      drinks, complimentary of DoCSoc. For this event, we have reserved a number of tables in
      Eastside Bar.

      Bar tokens will be provided, eligible for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks. A limited
      amount of canapés will be served at the start of the event.

      Please note Eastside Bar (unlike our usual bar venue, Metric) has limited space, shared with
      other bookings, and we will not be able to accommodate all postgraduates this time round! We
      will be returning to Metric for future postgraduate drinks over the academic year.
      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/551673548909850/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>
</email>