<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/zUwtCNT.jpg?1"
    alt="Stack of chocolate chip biscuits next to a glass of milk"
    title="" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Thanks to everyone who came to Games Night with G-Research and our Google
    Hash Code hub last week!

    We have a busy week ahead, with our yearly joint event with RCSU, Vive la
    Revelution, taking place on Monday. In the days which follow, we will be
    holding an Introduction to Unity workshop, inviting Palantir for a talk and
    product demo and finishing the week with DoCSoc's election hustings.

    Read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>An Introduction to Unity</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NA1HnpI.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-05T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-05T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      An introduction to Unity (the popular game engine used to make games like
      Hearthstone and Pokemon Go), how to use it, and what you can do with it.

      Open to all Imperial students, no coding experience required. Bring your
      laptops and code along!

      This session is targeted for those participating in HealthHack 19, check out:
      https://www.facebook.com/events/293101718230640/

      Please download the latest version of Unity from the official Unity website
      in advance: https://unity3d.com/
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/408088853331218/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir - An Engineer's Experience</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/z0JdTDu.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-07T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-07T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Clore Lecture Theatre">
    <text>
      Register here: http://tinyurl.com/y63g5ag9

      Come join us for an evening with Randall Dorin, one of Palantir's Forward
      Deployed Software Engineers, for a sneak peak of what it’s like to work at
      Palantir and to see first-hand a demonstration of the work Palantir has done
      with some of their biggest clients.

      Randall graduaded from University of Arizona with a degree in Electrical
      Engineering. He started his professional career working at Lockheed Martin
      Aeronautics on the JSF program and then spent a few years as a government
      contractor on various IT projects for Lockheed and NGC before joining Palantir in 2010.

      Food and drink will be provided! If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://tinyurl.com/y63g5ag9">RSVP</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1175972195912709/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc: Meet the Candidates!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Jc0jUeP.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-08T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-08T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 340">
    <text>
      After nominations close on Friday 1st March, it's time to Meet the
      Candidates!

      Join us in Huxley 340 from 1pm on Friday 8th March to meet the candidates
      running for all of the positions in DoCSoc.

      This is your chance to ask any questions you may have, and hear more about
      what each candidate is campaigning for! Candidates for DoCSoc and Dep Reps
      will all be present.

      Candidates for contested positions: We'll release more preparatory information
      on Meet The Candidates soon. For now, think about why you'd be good for the
      position, and prepare to be asked some questions from the audience!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2229853583948069/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/wfS8fVU.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-09T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-10T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society and
      ICSM Coding Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2019!

      Combining your skills in bioengineering, coding, and medicine, this
      Hackathon will bring together talented students from each field and will
      be aimed at addressing current medical challenges through technology. Over
      the weekend of 9-10th March 2019, teams will bring their awesome ideas
      to life and develop solutions to real-life healthcare challenges.

      _This is NOT an overnight hackathon. The hackspace will be closed during
      the night and the hack spread out in two days._
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/293101718230640/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://ichealthhack.org/">Website</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>What I Wish I Knew As An Imperial Student (presented by a DeepMind employee)</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/zR7cyVF.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-12T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-12T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Andrea Michi is an Imperial alumni who's spent the last 3 years working
      for Google and DeepMind. He'll be coming in to present on everything he
      would have loved to know before he started his job - a talk which has been
      very popular when presented internally at Google.

      Andrea will cover many soft topics often ignored in the tech industry:
      how to deal with rejections and failures, what you should prioritise at
      the start of your career, how to give, receive, and internalise feedback,
      how you can be a better teammate and a more efficient engineer.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/338191750124340/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir Women in Tech Scholarship</heading>
  <sponsor company="palantir">
    We launched the Palantir Women in Technology Scholarship in 2010 to celebrate
    and support women who are beginning careers in technology. We hope to encourage
    women to pursue computer science, engineering, and technical studies, and to
    become leaders in these fields.

    This year, 10 scholarship recipients will be chosen and invited to visit our
    London office for a full-day, all-expenses paid developmental workshop.
    Programming will include professional development sessions, breakouts with
    our engineers, and some fun social activities! All recipients are awarded
    grants of £5,500 to support their education.

    The scholarship is open to students who:

    -	Are active, full-time undergraduate or Master's students enrolled in an
    accredited European college/university during the academic years that the
    scholarship is awarded, i.e., you must be enrolled in both the current
    (2018-19) and upcoming (2019-20) academic years
    -	Are majoring in or plan to major in Science, Technology, Engineering or
    Math (STEM) fields
    -	Identify as women
    -	Have not been finalists in the past

    For more information, click [here](https://jobs.lever.co/palantir/2dce1c15-faca-4e91-a8aa-0c2c6a259d77) and
    see the flyer attached!
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
