<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/7J6fHf7.jpg?1"
    alt="Four yellow macaroons in a horizontal line"
    title="Here's to hoping our weather will be as bright as those macaroons over the coming weeks!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome back to your weekly digest email!

    First off, congratulations to those who have just finished with their exams!
    Although Imperial won't give us our much-deserved break just yet, we have
    lots planned over the next few weeks of term so you can relax, make the most
    out of your downtime and take your mind off exam results.

    Over the next week, we'll be hosting a Game of Thrones finale viewing (**with pizza,
    tomorrow!**), an end of exams bar night and our annual international trip (this time,
    to Prague). More events follow, including our annual End of Year Dinner (location
    to be revealed soon!). Read on for more!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Merch Update</heading>
  <text>
    If you still haven't collected your merchandise, be sure to give us an email
    at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk with your order details and preferred collection times
    and we will be in touch shortly.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>EmpireCTF - Weekly CTF Sessions</heading>
  <text>
    Hello everyone!

    **We are EmpireCTF, the Imperial CTF team, currently ranking second in the UK.**
    Capture The Flag is a type of cybersecurity competitions that covers a large
    range of topics including (but not limited to) web security, forensics,
    reverse engineering, binary exploitation, cryptography, and blockchain security.

    Last term we have organized CTF dojo sessions every Wednesday led by Aurel –
    we hope you’ve enjoyed it. This term, we are going to cover reverse engineering
    and binary exploitation. You might be familiar with reverse engineering if
    you have done the bomb lab in the architecture course before; you might also
    want to learn about binary exploitation if you are interested in how a C program
    with buffer overflow can be hacked. These are all very interesting topics and
    I hope to see you on Wednesday!

    If this piqued your interest, please join our Facebook group where we will
    announce the room and times for our weekly session:
    https://www.facebook.com/groups/2422843637940223/

    – EmpireCTF
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Global Female Leadership Conference</heading>
  <text>
    The Global Female Leadership Conference, **the largest university-led conference
    on female leadership in the world** is taking place on the 22nd of May at Oxford
    University’s Said Business School.

    The conference will focus on the experiences and insights of inspiring female
    leaders from a wide variety of sectors and the challenges they have faced whilst
    showcasing their great accomplishments. A key theme will be the discussion of
    obstacles those identifying as women face in environments where they are
    underrepresented, which can make a career progression more challenging,
    as well as the questions about how to best combine prosperous careers with
    families and personal lives.

    The organisers are very keen on having the students from this department attend
    and have offered a 50% discount on tickets - so they would cost less than £5.
    The discount code is VIPTICKET19.

    More details, including a line-up of speakers can be found on the Eventbrite
    event page: https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/global-female-leadership-conference-2019-tickets-61647939647
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Hopperx1 Women in Computing Celebration</heading>
  <text>
    [AnitaB.org](https://anitab.org/) offers an excellent opportunity for undergraduate and post-graduate
    students to attend a one-day locally organised event modeled after [Grace Hopper Celebration (GHC)](https://ghc.anitab.org/),
    the world’s largest gathering of women technologists. GHC is an immersive event
    bringing together women technologists at all levels – along with leading companies
    from industry, academia, and research – to build relationships, learn, and advance their careers.

    [Hopperx1 London](https://community.anitab.org/event/hopperx1-london/)
    is taking place on the **14th of June**, at **ETC - 155 Bishopsgate, Liverpool Street, London**.

    Scholars who attend Hopperx1 London gain access to career workshops, networking
    opportunities, and memories that will last a lifetime.

    The Hopperx1 London program includes keynote speakers such as -
    Brenda Darden-Wilkson CEO &amp; President of AnitaB.org, Mico Yuk Co-Founder/CEO
    of BI Brainz, panel discussions, as well as workshops and talks by inspiring
    women from our London WiT community, which will be split into Career, Data
    Science and AI, Emerging Technology and Open Source tracks.

    The scholarship is a £75 Hopperx1 student registration fee and will be granted
    according to eligibility (see application form) and first come first served basis.

    [AnitaB.org Hopper x 1 London Student Registration Scholarship Application Form](https://forms.gle/Q98sUDYAb66ktxGv8)

  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Watches The Game of Thrones Finale With Liquidnet</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NvvpeXV.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-05-20T18:45:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-05-20T20:30:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      No matter whether you've loved this season or hated it, join us in viewing
      and reacting to the finale of one the biggest and most popular TV shows to
      ever air, Game of Thrones! Drinks and snacks will be provided (including pizza!),
      but you'll want to bring your own tissues. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know as soon as possible by sending us an email.

      This event is kindly sponsored by Liquidnet, who currently have graduate
      positions for Quantitative Developers/Data Scientists open! For more
      information about the roles, click here: https://bit.ly/2YoxM4t and read
      more about Liquidnet below.

      "For 17 years, Liquidnet has revolutionized the way the world invests.
      Spanning 45 markets across the globe, our network connects the world’s
      biggest investors to the world’s biggest investment opportunities. We’re
      bold. We’re creative. We’re growing.

      And we’re passionate about the power of technology to change the lives of
      our customers and the world beyond.

      Liquidnet prides itself on standing at the nexus of Wall Street and Silicon
      Valley. But, with fewer than 500 employees, Liquidnet is more like a
      start-up than any dusty old bank or overgrown tech giant. It’s a culture
      where everyone has an opportunity to make a difference — and to make someone’s
      day a little brighter.

      We’re looking for people who are smart, accomplished, and one of the
      friendliest people in the room. If that describes you, we’d love to talk
      to you about working with us."
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2085636301547867/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>The Ramji-Bonardi End Of Exams Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/e5Ts9Wu.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-05-23T20:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-05-24T00:00:00+01:00"
    location="Metric">
    <text>
      Exams are soon over, so come along to celebrate (or drown your sorrows) on
      Thursday 23rd May at Metric! Kick off summer term the right way, and don't
      miss out on what's sure to be a great night.

      We're also dedicating this bar night to Inara Ramji and Alessandro Bonardi,
      the President and Vice President of DoCSoc.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to DoCSoc members. Tokens
      are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks. We have the right
      to refuse tokens to members at our discretion.

      Please note: Drinks are not allowed to be taken outside Metric and we have
      the right to stop members from doing so.

      You are entitled to bring one non-Imperial plus one. Please message/email
      DoCSoc with your plus one's name. The deadline to do this is BY 22nd May 10pm.

      Any plus ones whose name has not been provided beforehand will not be let in!

      College ID of your plus one must be shown at entry. You must stay with your
      plus one at all times and they will not be given any drinks tokens.
      Imperial plus ones must be DoCSoc members in order to attend.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/341298409836110/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Facebook Cyber Security - Decoded Summer 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NxONDEd.png" />
  <text>
     \
    Are you interested in cyber security? Join Facebook's Product Security team
    at our London offices for an evening of networking and talks about security here at Facebook.

    Facebook's London Product Security team or PSAA is part of a global team who
    are focused on discovering potential weaknesses and then crafting creative
    solutions to eliminate those weaknesses. We achieve this by doing security
    reviews, code and design reviews, building tools and automations through our
    WhiteHat program. The team is spread across three offices, Menlo Park, Seattle
    and London and works cross functionally with software development teams.
    Testing code for vulnerabilities building out longtime security tools and
    protecting against anomalies or vulnerabilities. We aim to make life hard for the bad guys!

    Our security team are focused on making Facebook a safe and secure place for
    the 2 billion people on our service to connect and share with each other.
    We're fortunate to have some of the brightest security minds at Facebook,
    and they are working around the clock to help protect people's Facebook accounts.

    **When: 12th June**\
    **Where: Facebook London Offices**

    If you are interested in attending the event, please follow this [LINK](https://facebookdecodedsummer2019.splashthat.com/) and **submit your details by the 20th May**.

    All applications will then be reviewed and decisions communicated by the 27th May.

  </text>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
