<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/rsRbmH2.jpg"
    alt="Bowl of biscuits"
    title="Homemade biscuits! "/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Another week another digest!

    We're sending off a week with some very successful and interesting industrial events from
    Microsoft and Bloomberg, as well as our Welcome Bar Night! Thank you to all who came to those
    and we hope you had fun!


    This week, we bring you more internal events (and a breakfast!) with our sponsors, so read on.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Volunteer at DoCSoc Events</heading>
  <text>
    Attended our events? Have you wondered how we make them happen under the hood?

    If you would like to be part of the organisation behind our industrial events and get to know
    sponsors or committee members, then go to docsoc.co.uk/volunteer and join the DoCSoc: Operations
    Facebook group for updates. Volunteering at events can get you recognition and experience that
    can one day earn you a spot in DoCSoc committee. If you have any queries ask us at
    docsoc@imperial.ac.uk!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Create the DoC Banner Competition!</heading>
  <text>
    Take a chance in winning a £20/£10 Amazon voucher and get a better banner for our department!

    Did you know that our department uses this banner below at all its public events? It looks quite
    outdated, right? That is why we decided to partner with the department to have the competition
    of creating a better DoC banner! All you need to do is design a banner that follows all the
    requirements below and submit your design here! The winner will get a £20 Amazon voucher, while
    the runner-ups will get £10 Amazon vouchers.

    [Click here to enter the competition!](https://forms.gle/cZP52Fx97N8JdN9t6)

    **The deadline: 1st December 2019**
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>2019 Milner Award Lecture - Towards the Genomic Footprints of Life</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-02T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-02T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="The Royal Society, London, 6-9 Carlton House Terrace, London, SW1Y 5AG"
    external="true">
    <text>
      Milner Award Lecture 2019 given by Professor Eugene Myers.

      We are about to enter an era of DNA technology where one can determine the genome sequence of
      any living animal or plant with near perfect fidelity for €1,000 or less. Already there are
      nascent projects such as the Vertebrate Genome Project (VGP) whose goal is to sequence every
      one
      of the more than 70,000 species of vertebrates currently extant on our planet. As such, this
      ability will revolutionize ecology, evolution, and conservation science and effectively mark
      the
      beginning of a new exploration of the natural world.

      The lecture will start with a brief review of the history of DNA sequencing technology and the
      computational problems involved in interpreting the data so produced. This history begins with
      Fred Sanger’s sequencing of the virus “lambda” in 1980, continues to the sequencing of the
      Human
      genome in 2000, and culminates in the present with an introduction to the transformative
      technologies alluded to above. However, the primary hurdle in this future vision is actually
      computational and the issues and potential approaches to addressing them will be discussed.
      Professor Myers will present several recent findings enabled by having the genome sequences of
      related species and conclude with a prospectus of what could be discovered in the future.

      The prize lecture will be webcast live and the video recording of the event will be available
      shortly after the event.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://royalsociety.org/science-events-and-lectures/2019/12/milner-lecture/">
        RSVP
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Huxley Breakfast! Sponsored by Bank of America Merrill Lynch</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/upFz5ba.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-28T08:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-28T10:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 341/342">
    <text>
      Get your week off to a great start with one of DoCSoc's free breakfasts - generously sponsored
      by Bank of America Merrill Lynch! Come along to Huxley 341/342 any time from 8am-10am and
      enjoy a great pre-lecture breakfast with other DoCSoc'ers and fellow MathSoc folk. So come on
      over, have a snack and meet with engineers from BAML!

      If you have any specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few days beforehand!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2784190164960020/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Reading Groups by Nuri Cingillioglu and Dr. Antoine Cully</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/rR75XiS.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-28T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-28T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217">
    <text>
      We are happy to announce that the Reading Groups are back! Reading Groups are lectures/panels
      where researchers talk about their current work, aimed at final and penultimate year
      undergraduate, as well as and postgraduate students. Our main goal for organising such talks
      is to expose students to different types of research in Computer Science. Our first 2 Reading
      Groups will be by Nuri Cingillioglu and Dr. Antoine Cully.

      Reading Group by Dr. Antoine Cully 1 - 1.30pm

      Title: Creative Learning algorithms for Resilient Robots

      Abstract: Reinforcement learning algorithms are tightly linked with the optimisation of
      functions to find the best solution according to one or several objectives. Recently, we
      developed a new family of optimisation algorithms, named Quality-Diversity optimisation, that
      contrasts with classic algorithms. Instead of searching for a single solution,
      Quality-Diversity algorithms are searching for a large collection of both diverse and
      high-performing solutions. With this approach, robots are capable of finding creative
      solutions to overcome complicated situations, like loss of a leg. During this seminar, I will
      show several examples of applications of these algorithms.

      Reading Group by Nuri Cingillioglu 1.30 - 2pm

      Title: Computational Neuro-Symbolic Reasoning and how machines can learn elements of logical
      thinking

      Abstract: "Can machines think?" - asked Alan Turing in his 1950 seminal paper "Computing
      Machinery and Intelligence". Recent advances in deep learning are yielding great results
      across practical applications such as natural language processing, image recognition and
      reinforcement learning; however, how machines can incorporate elements of logical thought and
      learn to reason are open to research. Combining machine learning with logic-based expert
      systems in order to get the best of both worlds are becoming increasingly more popular. In
      this talk, I’ll give a brief overview of my involvement in the field of neuro-symbolic
      reasoning and discuss how the future of Artificial Thought is evolving.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/519302712237572/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Palantir Decomposition Workshop</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/tIB9YOs.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-29T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-29T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      At Palantir, we solve real-world problems. A big part of this is being able to break down a
      problem you aren’t familiar with, and coming up with creative and strategic solutions. This is
      what we call decomposition. Come join our workshop to learn more about how we problem solve
      and how to ace any technical interview! We will also be showing a live demo of our software in
      action.

      We look forward to seeing you there!

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      Please fill out this link as well if you are going to the event:
      https://palantir.recsolu.com/external/events/-VpzqQIxns4qxR8yKPulxA

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/774649976321372/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Netcraft - Credit Card Skimming for Fun and Profit</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/owOcYwu.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-31T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-31T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton 060">
    <text>
      JavaScript credit card skimmers are increasingly prevalent. Criminals break into online
      shopping
      websites and insert small snippets of JavaScript which steal a copy of credit card details and
      any other credentials as they are entered, sometimes receiving them even before the legitimate
      site processes the payment.

      Strategies available to criminals include researching vulnerabilities in widely used commerce
      software, scanning across the internet to install their skimmer on all the matching shops
      worldwide and then securing the site so that other criminals are unable to do the same.
      Alternatively, criminals may try to find a vulnerability in a high traffic shop which alone
      might do as many transactions as the entire set of vulnerable installations of shopping
      platform
      such as WooCommerce or Magento.

      To illustrate the scale of the opportunity, last year a skimmer were discovered on the British
      Airways' site after it had harvested an estimated 380,000 credentials. The Information
      Commissioner’s Office subsequently fined British Airways £183 million for the breach.

      As part of the UK’s Active Cyber Defence (https://www.ncsc.gov.uk/news/annual-review-2019),
      Netcraft protects UK shoppers against JavaScript skimmers by continually searching for
      skimmers
      on shops hosted in the UK, notifying all the people in a position to influence the removal of
      the skimmer including the shop owner and hosting company. To date we have done over 2000
      successful takedowns of JavaScript skimmers on British shops. Current DocSoc members have
      contributed significantly to the development of this service.

      The Challenge

      After a tutorial on JavaScript skimming, each team is given a shopping site to operate. A
      shopping bot makes purchases from each shop throughout the event. The aim is to keep your own
      shop free of skimmers so that it makes money through the shopping bot’s purchases, whilst
      attempting to install and maintain a skimmer on as many of the other contestants shops as
      possible and steal their transactions.

      The team with the most money at the end of the event is the winner.

      To take part, bring your own laptop with a web browser and an SSH client (e.g. Putty
      http://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/putty/ for Windows users; OpenSSH for Linux/Mac
      users).

      Pizza and soft drinks will be provided during the event, followed by a Netcraft-sponsored bar
      night. This event is only for DoCSoc members. Netcraft’s previous workshops have been very
      popular, please make sure you press "Going" so we know how much food to order. If you have any
      specific dietary requirements, please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing
      docsoc@imperial.ac.uk
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/516331008913687/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Internship 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/dhv4A4V.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-04T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-04T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      If you're currently looking for an internship, or simply want to know more about the
      internship
      process, come along to Internship 101 to find out about companies that are still hiring from
      past interns.

      Gain an exclusive honest insider opinion, learn about the types of projects interns worked on
      and the interview process to give you the best chance of getting an offer!

      This event will be held as a panel discussion with past interns from Google, Bloomberg and
      other
      companies. We tried to gather a diverse group of panellists who interned not only at banks and
      big tech companies but also smaller firms and startups.

      If you have any questions that you would like to be answered during the panel, please submit
      them using this form: docsoc.co.uk/internship101-questions

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help
      us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements, please
      let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC,
      and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/417525138959228/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel - Challenge the Impossible</heading>
  <image src="https://docsoc.co.uk/img/sponsors/citadel_logo.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-31T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-10-31T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="Skempton LT 201">
    <text>
      Citadel is hosting an Information &amp; Networking session on Thursday 31st Oct at Imperial!

      If you're interested in learning more about the different roles in a leading trading firm and
      are looking to expand your career options, then come along in Lecture Theatre 201 in Skempton
      Building at 18:30 on the 31st.

      For more information check out the attached PDF.
    </text>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>

</email>