<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="London Stock Exchange Group – Grow your career at market speed "
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    London Stock Exchange Group have opened their applications for graduate and internship
    programmes in both Business and Technology roles. If you're interested in working in one of the
    most well established financial institutions, check out both positions below!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <sponsor company="lseg">
    London Stock Exchange Group (LSE.L) has a long, prestigious heritage that few organisations
    around the world can rival, dating back to 1698. We have grown to become one of the world’s
    foremost financial market infrastructure and capital markets groups, and a global leader in new
    financial technology (FinTech).

    Headquartered in London, our geographic footprint extends to more than 25 cities worldwide. As
    we continue to expand around the world, there has never been a more exciting time to join our
    business. Whether graduate or intern, you’ll have the opportunity to work on critical projects
    with leading individuals from the world of finance and technology.

    From Capital Markets to Post Trade, Information Services and Technology, the unique rotational
    nature of our programme will provide unlimited opportunities to test yourself as you take on a
    range of diverse and challenging roles. You could find yourself bringing fast-growth SME
    companies to market or guiding clients through regulatory challenges in a constantly shifting
    financial landscape.

    Whatever your background and interests, you’ll have every opportunity to develop your knowledge
    and skill set. What’s more, you’ll have the constant support of colleagues along the way.

    Apply before **1 December 2019** to take your first steps towards a varied and impactful career
    in financial markets. We recruit on a rolling basis and encourage early application.

    [lseg.com/graduates](https://lseg.com/graduates)


  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/00vj60X.jpg"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    London Stock Exchange Group (LSE.L) has a long, prestigious heritage that few organisations
    around the world can rival, dating back to 1698. We have grown to become one of the world’s
    foremost financial market infrastructure and capital markets groups, and a global leader in new
    financial technology (FinTech).

    Joining the Technology programme at London Stock Exchange Group is a chance to work with the
    essential systems and platforms that drive the world’s markets. From Artificial Intelligence, to
    Blockchain and beyond, our technologists are helping to shape the future of financial services
    technology, improving efficiencies, reducing risk and creating new business models.

    Both our graduate and internship programmes offer real responsibility from day one. This means
    the opportunity to work on critical projects with leading individuals from the world of finance
    and technology. Underpinning this is a friendly and supportive working environment where
    work-life balance is both respected and encouraged.

    If you have a STEM degree, a passion for technology and are ready for a challenge, we’ll provide
    roles that will stretch you and enable you to develop your skills and knowledge.

    Apply before **1 December 2019** to help shape the future of LSEG’s dynamic and growing global
    technology operation. We recruit on a rolling basis and encourage early application.

    [lseg.com/graduates](https://lseg.com/graduates)

  </text>

</email>