<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/T18dBBr.jpg"
    alt="Row of Leibniz biscuits"
    title="This is what happens when you let mathematicians name biscuits"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    We're saying goodbye to another busy week full of events both on- and off-campus. We hope that
    you found our sponsored industrial events by DRW and LSEG helpful and we hope you enjoyed our
    informative Internship 101 session. Also, a big thank you those who went to the AMEX pub quiz
    and the LSEG WIN afternoon session.

    For next week we have more educational events planned, as well as a Game Jam, but also a lot of
    messages for you! So without further ado, let's get right into it.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>CGCU Football League</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DPERyrD.jpg"/>
  <text>
    For those who don't know, the CGCU Football League is a currently running championship, where
    each department represented in the CGCU competes to prove their superiority in the game of
    football.

    To represent DoC, we have team Foo Bar FC with players:
    Athithan Dharmaratnam, Avish
    Vijayaraghavan, George Mitenkov, Kyle Patel, Rohan Gupta, Pranav Bansal. In their first match
    against the Chem Eng Blues, our team won with a whopping 4-1. Here's a brief match report from
    the game:

    First game of the season produced a strong start for league aspirations with a dominating win
    against the Chem Eng Blues. A solid defensive performance by Rohan and Pranav created a
    foundation for the attackers to play more freely. The final goal summed up the performance of
    Foo Bar FC with a route one goal kick to Avish, banged in with a first time volley. A clinical
    all round performance.

    We wish the players even more success in the games to come and to make DoC proud of their
    performance.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>NXP Cup Competition</heading>
  <text>
    The NXP Cup Competition is an innovational challenge for students all around Europe to build a
    self-driving DIY race robot for the chance to win big prizes such as a trip to Bucharest! In
    order to participate players need to have a basic entry
    electronics kit which comes equipped with NXP components that are used in cars on the road
    today. All you need is basic embedded software programming and circuitry knowledge – and the
    willingness to learn!

    If you're interested in participating make sure to [sign your team up
    here](https://getregisterednow.com/NXP/Cup/Registration/Register.aspx?li=87&amp;l=1), as well as
    [message us about your interest](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk) for more information surrounding
    how to get the kit. The deadline for signing up is **30th of November**.

    For more information check out the competition at their website: https://nxpcup.nxp.com/
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Create the DoC Banner Competition!</heading>
  <text>
    Take a chance in winning a £20/£10 Amazon voucher and get a better banner for our department!

    Did you know that our department uses this banner below at all its public events? It looks quite
    outdated, right? That is why we decided to partner with the department to have the competition
    of creating a better DoC banner! All you need to do is design a banner that follows all the
    requirements below and submit your design here! The winner will get a £20 Amazon voucher, while
    the runner-ups will get £10 Amazon vouchers.

    [Click here to enter the competition!](https://forms.gle/cZP52Fx97N8JdN9t6)

    **The deadline: 1st December 2019**
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Imperial Mathematics Competition</heading>
  <text>
    Challenge yourself with maths puzzles in the third edition of Imperial Mathematics Competition!
    Round One of the annual contest will take place in late November, when contestants, from
    universities across the UK, will be given 3 hours to solve 6 problems individually. The top
    performers will be invited to Round Two (the final round) in Term 2.

    Sign up [here](https://icmathscomp.org/signup/). You can have a look at [past papers
    here](https://icmathscomp.org/pages/past-papers.html).

    Students from all departments are welcomed, both undergraduate and one-year master's. Some of the
    problems on the papers may require knowledge from the first year of an undergraduate course in
    Maths, much of which is covered in science and engineering courses as well. A separate team
    competition will be run in Term 2, with details to be announced in January.

    The deadline for signing up for the individual contest is **18th of November** and the
    competition will take place on **Sunday 24th November 9:30 - 12:30** in Huxley.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Hack 20 Volunteers Onboarding Meeting</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-11T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-11T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      Our annual hackathon is coming up and we're looking for volunteers! Last year, IC Hack 19 was
      the largest student run hackathon in the UK with over 420 attendees. This year, we aim to make
      it bigger and better! Check out our
      [montage from IC Hack 19!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oy6tcQY6K6Q).

      Our kickoff meeting will take place on **Monday 11th 6-8pm in Huxley 145** and
      we're looking for people to take on the responsibilities beyond the standard volunteering
      role.
      If you want to be a part of this mammoth event, come along to find out more about the roles
      we're looking for!

      Make sure to join the [DoCSoc: Operations](https://docsoc.co.uk/volunteer) Facebook group to
      keep yourself updated and you can also learn more about organising IC Hack
      [here](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/2621692211489700/).
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Website 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DpN7m4k.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-12T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-12T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      Are you a first year Computing student? Then come join us at this event! DoCSoc presents
      “Website 101: A Basic Introduction to Web Development”! In this event, you will learn the
      basics of what a website is, how to build your own, and how to deploy it!

      This event is Part 1 of 2 DoCSoc events that will help you lay down the foundations of website
      development, and can prove to be quite useful for your future studies and the beginning of
      your professional career. We look forward to seeing you there!

      ***Important***
      This event is aimed at those people who have never had any experience with web development. If
      you are familiar with the basics, then feel free to join our next event on the 21st November
      for more advanced content.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2388381191288314/">
        Facebook
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Prototype Gamejam</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/LCS1WF3.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-16T10:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-16T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 341">
    <text>
      We are excited to announce the first Gamejam of the year, hosted in collaboration with ICU
      Game Development Society. Get ready for a day of fun game prototyping and development on
      Saturday the 16th of November.

      If you are already working on some games, feel free to come along and boost your game
      development process. For those who don't have a project yet, this is the perfect opportunity
      to get started and find something to work on for the rest of the year.

      The event will feature a Unity tutorial at the beginning to bring game development novices up
      to speed, free Pizza for lunch 🍕, a fun time making games 🕹, and prizes for the best game
      prototype made by teams of up to 4 🏆.

      Make sure to bring your laptop, so you can work on your game during the event!

      We will be releasing the tickets for the event **on Eventbrite on Tuesday 1:00pm.** The
      tickets
      are free, but you have to have a valid one in order to attend as places are limited!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/430635647644613/">
        Facebook
      </link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/docsoc-prototype-gamejam-tickets-81095574045">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>RESCHEDULED: Reading Group by Sophia Drossopoulou</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1CtC1B4.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-19T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-19T13:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217">
    <text>
      **Please note this event has been rescheduled to the 19th of November. We apologize for the
      inconvenience.**

      Come and join us at our bi-weekly Reading Groups. This time we have Sophia Drossopoulou who
      will talk about her research "Holistic specifications for robust code". This talk is aimed at
      penultimate/4th year undergraduate as well as postgraduate students.

      Abstract
      Functional specifications of program components describe what the code can do — the sufficient
      conditions to invoke the component’s operations: a client who supplies arguments meeting that
      operation’s preconditions can invoke it, and obtain the associated effect. While
      specifications of sufficient conditions may be enough to reason about complete, unchanging
      programs, they cannot support reasoning about components that interact with external
      components of possibly unknown provenance. In this open world setting, ensuring that your
      component is robust even when executing with buggy or malicious external code is critical.
      Holistic specifications — as their name implies — are concerned with the overall behaviour of
      a component, in all possible interleavings of calls to the component’s operations with those
      of the external code. Thus, holistic specifications are concerned with sufficient conditions,
      i.e. what is enough to cause some effect, as well as with necessary conditions, i.e. what are
      the conditions without which an effect will not happen. By adopting holistic specification
      techniques, programmers can explicitly define what their components should not do, making it
      easier to write robust and reliable programs.

      In this work we argue for the need for such holistic specifications, propose a language
      Chainmail for writing specifications, give a formal semantics, and discuss several examples
      from the literature.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/437009023668599/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Ed Tech Hackday</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/D0rw30s.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-23T11:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-23T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 342">
    <text>
      Join DoC on Saturday 23rd for a one day Hackathon to learn how your education tools
      (Materials, eMarking and more) are made.

      Please RSVP here: https://forms.gle/foZwZKEN6XVrNVr68

      Learn how real webapps work, chalenge yourselves to contibute to these open sourse projects
      with new and amazing ideas, and win the prize for the best contribution, OR show us your web
      apps knowledge by creating a whole new webapp that will help the EdTech ecosystem!

      Lunch will be provided on the day, so let us know if you plan to attend by sellecting "going"
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/494024571188237/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdQaMWltx44IvT1WfalwPYN-u5oFRRiI9u5Q70IuuHrjftGSQ/viewform">
        RSVP
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Liquidnet Interactive Session: Graduate Recruitment; Trading &amp; AI</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/anyZi0q.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-25T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-25T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 24 Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London EC2A 2EW">
    <text>
      Join Liquidnet for pizza and prosecco followed by a talk at their offices, 24 floors up in the
      heart of the City of London. It's a great way to network and learn more about the company,
      while
      having fun!

      Check out the event information below and RSVP **for free** in
      [Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-80036171343).

      _Please note this event is 18+ only._

      ---

      Traders in financial markets perform tasks that require them to absorb large amounts of data
      in limited time and make rapid decisions. Time is money and sub-optimal performance can cost
      firms hundreds of millions of dollars a year. Liquidnet augments the human expert with a
      variety of technologies, from anomaly detection pattern recognition algorithms to natural
      language generation and visualizations.

      **Join Liquidnet Chief Data Scientist Tom Doris, PhD.** to discuss challenges in adoption and
      adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct the methods that were effective in
      overcoming the obstacles, and review similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology team, our Recruitment
      Team and Product Team once the interactive session has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-80036171343">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities Internships and Graduate Positions</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    **Citadel** is a leading investor in the world’s financial markets. For over a quarter of a
    century,
    we have sought to deliver industry-leading investment returns to clients including corporate
    pensions, endowments, foundations, public institutions, and sovereign wealth funds.

    **Citadel Securities** is an award-winning global market maker that helps meet the liquidity
    needs
    of asset managers, banks, broker-dealers, hedge funds, government agencies, and public pension
    programs.

    Applications open for both internships and graduate roles for the following positions:
    - Investment &amp; Trading
    - Quantitative Strategies
    - Software Engineering

    Apply via our websites citadel.com &amp; citadelsecurities.com

    _For more information check out the attached PDF._

  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jane Street - Spring Insight Programme - SPiN</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/E270kzP.png"/>
  <text>
    Spring Insight Programme (SPiN) is a new three-day programme hosted by Jane Street. Participants
    will learn about the real world ways we use math, computer science and probability concepts in
    the work we do. We’ll also provide an in-depth look at the different roles that exist within our
    firm. Participants will hear from and interact with full timers to learn how they transitioned
    from studying STEM subjects at university to a career at Jane Street. In addition, there will be
    a few social events which will provide another great opportunity to speak with Jane Street
    employees and the other students attending the event.

    Selected students will arrive in London the evening of Tuesday 14th April and will depart the
    evening of Friday 17th April. Jane Street will provide all travel to and from London,
    accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food and drinks throughout
    the event.

    **[APPLY HERE](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-spin/?utm_campaign=spin-2020)**

    **Sign-ups will close on Sunday 5th January at 11:59pm.** Selected applicants will be notified
    after the 6th January regarding your status.

    Questions? Please don't hesitate to email [work@janestreet.com](mailto:work@janestreet.com). We
    look forward to meeting you!

    ---

    Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative technology, a scientific
    approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our business, working out of offices in
    New York, London, Amsterdam and Hong Kong. Founded in 2000, Jane Street employs over 1000
    people. We are always recruiting top students and the environment at Jane Street is open,
    informal, intellectual and fun. The dress code is casual, the kitchen is stocked and discussions
    are always lively. Teaching and learning are central activities through classes, mentoring and
    discussion.

  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>LSEG Graduate Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg">
    This is the link to the technology graduate webpage
    https://www.lseg.com/careers/graduate-and-internship-programmes/graduate-opportunities/technology-graduate-programme

    Here is our brochure:
    https://www.lseg.com/sites/default/files/content/documents/FINAL%20LSEG_GRADUATE_BROCHURE_2019%20condensed.pdf
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Macquarie - Interview with Florence Marshall, Intern</heading>
  <sponsor company="macquarie">
    If you are interested in applying and working at Macquarie Group, please find attached an
    interview with Florence Marshall, a summer intern.

    You can learn more about the culture and a typical work day at Macquarie, as well as first-hand
    insights on the application and interview process.
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>