<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/S8dPKIl.jpg"
    alt="Snickerdoodle"
    title="Snickerdoodles are crunchy on the outside and chewy on the inside!"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Just to give a brief recap of the past week: we held Mums and Dads lunch for freshers to meet
    their new college families, an informative Intro to Linux talk and a relaxing games night with
    Next Jump.

    We also held our annual Sponsors' Exhibition, which was a massive success with over 500
    attendees. It was wonderful to see the Great Hall - one of the biggest halls in Imperial, full
    with enthusiastic students together next to our amazing sponsors! If you have any feedback,
    regarding the exhibition, please contact us at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.

    In the upcoming week, we are continuing with our sponsor events, holding three big industrial
    events, which will be catered with food and drinks. Please make sure to **RSVP to all events
    that you will be attending by pressing Going on their Facebook events.** That way we can ensure
    that there is enough food and drinks for everyone. For dietary requirements, please [contact us](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk)
    as soon as possible, specifying the event that you will be attending and your dietary
    requirement.

    This week's digest is full with a lot of useful information, so without further ado, let's get
    to it!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Autumn Elections - Nominations Close Tomorrow!</heading>
  <text>
    Nominations in the Union Autumn elections close at
    **Noon tomorrow, Monday 14 October**!
    This is an opportunity to make your voice heard within the College and the Union.

    Students in every year group vote for an Academic Year Representative and Wellbeing Year
    Representative.

    Year reps make **real change within the department**, with a place on regular Staff
    Student Committee meetings, voicing their concerns to teaching fellows and staff.

    To nominate yourself and for more information on the mentioned and other roles available,
    visit the Union's [Autumn Elections
    page](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/autumn-elections-2019).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Internship 101 - Panelists Wanted!</heading>
  <text>
    **Did an internship this summer? Want to share your experience?**

    DoCSoc will be holding an event - Internship 101, a panel-based discussion where you will be
    asked about your internship experience. This event will be on the 4th November at 6 pm and will
    be catered. If you are interested in being a panelist, please fill out this form and we will
    send you an email with more details!

    **[Click here if you're interested in being a
    panelist!](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdScW9hQtg67Dzk6MTjT3BFNm06Qjh3omgY-SV4-F6ai0lPAQ/viewform)**
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc: Operations - Your Chance to Help!</heading>
  <text>
    We are kicking off next week with a wowing **three events** from our wonderful sponsors (more
    details below).
    All of our talks and events will be catered with _free_ pizza and drinks for all of our members.
    If you want to lend a helping hand or are just interested in the magic of organizing such events
    then check out [DoCSoc: Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/) - our
    Facebook group for volunteers, where we will post all things events. Our events wouldn't be
    possible without the help of our amazing volunteers and it is also a great chance to meet both
    committee members and sponsor representatives!

    If you're interested, join the Facebook group and make sure to keep yourself updated for when we
    post there!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Coding Challenge with G-Research</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/XJYbgf7.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2018-10-14T18:15:00+01:00"
    endDate="2018-10-14T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060 A/B/C">
    <text>
      Calling all software engineering enthusiasts that enjoy a bit of healthy competition!

      G-Research is a leading quantitative research and technology company. By using the latest
      scientific techniques, we produce world-beating predictive research and build advanced
      technology to analyse the world’s data.

      Join us for the G-Research Coding Challenge where you will compete in teams in a series of
      progressively difficult challenges. You will be competing in teams of 2-3 to build a natural
      language calculation engine (no prior NLP experience required). The challenges will cover
      things like evaluation of arithmetic expressions to unit conversions and equation solving.

      We can allocate teams when you arrive, you don't need to find a team beforehand - but feel
      free to bring your own team if you would like. To take part, you will need to bring at least
      one laptop per team. **If you can, please install an IDE ahead of time.**

      There will be a live leader board up on the projector to give all teams the opportunity to see
      where they are placing throughout the challenge. 1st, 2nd and 3rd place (decided by a point
      system) will win prizes!

      Following the event we will provide drinks and canapés and a chance for you to informally talk
      with our employees about internships, graduate roles and life at G-Research.

      Languages for the challenges - .NET Core 2 , Java and Maven or Python 3 with client starter
      kits provided when you login.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please RSVP to help us
      gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements, please
      let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/909394122791273/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>An Evening with Macquarie - Talk, Interview Prep and Networking!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/cgo87A8.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-15T18:15:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-15T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Skempton 060 A/B/C">
    <text>
      **Our first event of the year for people looking to find out how to prepare for internship
      interviews** and see what life is working in a financial services company.

      ---

      At Macquarie, we look for innovative, driven and talented students who share our drive for
      excellence. People who drive their own success, are high calibre, motivated and creative.

      Is this you? Then come to our event to find out more about Macquarie and the role of
      technology in the financial sector, including some of the exciting projects we are working on
      in this space.

      An interactive session will help you experience some of the ways in which we interview
      candidates for our technical interviews, and we will have plenty of time for you to chat to
      our graduates over pizza and soft drinks where you can ask them any questions you might have.

      We look forward to meeting you!


      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please RSVP to help us
      gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements, please
      let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk


    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2362712984057093/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Intro to Vim</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qXXUcz7.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-17T13:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-17T14:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      Different tools and technologies have come and gone across the past few decades, but even
      after 30 years since its release, this popular text editor is still favoured by many
      programmers in the industry.

      Come and join us at the Intro to Vim talk where we will introduce the basic building blocks of
      Vim and what makes it so productive. We will also show you some very powerful commands that
      may make you throw your old text editor away!

      Whether you want to actually switch to Vim, or you're just a little curious about it, do come
      along and bring friends!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/678948305931648/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Facebook - React: A Tree of Functions</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/jMdYslO.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-17T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-17T20:00:00+01:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      Hi there!
      Facebook are holding a Tech Talk with Imperial DoCSoc called React: A Tree of Functions.

      What’s it about?
      From the roots of server rendered web, to the most modern of React APIs, we can express the UI
      problem as a problem of tree generation and manipulation. This allow us to reevaluate UI not
      in term of its visual elements, but instead as a general computer science problem for which a
      wide range of solutions is available. We will dive into the concept of UI as a tree and how
      React allows us to build rich applications within this tree abstraction.\
      **Make sure to RSVP using the sign-up link: https://imperialtechtalk.splashthat.com/**

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please RSVP to help us
      gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements, please
      let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30
      at docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/453913321886476/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>CV Tutorial by Nic Prettejohn, a former Computing student</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Rwq8j6I.jpg"/>
  <event
  startDate="2019-10-21T13:00:00+01:00"
  endDate="2019-10-21T14:00:00+01:00"
  location="Huxley 145">
  <text>
    CV is a great chance to make a good impression on a potential employer as it is the first thing
    they receive from you. That is why it is important to put enough time and effort into perfecting
    your resume.

    Join us at the CV Tutorial talk where you will be given tips and tricks on how to write a resume
    that reflects all your relevant skills and abilities for a software engineering internship/job.
    You will also have a chance to ask any questions from our speaker at the end of the event.

    The talk will be hosted by Nic Prettejohn who graduated from Imperial with a BEng in Computing
    in 2016 and was the former DoCSoc President.
  </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1173847982809957/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
</event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Welcome Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/GMVIPh3.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-10-21T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-10-21T23:00:00+01:00"
    location="Metric">
    <text>
      It's time for DoCSoc's first bar night of the year: The Welcome Bar Night!

      Come along for free drinks and to say hi to our new freshers or catch up
      with friends - it's sure to be a night you don't want to miss out on.

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for **FREE** to all DoCSoc members.

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30
      at docsoc.co.uk/join. Non-Imperial plus ones are allowed entry only after notifying
      docsoc@imperial.ac.uk in advance.


    </text>

  </event>

  <hr/>


  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Facebook Industrial Placement Application Deadline</heading>
  <sponsor company="facebook">
    For all students in their penultimate year, interested in an industrial placement, please note
    there is a new deadline for applications on the **25th of October** – please apply via the
    following link: https://www.facebook.com/careers/jobs/702665046848694/

    For all penultimate year student’s applying for the 12 week internship the deadline is rolling
    but we would recommend getting your CV in by mid-November at the latest. The same application
    link applies.
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>StarLeaf Student and Graduate Roles Now Live!</heading>
  <sponsor company="starleaf">
    StarLeaf have now launched their new [Careers Hub](https://jobs.starleaf.com/) and their 2020 student and graduate roles.

    **Graduate roles**\
    So, you are in your final year at Uni and you find yourself here, looking for a job that you
    will start nearly a year away! Well, we salute you. The last thing you need during your exams
    next year is to have interviews to worry about, even worse, countless calls from recruiters
    telling you about an “exciting new opportunity.”

    We are not hanging about either. We are interviewing people right now to start with us in 2020.
    It’s a win win, we get to hire the smartest people and you get to secure yourself an awesome job
    and sit back and relax over the festive break.

    Check out our opportunities and get in touch with us now to find out some more and ask any
    questions you may have.

    **Intern roles**\
    StarLeaf are currently looking for 2020 Interns to join our software engineering teams. They
    will be attending a lot of careers fairs between now and the end of the year, so please do pop
    by and say hello.

    https://www.starleaf.com/careers/students-and-graduates/ - Showcase of Life at StarLeaf as a
    student or graduate and hear from the Humans of StarLeaf.

    **Opportunities**

    [Product Team Graduate](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/580CF18AC2-product-team-graduate/) – Watford\
    [Graduate Cloud Ops Engineer](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/5788C13092-graduate-cloud-operations-engineer/) - Watford\
    [Graduate Software Engineer 2020 intake](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/42D5BFD4BA-graduate-software-engineer-2020-intake/) – Watford\
    [Software Engineer Intern 2020 intake](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/90395F60A1-software-engineer-intern-2020-intake/) - Watford\
    [Graduate Software Engineer 2020 intake](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/8B350E9DB8-graduate-software-engineer-2020-intake/) – Cambridge\
    [Software Engineer Intern 2020 intake](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/696FB8624B-software-engineer-intern-2020-intake/) - Cambridge\
    [Graduate Solutions Consultant](https://www.starleaf.com/careers/jobs/job/9C0B8D382D-graduate-solutions-consultant/) – London
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jump Trading Internship/Placement Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="jump_trading">
    **APPLY BY November 18, 2019 for most roles**\
    **London Software Engineer role has earlier deadline of October 25, 2019**\
    _Only a resume is needed_

    **London job vacancies**

    - Software Engineer (Python or C++) | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550596
    **October 25 deadline**

    - FPGA Hardware/Software Engineer | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550517

    - Web Dev / UI Software Engineer | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550590

    - Tech Ops Engineer | Summer Internship - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550559

    - Production Engineer | Summer Internship - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1550525


    **Bristol job vacancies**

    - FPGA Hardware/Software Engineer | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1803025

    - FPGA Hardware/Software Engineer | Full-Time / Graduate Placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1902736

    - Software Engineer (Python or C++) | Summer Internship / 6 month placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1862851

    - Software Engineer (Python or C++) | Full-Time / Graduate Placement - https://www.jumptrading.com/apply.html?gh_jid=1815371

    _Follow the links above for information regarding each opportunity. Only a resume is needed to apply!_

    ---

    **About Jump Trading**

    Jump Trading is a leading global trading firm that combines sophisticated quantitative research,
    cutting-edge technology, and an entrepreneurial culture.

    Jump has 20 years of experience investing in superior infrastructure, including custom hardware,
    software, wireless networks, and a world-class supercomputer. We leverage our proprietary
    technology to analyze massive data sets and identify trends in global markets across asset
    classes.

    Jump is privately owned and funded, fostering a culture of intellectual curiosity, learning and
    experimentation.

    With offices around the globe, Jump has more than 700 employees, many with backgrounds in
    trading, Silicon Valley tech companies and startups, top PhD programs, and research labs.
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Macquarie Internship Programme</heading>
  <sponsor company="macquarie">
    As an intern at Macquarie, you’ll sit side-by-side with business leaders and have the
    opportunity to work on live projects and transactions from day one. After an in-depth
    induction, you’ll gain valuable experience and insight into your chosen business area working
    closely with the team on live deals and transactions. This valuable experience will provide
    unique insights into both Macquarie and the broader financial services industry and can set
    you up for a successful career once you have completed your studies

    Our internship programmes offer an opportunity to be a part of a talented, global team.
    Instinctively entrepreneurial. Ambitious in nature. Determined to succeed. As an intern at
    Macquarie, you’ll sit side-by-side with business leaders and have the opportunity to work on
    projects and transactions from day one.

    Macquarie is a diversified financial group providing clients with asset management and
    finance, banking, advisory and risk and capital solutions across debt, equity and commodities.
    Our global operations include offices in the world’s major financial centres. Founded in 1969,
    Macquarie operates in 30 markets, employs more than 15,715 people and has a total of £305.8
    billion assets under management (as at 31 March 2019).

    For more information about our internship programmes, visit our
    [careers page](https://www.macquarie.com/uk/about/careers/emea/graduate-and-interns).
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
