<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="70"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/SNgkxyi.jpg"
    alt="Chocolate chip cookies with hot chocolate"
    title="It's cold outside, so wrap up and stay warm!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    With a hugely successful IC Hack 19 over, we'll now be busy working on our
    next events, including HealthHack 2019 and Revel (we can't tell you more
    about that just yet...)! Over the next few weeks, we'll be also be running
    our annual Python workshops, as well as our Google Hash Code Hub.
    Read on for more details!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Videos</heading>
  <text>
    For those of you who couldn't make it to IC Hack 19 (as well as those who did!),
    be sure to check out the [**montage video**](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oy6tcQY6K6Q) of
    the event, and if you have the time, check out the [**Opening Ceremony**](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VsOa8KYeWpo)
    and [**Closing Ceremony**](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=piaTBgY5EUc) streams.

    We've taken plenty of photos over the hackathon, which will be released soon!

    (P.S: if you did attend the event, don't forget to fill out the **feedback form**
    we sent in Saturday's _Thank You_ email!)
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Careers Service: Friday Lunchtime DoC Careers Talks</heading>
  <text>
    Careers Service have got in touch to advertise Friday Lunchtime careers talks
    as follows.

    Every Friday 13:00 – 13:50 in Huxley 311 – these events will appear in
    timetables and the content is very similar to the season run through the
    Autumn Term. Sessions will not run in summer term so this is the last chance
    to access this content for the 2018/19 academic year.

    - 08 February 2019 - 13:00 - 13:50 - Application Forms - How To Ace Them
    - 15 February 2019 - 13:00 - 13:50 - Finding Internships, Insight Weeks, Projects and Vacation Opportunities
    - 22 February 2019 - 13:00 - 13:50 - Psychometric Tests &amp; Assessment Centres
    - 01 March 2019 - 13:00 - 13:50 - Interviews – The Guide To Success
    - 08 March 2019 - 13:00 - 13:50	- Postgraduate Study – Options &amp; Applications
    - 15 March 2019	- 13:00 - 13:50	- LinkedIn – Leverage The Power Of Social Media

    For more information, including event descriptions, please see the **attached PDF**
    for more details.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Coding 101 | Python for Beginners</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/XK6R3IZ.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-04T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-04T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="SAF G34">
    <text>
      _(This event is aimed at non-DoC members. Please share this with any of your
      friends who might be interested!)_

      Want to know how to code but have no idea where to start? Tried to learn on
      your own but not really made any progress? Whether you've dabbled in programming before,
      or you barely know what a computer is, DoCSoc (Department of Computing Society)
      is once again running a course for you!

      After our highly successful (and award-winning!) series last year, we'll be
      repeating our beginners coding course starting Monday, 4th Feb.

      This year the course isn't just open to people from Biology / Biochem, but
      anyone at all who wants to come along! Check out the Facebook event description
      for more information.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2080323318702227/?event_time_id=2080652732002619">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Coding 102 | Intermediate Python</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DHNRpcW.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-07T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-07T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="TBA">
    <text>
      _(This event is aimed at non-DoC members. Please share this with any of your
      friends who might be interested!)_

      For those of you who have dabbled a little bit in programming before (Python
      or not) and want to learn more, DoCSoc is holding a free, 6-week course on intermediate Python!

      We expect you to know the basics of programming already - functions,
      conditionals, loops, basic data structures and types, etc, either from
      Python or other languages.

      We will cover a range of topics, such as object-oriented programming, good
      software engineering design, as well as applications of Python in statistics,
      sciences, machine learning/data science, and building web applications.

      The course will focus on enabling you to understand the underlying logic and
      thinking process of programming, in order for you to become self-sufficient
      in your own learning and future development.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2374077755936130/?event_time_id=2374077772602795">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Hosts Google Hash Code 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bobaBYY.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-28T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-28T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="RSM G01 ">
    <text>
      DoCSoc is hosting a hub for the Online Qualification Round of Hash Code,
      a team programming competition organized by Google.

      The Online Qualification Round takes place on **February 28th, 2019 at 17:00 UTC**
      and registered teams for **Imperial College London Hub United Kingdom**
      are invited to participate from our hub, which will take place at **RSM G01**.

      Top scoring teams from the Online Qualification Round will then be invited
      to Google’s office to compete in the Final Round of the competition in April.

      If you’re interested in joining our hub, find a team (2 to 4 people) and
      be sure you all register at g.co/hashcode. You’ll then need to select **Imperial
      College London Hub United Kingdom** from the list of hubs in the Judge System
      *after you create your team!*
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/472520253277578/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hxpP0Yp.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-02T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-03T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society and
      ICSM Coding Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2019!

      Combining your skills in bioengineering, coding, and medicine, this
      Hackathon will bring together talented students from each field and will
      be aimed at addressing current medical challenges through technology. Over
      the weekend of 2nd - 3rd March 2019, teams will bring their awesome ideas
      to life and develop solutions to real-life healthcare challenges.

      Registration and ticketing will start in the next two weeks following our
      sponsor announcements! Stay tuned and follow our event and page for our
      latest updates!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/293101718230640/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Schlumberger Women in Technology Day</heading>
  <sponsor company="schlumberger">
    Schlumberger are holding a **Women in Technology Day** on **Thursday 28th February**
    and **Friday 1st March**.

    ## What is this event about?

    The Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is an annual INSIGHT EVENT
    designed for future female leaders in engineering sciences.

    The fully-hosted program (see FAQs for more details) allows you to come and
    see for yourself what it's like to work at Schlumberger. In one comprehensive
    day you will get an in-depth view of the diverse career paths an engineer or
    scientist can have in our company, from oil rigs to software technology centres
    to research facilities.

    This event is a phenomenal opportunity for anyone who is looking to get a
    wider view of their career opportunities.

    ## On the schedule:

    Schlumberger Women in Technology Day - UK 2019 is a unique chance to explore
    worldwide career opportunities and meet face-to-face with professionals you
    would not meet otherwise. The agenda will include:

    - a welcome drink and dinner on the Thursday
    - a full day at the Schlumberger Cambridge Research Centre on the Friday
    - detailed insights into the different activities and jobs offered
    - an exciting technical challenge
    - a roundtable and Q&amp;A session with International Senior Management

    Register your interest by [applying here](https://www.eiseverywhere.com/womenintechnologyuk).
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time
  </sign>
</email>
