<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/10yQfIX.jpg"
    alt="Chocolate chip cookies"
    title="I was going to put snowman cookies but it didn't snow enough at all :(" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    As IC Hack 19 approaches its final hours, we want to firstly thank all of our
    organisers and volunteers for making IC Hack 19 possible. We will have a live stream
    of the closing ceremony taking place today, with more details below.

    Next week will be relatively quiet as we recover from the hackathon. However, we
    have a few opportunities from sponsors (both held in their offices!),
    introductions to DoCSoc CTF and Google Hash Code 2019!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Closing Ceremony</heading>
  <text>
    As IC Hack comes to a close, you can tune into a livestream of the **closing ceremony
    from 3pm today**. Stay tuned on our social media channels for the YouTube link!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc CTF</heading>
  <text>
    We run weekly sessions of "CTF dojos" every Wednesday afternoon (15:00 – 17:00).
    During our sessions we cover various cybersecurity related topics, including
    network and web security. We often participate in (rather challenging) CTFs
    during the weekend, which provide interesting challenges to dissect during
    the dojos as well.

    If you have never heard of Capture The Flag (CTF) competitions, they are e
    ssentially challenges which require you to develop exploits or take advantage
    of vulnerabilities based on black-box analysis, source code analysis, forensic
    analysis, etc. These skills are very useful for your career and for courses like 331 Network and Web Security.

    Here is a video introduction by a popular CTF channel: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ev9ZX9J45A

    If you are interested, please join our FB group, [DoCSoc CTF](https://www.facebook.com/groups/2422843637940223/).
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Hosts Google Hash Code 2019</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bobaBYY.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-28T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-28T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="RSM G01 ">
    <text>
      We’ll be hosting a hub at Imperial College London for the Online Qualification
      Round of Hash Code, a team programming competition organized by Google.

      The Online Qualification Round takes place on February 28th, 2019 at 17:30
      UTC, and registered teams from are invited to participate from our hub, which
      will take place at Imperial College London RSM G01. Top scoring teams from
      the Online Qualification Round will then be invited to Google’s office to
      compete in the Final Round of the competition in April.

      If you’re interested in joining our hub, find a team (2 to 4 people) and
      be sure you all register at https://g.co/hashcode. You'll then need to select Imperial
      College London Hub United Kingdom from the list of hubs in the Judge System.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/472520253277578/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Facebook Hack-a-project</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NxONDEd.png" />
  <text>
    This is just a gentle reminder that we are **closing applications** for our 3rd run of **Hack-a-project on Feb 1st 2019**.

    This is a 5-week mentoring programme kicking off in February 2019, designed
    for 1st years of a three year degree and 2nd years of a fourth year degree,
    looking to apply for a Software Engineering internship with Facebook. Selected
    students will come to the Facebook office, once a week in the evening to learn
    about the whole development cycle and build a project as a team via a hackathon!

    Each session will also be catered, so come hungry (to learn and to eat!)

    Please take a look at the video from our last Hack-a-project to find out more https://www.facebook.com/265781023507354/posts/2024153967670042/.

    **If you are interested, please sign-up by following [this](https://hackaproject2019.splashthat.com/)
    link AND send your CV to LucyKemp@fb.com with the subject headline ‘Hack-a-project – applicant 2019’.**
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Discover Bloomberg</heading>
  <sponsor company="bloomberg" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-06T15:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-06T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Bloomberg LP, 3 Queen Victoria Street, London, EC4N 4TQ"
    external="true">
    <text>
      Bloomberg Women in Technology are pleased to invite you to '**Discover Bloomberg**'
      on **6th February**.

      **Bloomberg Women in Technology (BWIT)** is an employee network focused on
      encouraging increased participation of women and other underrepresented
      groups in technology. The goal of the community is to offer a strong support
      network, encourage community members to continuously pursue technical
      advancement and leadership, helping to inspire the next generation of
      girls in STEM.

      Starting at 3pm, you will get a **tour of our fantastic office space**, gain
      insight into our Software Engineering department, and learn more about life
      at Bloomberg through **1-2-1 shadowing** with an engineer and our **panel discussion**.
      And, if this sparks your interest in a career at Bloomberg, our recruitment
      team will be on hand to talk to you about the Software Engineering positions
      available to you.

      Spaces for this event are limited. We therefore ask you to complete the
      registration form by **28th January**. Spots will be confirmed on **31st January**
      and we will then reach out to you to arrange any travel assistance that you may need.

      Please sign up via http://tinyurl.com/ydy8aaj4.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://tinyurl.com/ydy8aaj4">Sign-up</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>Entrepreneur First - Future Outliers Workshop</heading>
  <sponsor company="ef" />
  <event startDate="2019-02-12T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-12T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Block L, The Biscuit Factory, 100 Drummond Road, SE16 4DG"
    external="true">
    <text>
      **Do you have the technical skills and ambition to build a deep tech company?**

      Entrepreneur First and Imperial are hosting a _Future Outliers_ workshop
      series for 40 students interested in learning how to build a company from
      scratch. You'll get access to the same learning EF shares with the founders
      on their programme. If you want to build a world-changing company, but don't
      know where to start, apply here http://buff.ly/2W9ZFx6 by **February 2nd**.

      The workshops will take place at **EF's London office** on 12th, 13th and 19th Feb from 6pm.

      Please see the flyer attached for more information.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://buff.ly/2W9ZFx6">Apply</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time
  </sign>
</email>
