<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/b13LgID.jpg"
    alt="Stack of biscuits on a plate"
    title="I can't think of an alt text for this one"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome to another digest!

    Last week we kicked off for our IC Hack 20 volunteer onboarding and we want to say "thank you"
    to all passionate students who came - IC Hack is only possible because of you! If you have
    missed the meeting but are still interested to help, you can catch the slides at
    https://docsoc.co.uk/ichack20kickoffcatchup.

    Over the next week, we have planned many academic and off-campus events if you are looking for
    something to distract you from your coursework! We also have some sponsor events and notices, so
    make sure you read till the end!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Imperial College iGEM team</heading>
  <text>
    This year, SynBIC (synthetic biology society at Imperial College), will be gathering an
    interdisciplinary team of exceptional undergraduate students for the international synthetic
    biology competition - iGEM. The 2020 Imperial undergraduate team is currently looking for people
    with strong computing backgrounds until the 15th of November. This google form must be completed
    to apply, and a CV must be submitted at the end of the form. Please note that the iGEM team will
    not be accepting applicants on the first year of their degree.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Imperial Mathematics Competition</heading>
  <text>
    Challenge yourself with maths puzzles in the third edition of Imperial Mathematics Competition!
    Round One of the annual contest will take place in late November, when contestants, from
    universities across the UK, will be given 3 hours to solve 6 problems individually. The top
    performers will be invited to Round Two (the final round) in Term 2.

    Sign up [here](https://icmathscomp.org/signup/). You can have a look at [past papers
    here](https://icmathscomp.org/pages/past-papers.html).

    Students from all departments are welcomed, both undergraduate and one-year master's. Some of
    the
    problems on the papers may require knowledge from the first year of an undergraduate course in
    Maths, much of which is covered in science and engineering courses as well. A separate team
    competition will be run in Term 2, with details to be announced in January.

    The deadline for signing up for the individual contest is **18th of November** and the
    competition will take place on **Sunday 24th November 9:30 - 12:30** in Huxley.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>RESCHEDULED: Reading Group by Sophia Drossopoulou</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Yx1VN94.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-19T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-19T13:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 217">
    <text>
      **Please note this event has been rescheduled to the 19th of November. We apologize for the
      inconvenience.**

      Come and join us at our bi-weekly Reading Groups. This time we have Sophia Drossopoulou who
      will talk about her research "Holistic specifications for robust code". This talk is aimed at
      penultimate/4th year undergraduate as well as postgraduate students.

      Abstract
      Functional specifications of program components describe what the code can do — the sufficient
      conditions to invoke the component’s operations: a client who supplies arguments meeting that
      operation’s preconditions can invoke it, and obtain the associated effect. While
      specifications of sufficient conditions may be enough to reason about complete, unchanging
      programs, they cannot support reasoning about components that interact with external
      components of possibly unknown provenance. In this open world setting, ensuring that your
      component is robust even when executing with buggy or malicious external code is critical.
      Holistic specifications — as their name implies — are concerned with the overall behaviour of
      a component, in all possible interleavings of calls to the component’s operations with those
      of the external code. Thus, holistic specifications are concerned with sufficient conditions,
      i.e. what is enough to cause some effect, as well as with necessary conditions, i.e. what are
      the conditions without which an effect will not happen. By adopting holistic specification
      techniques, programmers can explicitly define what their components should not do, making it
      easier to write robust and reliable programs.

      In this work we argue for the need for such holistic specifications, propose a language
      Chainmail for writing specifications, give a formal semantics, and discuss several examples
      from the literature.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/437009023668599/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>How to build your website with VueJS (Advanced)</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/UUmbQOk.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-21T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-21T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      DoCSoc presents the second workshop on Web Development: "How to build your website"! Come and
      learn more advanced content on web development! Learn you to use your first javascript
      framework (VueJS) using components and animations to make your website look amazing!

      This event is for everyone interested in learning javascript frameworks or expanding your
      knowladge by adding Vue to your toolset. Creating your own responsive and good looking website
      is a great thing to do or know how to do for your your career and future.

      This event will be catered with free pizza and soft drinks as usual! Please press GOING to
      help us gauge our food ordering requirements. If you have any specific dietary requirements,
      please let us know a few days beforehand by emailing docsoc@imperial.ac.uk

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to participate. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2498682180458862/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/docsoc-goes-mini-golf-tickets-81620853169?fbclid=IwAR0cxwGJ1c6YFT5pXupva78EJmBHmOZmJ8oNUOIerYXHEUeEPHyffltna94">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Ed Tech Hackday</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/D0rw30s.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-23T11:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-23T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 342">
    <text>
      Join DoC on Saturday 23rd for a one day Hackathon to learn how your education tools
      (Materials, eMarking and more) are made.

      Please RSVP here: https://forms.gle/foZwZKEN6XVrNVr68

      Learn how real webapps work, chalenge yourselves to contibute to these open sourse projects
      with new and amazing ideas, and win the prize for the best contribution, OR show us your web
      apps knowledge by creating a whole new webapp that will help the EdTech ecosystem!

      Lunch will be provided on the day, so let us know if you plan to attend by sellecting "going"
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/494024571188237/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdQaMWltx44IvT1WfalwPYN-u5oFRRiI9u5Q70IuuHrjftGSQ/viewform">
        RSVP
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Faces of Engineering</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/fZC4bYL.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-28T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-28T21:00:00+00:00"
    location="City and Guilds College Union CGCU">
    <text>
      JFaces of Engineering is CGCU's annual engineering diversity event, bringing together
      students, industry professionals, and engineers from all walks of life. Over the past few
      years, we have had the privilege of hosting companies like Google, Microsoft, and P&G, among
      others.

      This year, we are please to announce that we have confirmed the attendance of Bloomberg,
      American Express, and Qualcomm, with more companies expected to attend! Do be sure to come
      down and get a chance to meet the panelists and understand more about different types of
      engineering professions.

      This year, we are renaming the event "Faces of Engineering"; with Imperial being one of the
      world's most diverse universities, we at the CGCU are continuously striving to fully engage
      staff, students, and the community. We warmly welcome people of all cultures, languages, and
      backgrounds to this event and hope to see a wonderful turnout!

      Details on the location will be confirmed shortly, but in the mean time do sign up to the
      event using the link below. There will be a catered networking session after the panel
      discussion too!

      Thank you and we look forward to seeing you!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/456177365252525/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <text>## Off-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Goes Ice Skating</heading>
  <image src="https://imgur.com/7ppWfty"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-19T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-19T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Natural History Museum Ice Rink">
    <text>
      Get out your scarf and gloves, and join us at the Natural History Museum for an ice skating
      spectacular on Tuesday 19th November.

      DoCSoc will be heavily subsidising tickets to just £4.50! We only have a limited number of
      tickets for this session, so make sure to try and get one.

      The ice skating starts at 7pm, so we will be meeting at 6:30pm at the entrance of the Ice
      Skating Rink - stay tuned for more updates about this.

      TICKETS WILL BE RELEASED ON THURSDAY (14TH NOVEMBER) AT 1PM ON EVENTBRITE. With this please go
      to the Imperial College Union Shop to purchase your ticket, you have a 2 hour window in order
      to confirm your purchase! YOU CAN ONLY BUY A UNION SHOP TICKET IF YOU HAVE AN EVENTBRITE
      PLACEHOLDER TICKET.

      We hope to see you there!

      --------------------------------------------------------------
      You must be a member of DoCSoc by Tuesday 13th November in order to be admitted. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30.

      Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/433582897554833/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc goes Mini Golfing</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/gsNmYlN.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-20T15:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-20T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Puttshack (White City)">
    <text>
      Drop your keyboards and pick up your putters, because DoCSoc is going Mini Golf and we want
      you join in the fun with us!

      DoCSoc will be heavily subsidising tickets to just £6.00! We only have a limited number of
      tickets for this event, so make sure to try and get one.

      The event starts at 3pm at Puttshack White City! - stay tuned for more updates about this.

      TICKETS WILL BE RELEASED ON FRIDAY (15TH NOVEMBER) AT 1PM ON EVENTBRITE. With this please go
      to the Imperial College Union Shop to purchase your ticket, you have a 2 hour window in order
      to confirm your purchase! YOU CAN ONLY BUY A UNION SHOP TICKET IF YOU HAVE AN EVENTBRITE
      PLACEHOLDER TICKET.

      We hope to see you there!

      --------------------------------------------------------------
      You must be a member of DoCSoc by Tuesday 13th November in order to be admitted. Computing,
      JMC, and EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30.

      Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2498682180458862/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/docsoc-goes-mini-golf-tickets-81620853169?fbclid=IwAR0cxwGJ1c6YFT5pXupva78EJmBHmOZmJ8oNUOIerYXHEUeEPHyffltna94">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Women Create - Coding Interview Workshop</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/WzAuUwS.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-19T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-19T20:30:00+00:00"
    location="Facebook, 1 Rathbone Square, London, W1T 1FB">
    <text>
      Hi there!

      Come learn how to put your best foot forward at this Women Create - Crush Your Coding
      Interview Workshop hosted by Facebook.

      This presentation, delivered by one of Facebook’s Software Engineers will cover:

      - How to walk through an algorithm problem,

      - How to brainstorm solutions,

      - How to discuss the problem with your interviewer,

      - How to write (and test) code on a whiteboard

      - Office Tour

      Sign-up link: https://womencreate-codinginterviewwor.splashthat.com/

      Visit this link to prepare:
      https://www.facebook.com/careers/life/preparing-for-your-software-engineering-interview-at-facebook

      We look forward to seeing you there!

      The Facebook Team
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://womencreate-codinginterviewwor.splashthat.com/">
        RSVP
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Liquidnet Interactive Session: Graduate Recruitment; Trading &amp; AI</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/anyZi0q.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-11-25T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-11-25T21:30:00+00:00"
    location="Liquidnet Offices, 24 Floor, Broadgate Tower, Primrose St, London EC2A 2EW">
    <text>
      Join Liquidnet for pizza and prosecco followed by a talk at their offices, 24 floors up in the
      heart of the City of London. It's a great way to network and learn more about the company,
      while
      having fun!

      Check out the event information below and RSVP **for free** in
      [Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-80036171343).

      _Please note this event is 18+ only._

      ---

      Traders in financial markets perform tasks that require them to absorb large amounts of data
      in limited time and make rapid decisions. Time is money and sub-optimal performance can cost
      firms hundreds of millions of dollars a year. Liquidnet augments the human expert with a
      variety of technologies, from anomaly detection pattern recognition algorithms to natural
      language generation and visualizations.

      **Join Liquidnet Chief Data Scientist Tom Doris, PhD.** to discuss challenges in adoption and
      adherence of new technologies by human experts, deconstruct the methods that were effective in
      overcoming the obstacles, and review similarities across other industries.

      There will be an opportunity to network with members of Tom's Technology team, our Recruitment
      Team and Product Team once the interactive session has ended.

      Refreshments will be served.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/liquidnet-interactive-session-graduate-recruitment-trading-ai-tickets-80036171343">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>