<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/NwTWnqP.jpg"
    alt="Stack of biscuits on a plate"
    title="Oddly satisfying"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We hope you enjoyed our Faces of Engineering panel last week, as well as our End of Decade Bar
    Night and (for postgraduates) the Postgraduate Drinks. Thank you to those of you attending the
    off-campus events held by our sponsors Liquidnet and Entrepreneur First, we hope you found them
    useful and fun.

    As the Department of Computing goes into December exams (or in the case of
    second years, their final week of Pintos), the next week will be quieter.
    Despite the short digest, we have some exciting things to announce,
    including an open Union debate about the planned halls rent increase. There will also be our
    annual Christmas party and long-awaited UROP 101 talk, so read on for more information!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Halls Rent Debate</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/GXGejqV.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-03T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-03T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Read Lecture Theatre, Sherfield Level 5">
    <text>
      Have your say over the price of rent in halls.

      SIGN UP HERE: https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/whats-on/event/7503

      The College and the Union negotiate over the price of rent in halls periodically, and this
      year we have a real opportunity to shape what this will look like. We're holding a special
      meeting of Union Council to decide on the best way to move forward.

      The plan is for the President and Deputy President Welfare to present the information they
      have and invite questions and contributions from the floor, and then for elected student reps
      from across the College to take a vote on the best way to move forward.

      Please join us and make your voice heard!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/783256598770880/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/whats-on/event/7503">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Imperial Careers Service and JobsLive Events</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/tFXEIeD.png"/>
  <text>
    Are you an undergraduate still looking for an internship over the summer? Or maybe a
    graduating student looking for employment? With internship deadlines fast approaching, you're
    not too late to start applying with the help of Imperial Careers Service!

    From CV/cover letter workshops, mock interviews, to Employer Led sessions (past events include
    events run by Airbus, HSBC, Nestle and KPMG), there is a wealth of events available on JobsLive
    to help you get started with your internship/job pursuit.

    Make sure to follow Careers Service on social media to stay updated with events announcements,
    as well as different competitions they run (for a chance to win a prize!):
    [Facebook](https://facebook.com/imperialcollegecareers)
    [Twitter](https://twitter.com/imperialcareers)
    [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/ic_careers)
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Conf42 - Chaos Engineering Conference - Special DoCSoc Tickets</heading>
  <event
    startDate="2020-01-23T08:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-01-24T16:30:00+00:00"
    location="1a Oxendon St, London SW1Y 4EE">
    <text>
      Learn how companies such as Netflix and PagerDuty intentionally break their systems at scale
      to build more resilient, scalable systems.
      Conf42 (https://conf42.com) is giving away heavily discounted tickets to DoCSoc members and
      Imperial College students. Conf42 will take place on 23rd January 2020 at The Comedy Store in
      Soho, with a day of talks from industry leaders in chaos engineering, followed by networking
      drinks at The Comedy Pub.
      The following special tickets are available for all Imperial College students (bring your
      friends!):
      all students can purchase a conference ticket for a heavily discounted price of £39 (standard
      price £339);
      students from underrepresented groups in technology who are unable to attend without financial
      assistance can apply for free tickets. (DoCSoc is also able to subsidise the cost of travel
      for attendees who are eligible for this category.)
      To obtain a special ticket, email docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Christmas Party</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/4GFqCv2.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-03T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-03T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 342">
    <text>
      Come put on your Santa hat and Christmas jumper, and join us for a night of festive fun!
      There'll be mince pies, Christmassy snacks, mulled wine, hot chocolate, and more. We'll also
      be playing some games, so come get into the holiday spirit with us at the end of a busy term
      or have one final party before your exams!

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to attend. Computing, JMC, and
      EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/566830340747253/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>UROP 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/mxAQAd9.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-06T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-06T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 145">
    <text>
      Thinking of how to enjoy your summer and learn new technologies? Then join us at UROP 101 talk
      where you will get to know all essential information about Undergraduate Research
      Opportunities Programme. The speaker of the talk will be Paul Kelly who manages the scheme.

      _______

      You must be a member of DoCSoc on the day of the event in order to attend. Computing, JMC, and
      EIE students are automatically DoCSoc members. Membership can be purchased for £30 at
      docsoc.co.uk/join.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2192846977676102/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## External Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Future of Blockchain Algorand Workshop</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/0HOfBFA.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2019-12-03T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-12-03T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="KCL South East Wing">
    <text>
      Join us for a technical deep-dive into Algorand with one of their core developers.

      This is a must-attend event for those building on Algorand in Future of Blockchain or
      considering doing so!

      If you don't know already, Future of Blockchain is a 3 month competition for developers and
      entrepreneurs to build a project. Late registrations are still open via
      www.futureofblockchain.co.uk.

      We'll be covering:
      - Technical overview of Algorand
      - Algorand new features
      - How to build an app on Algorand
      - Top tips on how to win a prize on Algorand!
      - Pizza and beer

      Please note it would be helpful to bring a laptop!

      There are travel grants of available for those travelling from Cambridge or Oxford! Email
      Anthony if you need one - anthony@stakezero.com.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/772118853306920/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities Internships and Graduate Positions</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    **Citadel** is a leading investor in the world’s financial markets. For over a quarter of a
    century,
    we have sought to deliver industry-leading investment returns to clients including corporate
    pensions, endowments, foundations, public institutions, and sovereign wealth funds.

    **Citadel Securities** is an award-winning global market maker that helps meet the liquidity
    needs
    of asset managers, banks, broker-dealers, hedge funds, government agencies, and public pension
    programs.

    Applications open for both internships and graduate roles for the following positions:
    - Investment &amp; Trading
    - Quantitative Strategies
    - Software Engineering

    Apply via our websites citadel.com &amp; citadelsecurities.com
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>

</email>