<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Mums and Dads is Back - Parents Sign Up!" agenda="false" logos="false">
    <text>
        It's that time of the year again - DoC is about to be joined by a new
        cohort of first years!
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Hence, the Mums and Dads Scheme returns!

        If you're unfamiliar with the Mums and Dads Scheme, every year DoCSoc
        members can become the "adoptive parents" of up to 6 freshers and
        form a family. It is not only a great way to welcome freshers and help
        them settle into university life, but for everyone involved to make
        some friends and enjoy some events together. Each family will get a
        termly budget that they can decide how to spend themselves.
        &lt;br/&gt;
        **If you're interested in joining as a parent click [here](https://mad.docsoc.co.uk/parent)!**


    </text>
    <hr/>
    <text>
        FAQ:

        **How does it all work?**
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Parents are existing 2nd, 3rd, and 4th year Computing and JMC students
        in DoC. Each family will consist of two parents, and up to 6 freshers.
        After term commences, there will be a timetabled slot for freshers to
        meet their families, along with some food and activities to get to know
        each other. Each term there is also a small budget for each family
        (around 20 pounds) to use as appropriate (dinner, drinks, any family
        gathering etc).

        **Can I sign up as a solo parent?**
        &lt;br/&gt;
        No, unfortunately you can't. You will need to sign up with a partner -
        this is done to ensure the best possible experience for incoming
        freshers. If you sign up without choosing a partner, your registration
        will be ignored.

        **I've already signed up on the union website. Do I sign up here too?**
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Yes, please do. If you haven't signed up on the union website then you
        won't need to, as long as you sign up here.

        **How will freshers be allocated?**
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Based on the interests filled in, we do our best to assign each fresher
        to fellow freshers and parents with similar interests. If you're
        interested to find out more, the source code of this application is
        available on [Github](https://github.com/docsocsf/mad2).

        If you have any other questions, please feel free to message our
        facebook page or send us an email!
    </text>
</email>