<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="55"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/VsDtOCH.jpgl"
    alt="Chocolate chip cookie"
    title="" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Our committee has been busy preparing for IC Hack 19 but that definitely doesn't
    mean we'll let the term go by without any events! That's right - we have another
    bar night coming up this week! More details below.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 Volunteers</heading>
  <text>
    If you didn't manage to get a ticket to IC Hack 19, you can still take part
    by volunteering on the day! It isn't easy making an event go smoothly for
    400 attendees and every volunteer counts.

    To volunteer, join the [DoCSoc Operations](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/members/)
    Facebook group and we'll post more instructions soon.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Imperial Venture Catalyst Challenge</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/4pNN0eT.jpg" />
  <text>
    The deadline for applications to the Imperial Venture Catalyst Challenge
    competition is on the 20th Jan. This year’s competition has an £80K total
    prize fund as well as a dedicated AI, Software &amp; Robotics track sponsored
    by Amazon Robotics.

    The Venture Catalyst Challenge enables Imperial students and alumni, within
    three years of graduation, to develop an innovative idea for commercialisation.
    If you have created something as part of your coursework, have an idea that
    spins out of your research, or have a project you’ve been messing
    around with on weekends, then the VCC is for you!

    For more information, visit [this page](https://www.imperialenterpriselab.com/programmes/vcc/) for more details.

    _Please note this programme is not run by DoCSoc._
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>The New Year Bar Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/KbgH0WP.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-01-17T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-01-17T23:00:00+00:00"
    location="Metric">
    <text>
      Come celebrate the start of 2019 with us at the first bar night of the year!
      Everyone's welcome (even if you've given up on your New Year's Resolutions
      already 👀).

      Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to DoCSoc members. Tokens
      are valid for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/790551464622069/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/NxONDEd.png" />
  <text>
    Facebook is launching their 3rd run of Hack-a-project!

    This is a 5-week mentoring programme kicking off in February 2019, designed
    for 1st years of a three year degree and 2nd years of a fourth year degree,
    looking to apply for a Software Engineering internship with Facebook. Selected
    students will come to the Facebook office, once a week in the evening to learn
    about the whole development cycle and build a project as a team via a hackathon!

    In addition, we will be sharing tips on “how to crush your coding interview”,
    and also do a mock interview with you, where feedback will be provided to help
    you improve.

    Each session will also be catered, so come hungry (to learn and to eat!)

    **If you are interested, please sign-up by following [this](https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=https-3A__hackaproject2019.splashthat.com_&amp;d=DwMF-g&amp;c=5VD0RTtNlTh3ycd41b3MUw&amp;r=4Ht1aWc8IssynPN9692iKw&amp;m=3QnJFgqZ2ln3T1h10vEd1PXGLEETEPLoEWP_HRlZc9k&amp;s=rGe1mlmZqLK51_y0Ld3_wzqoa2xekf0TsLzs_VBIJ2E&amp;amp;e=)
    link AND send your CV to LucyKemp@fb.com with the subject headline ‘Hack-a-project – applicant 2019’.**

    **The deadline for applications is the 1st of Feb.**
  </text>


  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time
  </sign>
</email>
