<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email agenda="false" logos="false">

  <text>
    Wolfram Research is pleased to sponsor your event by providing access to our
    latest technology, Wolfram|One! For complimentary access to our development
    platform and the Wolfram API, just click here:

    https://account.wolfram.com/redeem/ICHackUK2019

    This URL will take you to a sign-in page and prompt you to log in using your
    Wolfram ID. If you don't already have a Wolfram ID, you'll be prompted to
    create one using an active email address. Once logged in, you will see in the
    Downloads section which platforms of the software you have access to, with
    their accompanying activation keys. Please download the desktop version to
    your machine, boot up the application and use the associated activation key
    when prompted. This will grant you full access for 30 days from your activation date.

    When you access Wolfram|One in the cloud for the first time, you can create
    a new notebook or load a pre-made Things to Try live notebook, which is designed
    to guide you through neat things you can immediately compute in the Wolfram Language.

    You can use Wolfram|One to create instant web apps and APIs, or to deploy to
    mobile. The Wolfram Language is also bundled on the Raspberry Pi, where you
    can connect directly to hardware, including Arduino etc.

    The fastest way to get an API up and running is detailed in the extensive
    Documentation Center available to you alongside your notebook: simply click
    the section in the documentation labeled Cloud and Deployment and select Instant
    APIs to access a handy how-to guide to help get you started.

    To view your account details-- including your available Cloud Credits and
    Cloud storage-- or re-download Wolfram|One, visit the following page:
    https://account.wolfram.com/products

    Wolfram|One is the world's first fully integrated cloud-desktop hybrid,
    integrated computation platform. The core of our technology stack is the
    Wolfram Language, which builds on three decades of development, and represents
    a new direction in programming-- that happens to be absolutely ideal for hackathons.

    The Wolfram Language is optimized to make it easy to write small amounts of
    code that do spectacular things. As a language, it has an immense amount of
    knowledge about the world built into it, allowing for maximum automation.

    If you've used Mathematica in school, you already know a lot about the Wolfram
    Language. But regardless, it's very easy to learn. If you want to get a sense
    of how quick it is to do interesting things, check out Tweet-a-Program:
    https://www.wolfram.com/language/tweet-a-program

    We've put together a general page of resources for hackathon participants: https://www.wolfram.com/hackathons

    And there's an online book with exercises: https://www.wolfram.com/language/elementary-introduction

    Wolfram Summer Programs has offerings for exceptional teens in high school as
    well as undergrads through post-docs. These programs are for those interested
    in programming, computational thinking, machine learning, and innovative tech.
    Students create and complete a unique project to publish during the program.
    For more information and to apply visit: http://education.wolfram.com/summer/

    A great way to continue building your Wolfram Language coding skills is to
    choose a track on the free Wolfram Challenges site: https://challenges.wolfram.com/.
    If you make it to the leaderboard please email me to let me know!

    Interested in Wolfram mentorships or internships? Check out our
    opportunities here: https://www.wolfram.com/company/careers

    Good luck, and happy hacking!

    Carol Cronin
    Sponsorships
    Wolfram Research, Inc.
    www.wolfram.com
    education.wolfram.com/summer
    carolc@wolfram.com
  </text>
</email>
