<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/nAINi53.jpg"
    alt="Two ice creams with biscuits in them next to sunglasses"
    title="Looks like summer's arrived!" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hello again!

    While you're busy with work or busy enjoying the sun (or both!), here's a short
    digest email to keep you up to date with DoCSoc.

    For those who got back from our international trip to Prague this week, photos
    will be uploaded soon!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc CV Reviews</heading>
  <text>
    Got questions about your CV or internship applications?

    Though it's still early for the upcoming internship search season, some of
    you may want to get a head start. DoCSoc is currently rolling out a new
    initiative, where first and second years who want a CV review and advice
    can be matched with third and fourth years who are seasoned veterans of the
    job search process (and have also been trained by the college Careers Service!).

    If you're interested, please fill in this form: https://forms.gle/7UYRsKvfwdmciQWQ9
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc End of Year Dinner (Sold Out!)</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hgi0gik.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-06-17T19:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2019-06-18T00:30:00+01:00"
    location="Bluebird Chelsea">
    <text>
      **Sold out!**

      It is time for the final DoCSoc event of the year, our annual End Of Year
      Dinner! Join us at Bluebird Chelsea on 17th June at 7pm for an exciting
      evening filled with food, drink and dance.

      Upon arrival, you will be welcomed with a champagne reception followed by
      a three-course meal along with wine or beer.

      So pick out your best dresses/suits for this glamorous, black tie evening
      and together we hope to make it an extremely memorable night!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/836958003349840/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Facebook Black@ Workshop</heading>
  <sponsor company="facebook">
     \
    Hi there!

    Facebook's Black@ community, are hosting a Web development &amp; Github Workshop for students.

    **The Black@ community’s mission**: is to build a strong vibrant community
    that leads the conversation on equity, accelerating the personal and
    professional development of its members, and beyond.

    This workshop will be run by one of our Software Engineers and will focus on:

    -	Basics of Web Development - front end, back end and data storage
    -	How to create and build a project on Github www.github.com
    -	Panel and Q&amp;A with members of the Black@ community
    -	Networking

    When and where?

    -	Date: Thursday 20th of June
    -	Time: 18:30
    -	Location: **Facebook’s London Office**

    Our aim with this workshop is for you to get a bit more exposure to web
    development, help you to start your own personal coding project and learn
    more about the Black@ community here at Facebook.

    If you are interested in signing up, please follow this link: https://webdevelopmentandgithubworksho.splashthat.com/

    Best wishes, \
    Lucy and The Black@ Facebook Community
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
