<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="EF x DoCSoc"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">

  <text>
    Hi all!

    **Entrepreneur First** are holding a **guest lecture** with Matt Clifford
    (the co-founder and CEO of Entrepreneur First) followed by a **panel discussion**
    with Georgina Kirby (Imperial alumnus and founder of Vine Health) and Mostafa
    Elsayed (founder of robotics startup Automata). This will take place in Clore LT
    next Thursday.

    If you're interested in entrepreneurship or looking into building your own startup,
    this talk will provide a great insight into the ecosystem and programme which
    EF provides. This event is aimed in particular towards postgraduates and PhDs,
    where specialisms and experience provide great value to building a startup.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>EF x DoCSoc: The Founder Mindset with Matt Clifford and guests</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DuO9Hdh.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2018-02-21T18:15:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-02-21T21:15:00+00:00"
    location="Clore Lecture Theatre, Huxley Building">
    <text>
      **Matt Clifford is the co-founder and CEO of Entrepreneur First**, the world's
      leading talent investor on a mission to kick-start the next generation of
      globally important deep-tech companies. How? By finding exceptional individuals
      before they’re founders and supporting them to find a co-founder, develop
      an idea and raise investment. Since starting EF seven years ago, he has
      worked with over 1,000 people to build over 200 companies around the world,
      collectively valued at $1.6bn.

      **From all the individuals he's met, Matt has had the chance to observe the
      most important, and often hidden, traits that the most successful entrepreneurs
      have in common. In this guest lecture, he will share five mindsets that are
      critical to successful founders, and what you can do to develop them.**

      EF will be inviting TWO ATTENDEES, selected at RANDOM, to visit their offices
      and meet with Matt or Alice (EF's co-founders), and the team! All you have
      to do is register for a ticket, and sign-in on the day.

      After his lecture, Matt will interview two founders who are at different
      points in their startup journey.

      **Mostafa ElSayed is the CEO and co-founder of robotics startup Automata**,
      which is democratising robotics for the SME, consumer and hobbyist markets.
      Their first product, Eva, is a benchtop robot arm that can be set up in
      minutes, costs a fraction of other industrial arms, and can be used in a
      range of industries including metals, pharmaceuticals and electronics
      manufacturing. Surprisingly, Mostafa didn’t have a history in robotics
      before starting Automata, but trained as an architect and was working for
      Zaha Hadid, the infamous designer of the London Olympics Aquatics Centre
      and many other iconic buildings. Fast-forward, four years and Automata has
      raised sizeable Series A and grown to a 30-person company, with plans to
      expand this year. Join us to hear Mostafa’s personal story, from everything
      he has learnt about startups, and himself, along the way.

      **Georgina Kirby is CTO and co-founder of Vine Health**. Having completed her
      Masters at Imperial Department of Surgery and Cancer, she went on to work
      as a Data Scientist for 5 years before joining EF’s current cohort. Having
      met her co-founder Rayna Patel, a medical doctor and neuroscientist, just
      4 months ago, they have now raised £80K in pre-seed investment from Entrepreneur
      First to launch Vine Health. Vine Health aims to optimise cancer patient
      outcomes using artificial intelligence and behavioural neuropsychology.
      Now, Georgina is preparing to pitch to VCs at Demo Day in just three months
      time. She’ll share her journey so far, and particularly what matters most
      in the very early days of starting something.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ef-x-docsoc-the-founder-mindset-with-matt-clifford-georgina-kirby-and-mostafa-elsayed-tickets-56180916634">Eventbrite (RSVP)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/304995220371967/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
