<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/R9e6434.jpg?1"
    alt="Stack of biscuits next to tea"
    title="I am eternally offended by a certain first year who suggested that a past digest had a photo of '*coffee* and biscuits'. It's completely absurd to even suggest such a non-traditional combination would appear in a digest email." />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Last week was a busy week, with events including Revel, a Unity workshop, a talk from
    Palantir, election hustings and finally, our yearly health-related
    hackathon, Health Hack!

    With exam season for third and fourth years, as well as voting opening for
    the Leadership Elections, we have a quiet week planned ahead so all of us can try
    focus on some work. If you don't have imminent exams just yet, we do have a
    talk by an ex-Imperial student (and now-DeepMind employee) next Tuesday and
    a few other announcements to make. Read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Merch Collection</heading>
  <text>
    If you ordered merchandise from us this year, they are now on the way and
    almost ready for collection! We'll be sending out a separate mailshot soon
    to let you know about collection dates and times.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Vote in the Leadership Elections!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/q5ZQOjp.jpg" width="80" />
  <text>
    It's that time of year again where you get endlessly pestered by people asking
    for you to vote for them. That's right - it's time to vote for next year's
    DoCSoc committee and wider Imperial College Union roles.

    Voting opens tomorrow, Monday 11th March and closes on Thursday 14th March.
    Be sure to check out candidates' manifestos [here](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/leadership-elections-2019/manifestos/a-to-z)
    and vote by going to https://vote.union.ic.ac.uk/!

    We would also encourage you to vote for CGCU and sabbatical roles too. Sabbatical officers
    such as the Union President and Deputy President for Finance and Services, as well
    as CGCU officers such as the President and Treasurer, all affect how well
    DoCSoc runs.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>What I Wish I Knew As An Imperial Student (presented by a DeepMind employee)</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/zR7cyVF.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-12T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-12T19:30:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Andrea Michi is an Imperial alumni who's spent the last 3 years working
      for Google and DeepMind. He'll be coming in to present on everything he
      would have loved to know before he started his job - a talk which has been
      very popular when presented internally at Google.

      Andrea will cover many soft topics often ignored in the tech industry:
      how to deal with rejections and failures, what you should prioritise at
      the start of your career, how to give, receive, and internalise feedback,
      how you can be a better teammate and a more efficient engineer.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/338191750124340/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir Women in Tech Scholarship</heading>
  <sponsor company="palantir">
    We launched the Palantir Women in Technology Scholarship in 2010 to celebrate
    and support women who are beginning careers in technology. We hope to encourage
    women to pursue computer science, engineering, and technical studies, and to
    become leaders in these fields.

    This year, 10 scholarship recipients will be chosen and invited to visit our
    London office for a full-day, all-expenses paid developmental workshop.
    Programming will include professional development sessions, breakouts with
    our engineers, and some fun social activities! All recipients are awarded
    grants of £5,500 to support their education.

    The scholarship is open to students who:

    -	Are active, full-time undergraduate or Master's students enrolled in an
    accredited European college/university during the academic years that the
    scholarship is awarded, i.e., you must be enrolled in both the current
    (2018-19) and upcoming (2019-20) academic years
    -	Are majoring in or plan to major in Science, Technology, Engineering or
    Math (STEM) fields
    -	Identify as women
    -	Have not been finalists in the past

    For more information, click [here](https://jobs.lever.co/palantir/2dce1c15-faca-4e91-a8aa-0c2c6a259d77) and
    see the flyer attached!
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
