<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Vive la Revelution - Early Bird Tickets"
  logos="false"
  agenda="false">

  <text>
    It’s finally time! 😃 Early Bird tickets for DoCSoc members will be released at **1pm
    on Thursday 21st February** for £20 each.

    In order to purchase tickets for the event you first need to secure
    **Eventbrite placeholder tickets** at https://revel-london.eventbrite.co.uk.
    Once you have secured a ticket on Eventbrite please head to the **Union website** [here](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/club-society-project-products/computing-products/26254/vive-la-revelution)
    to complete the purchase of your ticket **before 3pm**. Purchases without
    an Eventbrite placeholder ticket will be cancelled.

    Please note that you are allowed to buy a +1 ticket (for a maximum of 2 tickets
    per person). Please include the email address of your +1 when you buy the
    Eventbrite ticket and pay for both tickets on the Union website.

    Please remember to read the terms and conditions of your ticket after
    purchasing. You must have been a DoCSoc member before 18th February to be
    eligible for the tickets.

    We look forward to having you there!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/OxixkQe.jpg" />
  <event startDate="2019-03-04T20:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-03-05T02:00:00+00:00"
    location="Café de Paris, 3 Coventry Street, London, W1D 6BL">
    <text>
      DoCSoc and RCSU have come together again to bring to you the HOTTEST party
      of the year, this time with a French twist - Vive la Revelution!

      From rooftop bars to Spanish restaurants, we’re now taking you to the city
      of love. Vive la Revelution will be taking place in Café de Paris, one of the most famous entertainment venues in the world.

      Drinks, canapés, dancing and entertainment - we’ve got it all covered. All
      you have to do is buy a ticket and dress to impress in black tie!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/370168953714798/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <text>
    Terms and Conditions:

    - Tickets may be purchased by DoCSoc or RCSU members only, and the event
    is strictly 18+. Government issued ID must be brought to the venue or entry
    will be refused. You may purchase a +1 ticket for anyone from any department
    (or external), but tickets are limited to two per member across all sales!
    - Ticket transfers are allowed only to people who would have been otherwise
    eligible to them.
    - You must have been a DoCSoc member before 18th February 2019 to qualify for DoCSoc tickets.
    - RCSU members cannot purchase DoCSoc tickets (and vice-versa).
    - Drinks will be staggered throughout the night to ensure the best possible
    experience for all our attendees. In the case of indecent or rowdy behaviour,
    the venue reserves the right to escort you from the premises.
    - A maximum of two drinks are allowed to be ordered at the bar at any time.
  </text>
</email>
