<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email agenda="false" logos="false">

  <image
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dJL5aDU.png"
    title="IC Hack 19 IS ALMOST HERE!"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    **IC Hack 19 Powered by Cisco** is only a few days away. We can't wait to see
    you there! In the meantime, we have some **key information** for you to go through,
    so be sure to read through this email carefully!
  </text>

  <image src="https://media.giphy.com/media/1hwRvWKkkoJby/giphy.gif"
         width="50"/>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Join Our Slack!

    Join our Slack team using [this link](https://join.slack.com/t/ichack19/shared_invite/enQtNTEwNTA2OTAzODI0LWFjMWNkZTQyZDNjYTgxMTdhOTZlODNiNGZjYjc5MDI3YTdkYTVkYTc4MTRjM2QxMmFhZjA2NzUxN2Y3NzEzNzk).
    We use the Slack team to **make important announcements** (on the *#announcements* channel)
    and you can use the team to talk to organisers, sponsors and fellow hackers.
    Make sure you **join the team before the weekend** so you don't miss any important
    information.

    Keep an eye on our sponsor (*#sp-[sponsor]*) channels to find out more about them and take
    part in their challenges. If you're looking for a team, be sure to join the *#team-forming*
    channel.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Ticket Cancellations

    As we have a very long waitlist, if you are unable to attend, please cancel
    your ticket [via Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/mytickets/)
    as soon as possible so your space can be released. If you are
    having difficulties doing so, you can email us at info@ichack.org. Please note
    that tickets are non-transferable.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Equipment Requests

    We're happy to provide our attendees with hardware/equipment for their hacks
    on a best-effort basis. If you have an idea which requires additional equipment,
    please send a short proposal to info@ichack.org detailing your idea and what
    equipment you require, and we'll do our best to provide you with what you need!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## What to Bring

    On the day, be sure to have your Eventbrite ticket ready (either digital or
    printed - up to you!) and a **valid form of Government ID** (driving license
    or passport). Please note you must be **over 18** on the day of the event to attend.

    Also don't forget to bring chargers for your devices (including your phone and
    laptop) to keep them powered on overnight. Bringing a warm coat is also
    recommended as some of our activities may involve going outdoors.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Getting There

    IC Hack is hosted at **Imperial College South Kensington Campus**. The registration
    will take place at the **main entrance** on Exhibition Road, SW7 2BX. The best way
    to reach the venue is via tube to South Kensington Station (District, Circle and
    Piccadilly lines), then either walking up the subway (exiting at the end of the
    subway and turning left) or up Exhibition Road.

    Alternatively, you can take buses **9, 23, 52, 70, 452**, which stop opposite the
    Royal Albert Hall. The Imperial College main entrance is then a short, five-minute
    walk south from there. There are limited car parking spaces nearby, so we
    recommend using public transport.

    **Registration starts from 10:00am**. Please **do not be late** as the Opening Ceremony
    starts at 10:45am!

    Please be sure to bring a **valid form of Government ID** for admission,
    hardware loans and to be able to attend the _Drinks with PolyAI_ activity.

    If you are walking from South Kensington station, here is a map of the route:
  </text>

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6G1A6fb.png"
         width="70" />

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Schedule

    The schedule for the weekend is as follows:

    **Saturday 26th January**

    - **10:00** - Check-in
    - **10:45** - Opening Ceremony
    - **12:00** - Hacking begins
    - **12:15** - Cisco Workshop 1 - *Hacking with Cisco Collaboration Technologies*
    - **13:15** - Lunch
    - **14:00** - Next Jump Workshop - *Getting to grips with Go*
    - **14:40** - Visa Workshop - *Tech for Good: How can we utilize technology for the betterment of society?*
    - **15:20** - Atlas City Workshop - *Build your Dreamed dApp*
    - **16:00** - Cisco Workshop 2 - *Introduction to Cisco DevNet*
    - **18:00** - Sleep Class with Next Jump
    - **18:30** - Sleep Class with Next Jump 2
    - **19:00** - Nando's Dinner by Two Sigma
    - **21:00** - Drinks with PolyAI

    **Sunday 27th January**

    - **00:00** - Midnight Pizza with G-Research
    - **02:00** - Karaoke
    - **07:00** - Breakfast
    - **12:00** - Hacking ends
    - **12:15** - Lunch
    - **13:00** - Judging
    - **15:00** - Closing ceremony
    - **17:00** - IC Hack ends
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Venue

    Below is a map of the campus and of all the rooms where IC Hack will be hosted.
    If you're on a mobile device, click [here](https://i.imgur.com/r3AOiou.png) for
    the full image. A physical copy of this will be inside the lanyard booklet
    given to you at the event.
  </text>

  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/r3AOiou.png" />

  <hr />

  <text>
    Finally, be sure to make good use of the **#ICHack19** hashtag on social media!

    If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know by emailing
    info@ichack.org.

    We look forward to seeing you at IC Hack 19!

    _- The IC Hack 19 team_
  </text>
</email>
