<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><email title="Netcraft Open Days" agenda="false" logos="false">    <text>        Hi everyone,        Netcraft reached out to us with some great opportunities for you to        learn more about the company and web security, have fun with a        cryptocurrency workshop, as well as mingle with dinner and drinks!        If you're interested, check out the details below!    </text>    <hr/>    <sponsor company="netcraft">        Netcraft is running open days at our offices in London on multiple        dates through September and early October. We hire &amp; award prizes        to computer science students at top universities, including Imperial,        Bath, Bristol and Southampton, and so our open days are a good        opportunity to meet high achieving computer scientists from other        universities, and to meet Netcraft staff.        The event starts at 14:00, and we will adjourn to a local restaurant        for dinner and drinks by 18:00. At past events usually everyone has        left by 20:00 – 20:30. Please choose whichever is the most convenient        date. If traveling from outside of London, we are happy to pay        receipted travel expenses of up to £60, or possibly more if approved        prior to the event.        The draft schedule for each event is as follows:        **Introduction to Netcraft**        An introduction to Netcraft, the services we provide and our customers.        **Breaking Badware**        The traditional psychology of “blocking” malware attacks is        wrongheaded, because it puts the attacker in a “heads I win, tails        I don’t lose” situation. Breaking the malware by running it—observing        the network traffic as the malware fetches its payload and contacts        its command &amp; control URL(s)—and then launching takedowns against        those URLs is much more satisfying. In this way the recipient of the        malware not only protects themselves, but also a much wider community        of people who may receive the same malware, or other malware that        shares the same infrastructure. A better and more ambitious objective        than blocking attacks, therefore, is that each attack should leave the        attacker worse off as they lose progressively more and more of the        infrastructure and resources over which they had control. We will        demonstrate how this works in practice and at scale.        **Evil JavaScript**        JavaScript skimmers are an effective way for a criminal to monetise a        hacked shop or ecommerce site. JavaScript is added to otherwise        legitimate websites to steal a copy of all of the credentials entered        into the site, which can then be used by the criminal in        cardholder-not-present fraud. When a busy site is skimmed, the impact        can be substantial. British Airways was recently fined £183M after        giving in the region of half a million customers’ credentials to        criminals in this way. Through our relationship with the NCSC, Netcraft        provides countermeasures against JavaScript skimmers to shops hosted in        the UK, and we explore the cut &amp; thrust of this service.        **Breaking the Bank**        Netcraft tests the security of web based applications, usually for        banks, payment providers and the financial services industry. We review        the opportunities that we look for, the problems that we find, and        cover some of the defences that can be put in place to ensure your code        does not create these types of vulnerability.        **Cryptocurrencies for Fun and Profit**        To take part, **bring your own laptop** with a web browser and an SSH        client (e.g. Putty for Windows users; OpenSSH for Linux/Mac users).        Over the past few years the popularity and value of cryptocurrencies,        such as Bitcoin, has soared. Bitcoin has also spawned a number of        spinoff currencies, known as 'altcoins'. Some altcoins attempt to        provide innovations and improvements over Bitcoin; however, many are        forks with minimal changes launched as Ponzi schemes. Outrageous        vulnerabilities have been discovered in some altcoins, and even Bitcoin        has had its share of vulnerabilities.        Not wanting to miss out on the fun, we have created a cryptocurrency,        Cryptopuff. Like other cryptocurrencies, it has vulnerabilities. Your        challenge, after a short talk illustrating the concepts, is to compete        against your peers to mine, steal and forge as much Cryptopuff as you        can, whilst simultaneously defending your own stash against all comers.        The winner is the person or team with the most Cryptopuff when we pack        up to go to the restaurant.        **RSVP**        Please confirm your preferred date by filling out the following form:        https://forms.gle/VxptY55kDRj1WMuE8. Additionally, if you are        interested in working with us, please email [cv@netcraft.com](mailto:cv@netcraft.com).        **Location**        Our office is located in Hammersmith, approximately a 5 minute walk        from the underground station. If we receive a large number of signups        we will hire a larger venue in the Hammersmith/Imperial area and inform        you of the details in advance of the event.    </sponsor>    <sign name="Radostin Petrov"          role="DoCSoc Secretary 19/20"          facebook="radostin.petrov.99">        Until next time,    </sign></email>