<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email agenda="false" logos="false">

  <image
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dJL5aDU.png"
    title="IC Hack 19: Hello from Cisco"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    IC Hack 19 Powered by Cisco is only a few days away and we hope you're excited!
    In the meantime, our title sponsor, Cisco, have reached out with an introduction.
    Read on below!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    Cisco is proud to be title sponsor of IC Hack 19.

    Collaboration, IoT and networking are at the heart of what we do. To that end,
    the Cisco challenge for IC Hack 19 is to build something innovative in the
    collaboration space, leveraging the extensive developer APIs provided by Cisco's
    popular Webex platform (https://developer.webex.com/). Enhance collaboration
    however you see fit, from writing a bot powered by AWS, to customising the
    Webex experience with our widget API or even integrating Webex into an
    entirely new space utilising the power of our integration API. The team with
    the most innovative and useful hack will win £200 of Amazon vouchers per team
    member, courtesy of Cisco and IC Hack.

    No idea where to start? Then our two workshops are for you. At 12:15 on Saturday,
    we'll be running a "Your First Webex Teams Bot" workshop - guiding you through
    developing a Webex Teams chat bot from scratch (keep an eye on *#sp-cisco* for
    prerequisites). At 15:00, our second "Introduction to Cisco DevNet" workshop
    will give you an overview of the vast array of tools and resources that DevNet
    has to offer (https://developer.cisco.com/).

    Visit us at our stall over the weekend (we'll have plenty of goodies too!) or
    get in touch on #sp-cisco to learn more about who we are, what we do, and what
    opportunities we have here in London - here are some you can chat to us about:
    http://cs.co/media-engineering-uk-jobs.

    We hope you're looking forward to this weekend as much as we are. See you there!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know by emailing
    info@ichack.org.

    We look forward to seeing you at IC Hack 19!

    _- The IC Hack 19 team_
  </text>
</email>
