<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/WZJa6LG.jpg"
    alt="Container of Danish butter cookies"
    title="" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome back! We hope you had a well-deserved, enjoyable break and are feeling
    refreshed for another term.

    Over the next term, DoCSoc will be holding our yearly flagship events, IC Hack
    19 and Revel. We'll also be continuing our usual series of social events, including
    bar nights, trips and more! Be sure to stay updated over our social media
    channels (especially Facebook!) and weekly digest emails.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Merch Update</heading>
  <text>
    For those of you who ordered DoCSoc-branded merchandise last term, we will
    be following up with pick-up times over the coming weeks.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Post-Haskell Curry Night (Freshers Only)</heading>
  <event startDate="2019-01-13T17:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-01-13T20:00:00+00:00"
    location="Sheba Brick Lane, 136 Brick Lane, London, E1 6RU">
    <text>
      Now that you've finished your first major exam at Imperial, we want you to
      take a well-deserved break and enjoy the delicious curry dishes of the famous
      Brick Lane, on us!

      So whether you want to celebrate smashing the exam or drown your sorrows
      in tikka masala, come join your fellow coursemates at the Sheba Restaurant
      on Sunday 13th Jan at 5pm for a great time and great food!

      ONLY first year Computing and JMC students are allowed to purchase tickets - they
      will be revoked otherwise.

      Tickets will be released on Eventbrite - more information coming soon!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/post-haskell-curry-night-freshers-only-tickets-54499654935">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1966152080356316/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr />

  <heading>IC Hack 19 - Batch Two Ticket Release</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/dJL5aDU.png" />
  <event startDate="2019-01-26T10:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2019-01-27T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      24 hours.
      Amazing prizes.
      Are you ready for IC Hack 19?

      Running for its eighth consecutive year, we’re bringing over 400 of the
      UK's most creative and talented students together for 24 hours of learning,
      building, fun, and networking on the weekend of 26-27th January 2019.
      Come create something cool!

      IC Hack 19 Powered By Cisco will be hosted on Imperial College London's South Kensington campus.

      The **second batch of tickets** will be released on the **10th of January at 1:30pm GMT**,
      so don't miss out! The first batch sold out in under 15 seconds. Did we
      mention all tickets are completely free?
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="http://ichack19.eventbrite.com/">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
      <link href="https://twitter.com/ichackuk">Twitter</link>
      <link href="https://ichack.org/">Website</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time
  </sign>
</email>
