<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image width="70"
           src="https://i.imgur.com/g3NqkZY.jpg"
           alt="House-shaped welcome cookies"
           title="Welcome!" />
    <hr/>

    <text>
        Welcome to the Department of Computing!

        Whether you are a fresher, wondering what this email is, or a returning
        student, this is your first weekly digest of the year! With lots of
        useful information for the upcoming year let's get right into it!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>What is DoCSoc?</heading>
    <text>
        The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc) is one the of the most
        active societies at Imperial College and is here to improve your
        student life through a range of social and academic events. Our aim is
        to bring together all students in the Computing community, as well as
        provide students with amazing opportunities from our sponsors!

        **Introducing the committee for 19/20:**
        - **President**: Kelvin Zhang
        - **Vice President**: Rayan Hatout
        - **Treasurer**: Anindita Ghosh
        - **Sponsors' Liaisons and Industrial Events Coordiators**: Clara Lebbos, Tiger Cross
        - **Academic Events Director**: Azhara Panda
        - **Social Events Director**: Chandler Low
        - **Secretary**: Radostin Petrov
        - **Events Officers**: Viet Nguyen, Iulia Ivana, Eugene Lin
        - **Postgraduate Officer**: Rachel Mekhtieva Lee
        - **Marketing &amp; Publicity Officer**: Rosemary Ng
        - **Webmaster**: George Soteriou
        - **GameDev Society Officer**: Athi Dharma

        You will also be supported by our departmental representatives (dep reps)
        who are responsible for representing the student body (you!) to the
        department.

        This year they are:

        - **Computing**: Kaplian Mnc (Academic), Dmitrii Usynin (Wellbeing) ([email](mailto:dep-rep@doc.ic.ac.uk))
        - **Joint Maths and Computing (JMC)**: Mayeul Fournial (Academic), Hannah Schlueter (Wellbeing) ([email](mailto:dep-rep@doc.ic.ac.uk))
        - **Electrical and Information Engineering (EIE)**: Naim Govani (Academic) ([email](mailto:naim.govani17@imperial.ac.uk)),
        Agrim Manchanda (Wellbeing) ([email](mailto:agrim.manchanda17@imperial.ac.uk))

        If you have any academic or wellbeing related queries, your dep reps are
        the people you can talk to.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>What do we do?</heading>

    <text>
        We at DoCSoc are very passionate about our annual events. Here's what
        to expect in 2019/2020:

        - **Bar Nights** - Our most well-known events are our bar nights, which
        occur a couple of times each term. A wonderful social atmosphere, in
        which you can mingle with your coursemates, make new friends and
        occasionally network with recruiters sponsoring our bar nights.\
        Bar nights are _free entry_ to our members and each student is given
        _free_ tokens that can be redeemed for both alcoholic and non-alcoholic
        drinks.

        - **Talks and workshops** - DoCSoc runs many engaging and interactive
        talks and workshops together with our sponsors, usually in the evenings
        after lectures. We also provide free pizza and drinks after each talk,
        so make sure to stay till the end! In the past, we've run workshops
        such as capture the flag competitions with Netcraft, an _Extreme Startup_
        event with Palantir and Bloomberg's _CodeCon_. (Do not confuse with the
        Department's ACI talks, which happen around lunchtime.)

        - **Sponsors' Exhibition** - One of our biggest events, where you can
        meet our sponsors on campus and interact with them in a friendly
        atmosphere. Check out the below section for more information about the
        event!

        - **Revel and End of Year Dinner** - The two formal events hosted by
        DoCSoc. Taking place at the end of second and third term respectively,
        both events set up a fancy theme for you to enjoy with your friends,
        and a party that you will remember long after you have graduated!

        - **IC Hack** - Imperial College's flagship hackathon is one of our
        biggest and most successful events running for the ninth consecutive
        year! For 24 hours we take over the campus to create the most amazing
        hacking atmosphere for our attendees, while running mini-events and
        workshops such as NextJump's sleeping and meditation classes, games
        rooms and our grand karaoke! Lots of coding, prizes, food and fun is
        guaranteed! Check out last year's montage [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oy6tcQY6K6Q).

        - **DoCSoc Education** - An emerging initiative from our society, the
        aim of which is to share knowledge in a practical and engaging way and
        help students polish their professional and technical skills. Over the
        past year we ran successful events such as CV workshops, Internship 101,
        Building a personal website workshop, and our very well received Python
        lecture series.

        Throughout the year we also host a wide range of social events (go-karting,
        cinema and theatre trips) and academic events. Do you have suggestions for
        events? We're always looking for feedback so feel free to email us with anything
        you have in mind!

    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>How to get involved?</heading>

    <text>
        **Membership** - All of our events are members-only and as a departmental
        society, all students studying Computing, JMC or EIE are automatically
        DoCSoc members. For those _not_ on these courses, membership can be
        purchased on the [Union website](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/activities/a-to-z/computing).

        **Volunteering** - Running and organising events of such scale wouldn't be
        possible without the help of our volunteers. We have a central
        [Facebook group](https://www.facebook.com/groups/1509850436007222/) in
        which we post for when we need volunteers. If you're looking to offer
        technical skills or manpower, or want to join our team, make sure to follow
        the group so you keep yourself up to date!

        - IC Hack - No other event can compare to the scope of IC Hack and each
        year we put in a lot of time into organising the hackathon. From navigating
        Nando's orders and keeping track of the logistics to contacting and
        interacting with sponsor companies, we have a lot of open positions that we
        need help for. If you aren't looking to compete in the hackathon, lending a
        hand is a great way to participate so make sure to keep yourself updated
        for when we seek volunteers!

        **Keeping Updated -** Our weekly digest is one of two key ways to find out about
        events. The best place to stay updated about events is via our **[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ICDocSoc/)**
        page. You can also find us on [Twitter](https://twitter.com/icdocsoc/).

        Don't forget that we run **group chats for every academic year** on Facebook
        Messenger. Other than Piazza (run by the department), Messenger is a central
        place for discussions so if you aren't part of this group chat, get in touch
        with us and we'll add you!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Welcome Fair</heading>
    <event startDate="2019-10-01T11:00:00+01:00"
           endDate="2019-10-01T16:00:00+01:00"
           location="TBD">
        <text>
            Come and visit us at our stall at the Welcome Fair to learn more
            about the society, chat with the committee and play some TBD games
            to compete for prizes! We'll be there all day so you can explore
            all of the other amazing stalls in the fair. You can find us by
            consulting the official map.
        </text>
        <links>
        <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2357470714513948/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Mums &amp; Dads Lunch</heading>
    <event startDate="2019-10-07T12:30:00+01:00"
           endDate="2019-10-07T13:30:00+01:00"
           location="Huxley 341/342">
        <text>
            As a fresher, you will have already heard of our Mums and Dads (MaD) programme.
            If you don't have parents assigned yet or haven't heard of this programme, please
            reach out to your departmental representatives above.

            We'll be kicking off the Mums and Dads programme with an opportunity for you
            to meet your MaD parents and have lunch with them! We will be offering free
            food and drinks, as well as issuing a number of challenges. You might even win
            a prize!

            Mums and Dads parent? Be sure to turn up to this event to meet your children!
        </text>
    </event>

    <heading>Intro to Linux</heading>
    <event startDate="2019-10-07T18:00:00+01:00"
           endDate="2019-10-07T19:00:00+01:00"
           location="Huxley 308">
        <text>
            Are you new to Linux and using the command line interface?
            If so, we have got you covered with this informative talk
            covering the essentials of the the Linux command line!
            Come and join us for a beginner-friendly session and start off your
            degree right!
        </text>

    </event>

    <heading>Sponsors' Exhibition</heading>
    <event startDate="2019-10-09T12:00:00+01:00"
           endDate="2019-10-09T17:30:00+01:00"
           location="Queen's Tower Room (QTR)">
        <text>
            If you're looking for an internship or a graduate role, or are just
            an industry minded individual, then come along to our Sponsors'
            Exhibition in Queen's Tower Room (Sherfield Building)! Companies
            like Facebook, Microsoft and Palantir are sending their representatives
            on our campus and they want to meet you! So prepare yourself with
            lots of questions and even more bag space for all the swag you're
            going to get!
        </text>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Facebook 12 Week and 6-Month Placements/Internships</heading>
    <sponsor company="facebook">
        Facebook's mission is to give people the power to build community and
        bring the world closer together. Through our family of apps and
        services, we're building a different kind of company that connects
        billions of people around the world, gives them ways to share what
        matters most to them, and helps bring people closer together.

        Placement/Internship applications are open and you can apply via:
        https://www.facebook.com/careers/jobs/702665046848694/

        **The deadline for 6-month placements is 25th October** and 12 week
        internship applications are on a rolling deadline.
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Microsoft Full-Time &amp; Internship Opportunities</heading>
    <sponsor company="microsoft">
        At Microsoft we are passionate about technology that empowers people
        around the world to achieve more. We are currently offering full time
        and internship opportunities to students to help us develop technology
        solutions that will have an impact on billions of people.

        Do you have a bachelor's, master's, or doctorate degree in engineering,
        computer science or related field?\
        How about a year or two of experience programming in C++, Java or other computer
        programming languages?

        If you’ve answered yes to the above and have strong technical prowess, plus
        the ability to think unconventionally to derive creative and innovative
        solutions, then we want to see your application!

        To gain real experience in software development apply [here for European roles](https://careers.microsoft.com/students/us/en/job/653461/Internship-Opportunities-in-Europe-for-Students-Multiple-Locations-Software-Engineering)
        and [here for US roles](https://careers.microsoft.com/students/us/en/job/650858/Internship-Opportunities-for-Students-Software-Engineering-Program-Management).
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Artificial Labs Spotlight Feature Articles - David King &amp; Johnny Bridges</heading>
    <sponsor company="artificiallabs">
        \
        Artificial is a start-up in the InsurTech sector.

        Our mission is to enable insurance companies to leverage innovative
        technology so they can make their customers happier, act more efficiently,
        and scale faster. We are dedicated to building the most advanced and
        flexible Machine Learning-enabled insurance platform to cater for
        insurers, brokers and underwriters of all sizes and sectors.

        This past month we have published Spotlight feature articles on both of our founders.\
        These can be found at:

        [David King](https://artificial.io/company/blog/spotlight-founder-and-cco-david-king)

        [Johnny Bridges](https://artificial.io/company/blog/spotlight-founder-and-cpo-johnny-bridges)
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>PDT Partners 6-Month Industrial Placements</heading>
    <sponsor company="pdtpartners">
        If you are a MEng Computing Student looking for a 6-month Industrial
        Placement at PDT Partners please send your CV to [imperial2020@pdtpartners.com](mailto:imperial2020@pdtpartners.com).

        “During my time at PDT not only was I able to work on interesting problems,
        but there was a full calendar of additional events, ranging from board game
        nights, darts, mini golf and an overnight treasure hunt (Midnight Madness)
        around the city. In addition to this there have been regular ‘lunch and learn’
        sessions where I have been able to learn not just about PDT but also about
        subjects such as solar energy and various charities. It is going to be a
        difficult adjustment returning to university!” _(Isaac Hutt, Industrial Placement student 2019)_.

        [PDT group at the Midnight Madness finish line.](https://i.imgur.com/szrrNgP.jpg)
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Jump Trading Intern and Graduate Positions</heading>
    <sponsor company="jump_trading">
        Jump Trading is hiring interns and grads for software and hardware development positions!

        Jump Trading is a leading algorithmic trading firm built on cutting-edge
        technology, sophisticated quantitative research, and an entrepreneurial
        culture. Founded in 1999, Jump now has 700 employees across offices in Chicago,
        New York, London, Bristol, Amsterdam, Singapore, and Shanghai.

        Jump is still privately owned and funded, fostering a culture of intellectual
        curiosity and learning. Our people are some of the world's most brilliant minds,
        with backgrounds from the trading industry, Silicon Valley tech companies and
        startups, top PhD programs and research labs.

        We have a 20-year history of investing in superior infrastructure, including
        custom hardware, low-latency software, wireless networks, and a world-class
        supercomputer.

        We’ve built custom technology to power our high-performance, distributed
        systems and to identify trends in massive data sets across global markets.

        We offer internships and grad roles in:
        - **Software Engineering (C++) --** For students interested in low-level, high
        performance C/C++ code on Linux, you like to build optimal solutions from
        scratch, and you have interests in networking, operating systems, and compilers.

        - **FPGA / Hardware Development --** For students interested in building
        next-generation, ultra-low-latency systems to power trading with machine
        learning and other algorithms on a global scale. We value a blend of hardware
        engineering experience with exceptional software development skills to add
        value to our growing team.

        - **Production Engineering --** For students who have exceptionally strong
        skills in Python, Linux, troubleshooting, networking, and creative problem
        solving. We also highly value students who love to tinker with new
        technology – many team members have been contributors to open source projects.

        - **Web Dev/UI Development --** For students interested in using advanced
        JavaScript, Python, and modern Web frameworks to  build Web-based applications
        that interact with several components of our real-time trading platform.

        Visit the job board on our website [jumptrading.com](https://jumptrading.com) and apply to “Campus”
        positions OR get in touch with Amy at [aharvey@jumptrading.com](mailto:aharvey@jumptrading.com)
        if you want to learn more!
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Oliver Wyman Introduction</heading>
    <sponsor company="oliver_wyman">
        \
        Oliver Wyman is a global management consultancy with strong relationships in
        all corners of industry, government, and non-profit organizations. Our work
        is marked by exceptional impact for our clients and we have earned a reputation
        for quality work, which is why we represent half of the top 500 global companies.
        Our company comprises a diverse mix of talented people from varied backgrounds
        and areas of expertise who marshal creative thinking and analytical rigor.

        We created our digital practice in response to the demand for fit-for-purpose
        data infrastructure and analytical capabilities in a changing world. Oliver
        Wyman Digital deliver world-class products that give our clients a competitive
        edge. We have mixed agency skills with our consulting roots in order that we
        can best answer some of the largest companies’ toughest questions. Our global
        dynamic team deliver at the highest levels across many specialist skill sets
        including Design, Data Science &amp; Analytics, Project Delivery and Engineering.
        We’re committed to growth that provides our people the most exciting and
        fulfilling opportunities and we are looking for more people to join us.

        **Meet representatives of Oliver Wyman at their presentation on Monday 7 October
        at 6.30pm in the SAF building.**
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Bank of America Discover Technology Event - 17th October</heading>
    <sponsor company="baml">
        \
        **Every day is another chance to learn.**

        Technology touches everything we do and underpins each deal we make. In fact,
        our mainframe environment is the third largest in the world. That said, we
        don’t believe that there is a tech ‘type’. You don’t need finance experience
        to join us and D&amp;I is at our core. Our Global Technology and Operations (GT&amp;O)
        division gives our business the competitive edge to solve business problems by
        delivering high quality and practical solutions. And after our training, you
        could be contributing to that.

        We know you’ll want to hear from our own Technology people. They’ll be there
        to demystify tech at an investment bank, and an interactive activity will help
        you test your skills. It’ll be followed by drinks and canapés with people from
        across our technology divisions. So share your career aspirations with them,
        and discover how we can help you find the career you want.

        Places are limited, so please register as soon as possible by clicking [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/mobile-0/brand-9/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/2/opp/4757-UK-London-Discover-Technology-Event/en-GB).

        **Get Started. Apply Now at:** [campus.bankofamerica.com](https://campus.bankofamerica.com)
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Stake Zero Ventures - Future of Blockchain Competition</heading>
    <sponsor company="stakezero">
        Sign up for this year's Future of Blockchain competition. You have 3 months
        (November to February) to enter/build a startup or answer a challenge to do
        with blockchain. Participation is digital, with a few meet-ups organised and
        online support available. There are over £100k in monetary prizes available,
        including a £20k top prize.

        **Registration closes on 1st November 2019.** Enter at [www.futureofblockchain.co.uk](https://www.futureofblockchain.co.uk).
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Gousto - Taking a Lorry off the Road with Some Code</heading>
    <sponsor company="gousto ">
        Read about how changing the way we decided what packaging to send our
        customers had a big impact on our transport footprint [here](https://medium.com/gousto-engineering-techbrunch/taking-a-lorry-off-the-road-with-some-code-a988f70b37c1).

        We have a tonne of other great posts on our Medium page here: [https://medium.com/gousto-engineering-techbrunch](https://medium.com/gousto-engineering-techbrunch).
    </sponsor>

    <hr />

    <text>
        That's all for this week! Stay tuned for the next weekly digest to keep
        yourself updated with all of the events we have planned for you.
    </text>

    <sign name="Radostin Petrov"
          role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
          facebook="radostin.petrov.99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>
</email>