<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email agenda="false" logos="false">

  <image
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dJL5aDU.png"
    title="IC Hack 19"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Congratulations on securing your tickets to **IC Hack 19 Powered by Cisco**!
    IC Hack is back bigger than ever for its eighth consecutive year,
    with IC Hack 19 taking place on **26-27th January** at the Imperial College
    London South Kensington campus with over 400 participants!

    If it's your first time at IC Hack, be sure to check out our [IC Hack 18 Montage](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hngr7ts45Dc)
    video!

    This email contains **important attendee information**, so please take your
    time to go through its contents.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## CV Upload

    With over fifteen sponsors, IC Hack 19 is a great opportunity for you to meet
    recruiters and engineers from our sponsoring companies in person.

    Our sponsors are looking to recruit from the event for various roles. To help
    participants **get the most out of IC Hack 19**, interact with our sponsors to
    the fullest and to help you build your network, we are asking everyone to
    supply their CV.

    Make sure to submit yours using [this form](https://goo.gl/forms/tqqDFvMjuYPdqhdC2) before **Friday 18th January 11:59pm**!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Ticket Cancellations

    As we have a very long waitlist, if you are unable to attend, please cancel your ticket [via Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/mytickets/)
    as soon as possible so your space can be released. If you are
    having difficulties doing so, you can email us at info@ichack.org. Please note
    that tickets are non-transferable.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## What to Bring

    On the day, be sure to have your Eventbrite ticket ready (either digital or
    printed - up to you!) and a **valid form of Government ID** (driving license
    or passport). Please note you must be **over 18** on the day of the event to attend.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    ## Equipment Requests

    We're happy to provide our attendees with hardware/equipment for their hacks
    on a best-effort basis. If you have an idea which requires additional equipment,
    please send a short proposal to info@ichack.org detailing your idea and what
    equipment you require, and we'll do our best to provide you with what you need!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know by emailing
    info@ichack.org.

    We look forward to seeing you at IC Hack 19!

    _- The IC Hack 19 team_
  </text>
</email>
