<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/R9e6434.jpg?1"
    alt="Stack of biscuits next to tea"
    title="Will anyone notice if I reuse a digest biscuit?" />

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Firstly, for those of you who have exams next week, we wish you the best of luck!

    With third and fourth year exams next week, the upcoming week will be quiet.
    However, we do have a couple announcements to make in this (shorter than usual)
    digest, so read on!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Leadership Election Results</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/q5ZQOjp.jpg" width="80" />
  <text>
    Thanks for participating in the Leadership Elections 2019! We're excited to
    announce that the DoCSoc Committee for 2019/20 is as follows:

    - **President**: Kelvin Zhang
    - **Vice President:** Rayan Hatout
    - **Treasurer:** Anindita Ghosh
    - **Secretary:** Radostin Petrov
    - **Webmaster:** George Soteriou
    - **Marketing &amp; Publicity Officer:** Rosemary Ng
    - **Academic Events Coordinator:** Azhara Assanova
    - **Industrial Events Coordinators:** Tiger Cross, Clara Lebbos
    - **Social Events Coordinator:** Chandler Low
    - **Events Officers:** Viet Nguyen, Eugene Lin, Iulia Ivana
    - **Postgraduate Officer:** Rakhilya Mekhtieva Lee
    - **Game Dev Officer:** Athithan Dharmaratnam

    Congratulations to those elected and thanks to everyone who put themselves
    forward for these positions!

    Detailed results can be found here: https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/news/leadership-elections-2019-results
  </text>

  <hr />

  <heading>DoCSoc Merch Collection</heading>
  <text>
    The long-awaited hoodies, T-shirts and beanies have arrived!

    We have already held two collection days but if you've ordered one of the
    above and have not yet collected your order, Fawaz will be in the Huxley level two
    Computing common room for you on Monday 18th March (tomorrow) from 4pm to
    7pm to collect your order.

    Additionally, if you ordered a hoodie and are **graduating this year**, please
    let us know when you come to collect your order as we have special 'Class of 2019'
    hoodies available!

    If you can't make it for these times, please let us know via email at docsoc@ic.ac.uk
    and we will try work around your availability.
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr />

  <text>
    None this week! We won't be providing any more reasons to procrastinate from
    exams!
  </text>

  <hr />

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr />

  <heading>Palantir Women in Tech Scholarship</heading>
  <sponsor company="palantir">
    We launched the Palantir Women in Technology Scholarship in 2010 to celebrate
    and support women who are beginning careers in technology. We hope to encourage
    women to pursue computer science, engineering, and technical studies, and to
    become leaders in these fields.

    This year, 10 scholarship recipients will be chosen and invited to visit our
    London office for a full-day, all-expenses paid developmental workshop.
    Programming will include professional development sessions, breakouts with
    our engineers, and some fun social activities! All recipients are awarded
    grants of £5,500 to support their education.

    The scholarship is open to students who:

    -	Are active, full-time undergraduate or Master's students enrolled in an
    accredited European college/university during the academic years that the
    scholarship is awarded, i.e., you must be enrolled in both the current
    (2018-19) and upcoming (2019-20) academic years
    -	Are majoring in or plan to major in Science, Technology, Engineering or
    Math (STEM) fields
    -	Identify as women
    -	Have not been finalists in the past

    For more information, click [here](https://jobs.lever.co/palantir/2dce1c15-faca-4e91-a8aa-0c2c6a259d77) and
    see the flyer attached!
  </sponsor>

  <hr />

  <heading>Bloomberg Women in Tech Spring Program</heading>
  <sponsor company="bloomberg">
    To celebrate International Women's Month, Bloomberg are launching the
    **Bloomberg Women in Tech Spring Program**. The 3-day program is designed to
    introduce you to our work and culture, connect you to our diverse communities
    and help prepare you for future technical interviews. The program will run
    from **April 15th - 17th at our London EMEA Headquarters**.

    Travel, food and accommodation expenses will be covered for the duration of
    the program. Successful candidates will be **fast tracked** for our 2020 Summer
    Internship Program at the end of the program.

    For more information and to apply click [here](http://tinyurl.com/y2es9ohj).
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Kelvin Zhang"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '18/19"
    facebook="KelvZhan">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
