<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Google – Build for everyone" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <text>
    We’d love to invite you to the Google Students Virtual Series, specially
    curated for tech students in EMEA (Europe, the Middle East &amp; Africa).
    Full details of the five-part series are below. Get ready to learn about
    the products we’re developing at Google, student opportunities, how to
    submit a great application and much more.

    [Please sign up here](https://events.withgoogle.com/bfe-virtual-series/) to
    take part, including a CV if you’d like to be included in our Google swag
    prize draw… we hope you’re as excited as we are!
  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>
    # Google Students Virtual Series: Build for everyone

    ### Welcome event – Build for everyone: lightning tech talks

    #### 29 September 2020, 6pm CET / GMT+2

    Tune in to hear from Google engineers who have solved challenging problems
    around making products inclusive for everyone. We’ll also give you a sneak
    peak at what’s to come and highlight our internship opportunities for tech
    students.

    ### Building your technical career &amp; CV workshop

    #### 7 October 2020, 6pm CET / GMT+2

    Google engineers talk about their paths to Google, different technical
    careers, and their top tips for making the most of your time at university.
    We’ll also be running an in-depth CV workshop to help you showcase your
    skills to recruiters.

    ### Tech talk – “Autopilot” by Google Cloud

    #### 15 October 2020, 6pm CET / GMT+2

    Based on a research paper ("Autopilot: workload autoscaling at Google")
    between Google Warsaw and the Institute of Informatics at University of
    Warsaw, a Google engineer will take you on a journey towards clairvoyant
    resource management using Machine Learning in Google’s internal cloud.

    ### Technical interview workshop &amp; demo

    #### 21 October 2020, 6pm CET / GMT+2

    You’ve landed a technical interview – what now? Two experienced
    interviewers will take you through their top tips and common pitfalls,
    before demoing a real Google interview question. Watch and ask questions,
    or even code along!

    ### Women in tech panel

    #### 5 November 2020, 12pm CET / GMT+2

    Your chance to ask a panel of Google engineers anything you like, as they
    discuss navigating a career in tech, life at Google, challenges &amp;
    successes, and some of the cool things they’ve had the chance to work on.

    ## [Register](https://events.withgoogle.com/bfe-virtual-series/)
  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>
    If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to
    emea-tech-students@google.com.

    We hope to see you there! 

    Many thanks,

    Google University Programs team
  </text>
</email>
