<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="70"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/sDUoHX0.jpg"
            alt="Oreos"
            title=""/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Hope you all have settled into second term now and are excited for what's to follow. Our second batch of IC
        Hack 20 tickets sold out this Friday in a record 15 seconds! So, congratulations to all of you who were able to
        secure a ticket, we can promise you that this year's IC Hack will be more exciting than ever!

        Our committee is working hard on IC Hack 20 and if you did not manage to get a ticket, we will be holding a
        Volunteers' Briefing for everyone wanting to participate in the biggest event on our campus! For more
        information, read on!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 Volunteers' Briefing</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/M1IMK8l.png"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-21T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-21T19:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 311">
        <text>
            Come find out about volunteering opportunities at IC Hack, so you can enjoy all the fun of the hackathon
            without the stress of hacking!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/487749155451794/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## External Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Drinks and Pizza at the Amex Office</heading>
    <image width="50" src="https://i.imgur.com/B3If7Cr.png"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-22T15:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-22T17:30:00+00:00"
            location="WeWork,
            123 Buckingham Palace Road,
            Victoria,
            London, SW1W 9SH">
        <text>
            Are you a Student looking for a fun way to spend your summer,
            gain experience and meet some fantastic people?

            Here at American Express we have a number of opportunities for
            you to come and join our teams for a 10 week Summer internship.

            We’re looking for problem solvers who can drive results through
            precise analysis and programming methodologies. Individuals with
            a strong intellectual curiosity and a passion for innovation. Team
            players who can transform their ideas into working solutions.

            To find out more we would love to invite you to come and
            connect with our graduates.

            **RSVP by 20.01.20** at ask.campus.emea@aexp.com.
        </text>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Bank of America | GIS Summer Analyst Programme - Chester</heading>
    <sponsor company="baml">
        Are you interested in a career in **cyber security**? Join our **Global Information Security** (GIS) team – a
        group of
        cyber security problem solvers thriving in an inclusive workplace. Start your career in an environment that
        creates opportunities for employees to grow, recognizes and rewards performance, and supports employees’
        all-around wellness.

        Our **Summer Analyst programme** is designed to offer you a broad and exciting experience of work as a full time
        Technology Analyst. During the summer, you will be **placed within one team** and have the opportunity to
        participate in the **real delivery** of **technology security solutions**.

        Your training and development is our top priority, with **extensive formal training** offered at the start of
        the programme in addition to on the job support, educational speaker events and mentorship throughout.

        As a Summer Analyst, you will be a member of the GIS team, providing you with the opportunity to be part of a
        world-class information security workforce. Our teams cover all aspects of Information Security including cyber
        forensics and we look forward to finding the right opportunity for you.


        **To apply for our GIS Summer Analyst Programme (Chester) please click
        [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-5/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/1/opp/4324-EMEA-Chester-Global-Technology-Summer-Analyst-Programme-Global-Information-Security/en-GB)**.

        **Application Deadline 9th February 2020**
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities Internships and Graduate Positions</heading>
    <sponsor company="citadel">
        **Citadel** is a leading investor in the world’s financial markets. For over a quarter of a
        century,
        we have sought to deliver industry-leading investment returns to clients including corporate
        pensions, endowments, foundations, public institutions, and sovereign wealth funds.

        **Citadel Securities** is an award-winning global market maker that helps meet the liquidity
        needs
        of asset managers, banks, broker-dealers, hedge funds, government agencies, and public pension
        programs.

        Applications open for both internships and graduate roles for the following positions:
        - Investment &amp; Trading
        - Quantitative Strategies
        - Software Engineering

        Apply via our websites citadel.com &amp; citadelsecurities.com
    </sponsor>

    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>

</email>