<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="StudentShapers - an Imperial Award Summer Project Opportunity"
       agenda="false">
    <text>
        Hi everyone,

        We are sharing this opportunity for those of you looking for a summer
        project and interested in working with the Imperial Award team.

        Note that the deadline to apply is **14th June by 11:59 PM** and the
        project will be done entirely remotely.

        For more information check below!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>StudentShapers Recruitment: Calling All App Developers</heading>
    <text>
        **Bursary:** £305 per week for 10 weeks (mid-July to mid-September)

        **Who should apply:** What we're looking for is up to 3 students (apply
        individually) demonstrating:
        - Technical capability to produce simple, yet functional mobile
        applications
        - Commitment and motivation to produce work to a high standard
        - Enthusiasm for the vision behind the Imperial Award scheme

        **Campus/Location:** It's an entirely remote project (you can work from
        anywhere).

        **Project details:** The Imperial Award team are starting a year-long
        project to develop and
        improve the Imperial
        Award (IA) content, interactivity and effectiveness. The focus of this
        StudentShapers project will be to develop a
        proof of concept prototype mobile application. Building a prototype will
        be a crucial step towards improving the
        technology platform used to support the Imperial Award. The data
        gathered from the development and testing of this
        prototype will provide rich insights into whatever technology platform
        is ultimately chosen.


        StudentShapers with relevant experience in developing mobile
        applications are key to the success of this project. You
        will provide both the technical ability and the student perspective
        required to develop the app. You will work in
        partnership with staff to scope the development app (choosing content
        and functionality) and will lead on the
        development of the app itself. You can expect:

        - A good balance between support and autonomy
        - A highly collaborative and enthusiastic team
        - Regular catch-ups and weekly project meetings
        - Exposure to learning and coaching design
        - To develop pair programming skills
        - To create a mobile application that you’re proud of and can show to
        prospective employers

        **How to apply:** Please complete [this online
        form](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=B3WJK4zudUWDC0-CZ8PTB-2P72eMFRNMoNHCWwiiYuJUMDhDUklCOUdPUkFMNjhFUEEyVVJSTjRRRy4u),
        outlining why you're interested in this project, any relevant experience
        and why you'd be a good candidate.

        **Deadline:** 14th June 2020 (11:59pm)

        **Contact details:** Feel free to contact us at
        [al4714@ic.ac.uk](mailto:al4714@ic.ac.uk)

    </text>

</email>