<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/pKxKShK.jpg"
    alt="Making of Christmas gingerbread cookies"
    title="We're past Halloween, it’s officialy Christmas season now" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Just to give a quick recap, last week we hosted an Escape Room Night,
    G-Research Coding Challenge and My Journey to LSEG. We hope you've enjoyed
    all of the events!

    We've got more fun and informative events for you this week, including
    Thought Machine's Breakfast Show!

    We are also looking for students who want to share their knowledge of the
    software industry for an upcoming Industry Q&amp;A - sign up below!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <heading>Want to Share What You Know About the Software Industry?</heading>
  <text>
    DoCSoc is organising some Q&amp;As about the software industry
    (internships, cvs, interviews, making yourself more employable) for 1st,
    2nd years and MSc Students. We are looking for 3-5 3rd and 4th years or PhD
    students with comprehensive experience that will answer whatever questions
    the students may have (If you are an MSc with tons of experience that's
    also completely fine!).

    Fill out the [registration
    form](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=B3WJK4zudUWDC0-CZ8PTB4BymOWFa9VFtQLZQgz9br9UNUNVWjgyRFpGS0Q0NEdIUFg5OThQNlJSRi4u)
    if you're interested.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Thought Machine: The Breakfast Show</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/8CHH569.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-05T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-05T20:00:00+00:00">
  <text>
    Join Luke and Lorenzo from Thought Machine for a crazy night of fun and
    madness. You'll be in with a chance of winning some mystery prizes - from
    the wonderful to the downright weird. You can also hear about Thought
    Machine, what it's like to work here and how we're making the world of
    banking less terrible.
  </text>
  <links>
    <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/353476822388368">Facebook</link>
  </links>
</event>

<heading>Python 101</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/scdMdeq.jpg"/>
<event startDate="2020-11-03T16:00:00+00:00"
  endDate="2020-11-03T18:00:00+00:00">
<text>
  One of the key attributes DoCSoc hosts is the Python 101 Introductory
  Workshop for not only DoC students, but all members of Imperial College
  London. We invite everyone from any disciplines and level of education.
  This will be a beginners level course for anyone who has very little to
  none knowledge in Python. Please click "Going" on Facebook so we can
  estimate the size of the interactive workshops.

  Dates: every Tuesday 4-6pm GMT from Oct 20th to Nov 24th.

  This week's lecture will be on error handling, imports, functions and
  recursion.
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/276914916715070">Facebook</link>
</links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Graphcore - Applications for our 2021 Graduate Intake are now open!</heading>
  <sponsor company="graphcore">
    As a Graduate at Graphcore, you will have the opportunity to work on
    high-profile and meaningful projects from day one. You’ll enjoy on the job
    experience as well as building your knowledge through a comprehensive and
    tailored development plan.

    We have some fantastic opportunities for graduates to join us across our
    technical teams:

    * Product Test &amp; Diagnostics - Graduate Product Test Engineer

    * Customer Engineering - Graduate Customer Software Engineer

    * Software Engineering - Graduate Software Engineer

    * Silicon Engineering - Graduate Silicon Engineer

    We recommend that you review all opportunities before submitting _one_
    application for your preferred role

    To submit your application please visit
    https://www.graphcore.ai/early-careers.

    We recommend you apply as soon as possible!

    Good Luck!

    Graphcore Early Careers Talent Acquisition Team

    ### [Apply Now](https://www.graphcore.ai/e2t/tc/VVndVg1r1HLjW4bmntf6wWz-0W6y9Q694hMDVKN5l4bj_3p_9rV1-WJV7CgNTlN2shB1y5qhPRW6nMS5y8C79k1VJ1Fbq5DBcl6W47-p-z35WLwkW68BTfW7Pl_3pMS_-FLhtYW9W5bmj4d6bpHZKW3m5JnN1RGLLCW79xzTq68SMRFW6Xhv4669833JW7fycXr67FTRmW8J4tkm5znk31VSscN-5Y_RwXW1TyPh28QHPpWW2w5PF52GpmWKW8Kwfh02WfZYXW2Pz6SF2nSc82N8bd-bmfttBdW6BS5M71FkWlhW1WBR8j8_tbfsW3xF_fR9lm2K7W6QxgHg3FLJnCW6nS6sk4CYn5fVGkv4K1-N8B1W4_LMRR3C-12YW3PXH547wSPGj34LN1)
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities - Trading Simulation Challenge</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    Join Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities for our Trading Simulation Challenge,
    where you will be able to apply your quantitative knowledge to provide an
    automated solution to the role of a quantitative trader. We'll be hosting a
    kickoff event on 5 November to meet our Traders and share pre-learning
    materials for the simulation, ahead of the challenge itself taking place on
    7 November.  Submit your applications online by simply sharing your CV
    online - deadline is 3 November; however invites will be filled on a
    rolling basis.

    Please see the attached pdf for more details.
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
</sign>
</email>
