<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="70"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/SNgkxyi.jpg"
            alt="Chocolate chip cookies with hot chocolate"
            title="Happy palindrome day!"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Hi everyone,

        With IC Hack 20 on the horizon and so many more hackathons prepared (as you will see in this digest), February
        is bound to be full of hacking! This also is a good opportunity for anybody who did not manage to secure an IC
        Hack 20 ticket to check out the other events we have prepared this month. Besides Google Hashcode, we have
        also started organisation around Ed Tech Hackday and IC HealthHack, co-hosted by Bioengineering Society, ICSM
        Coding Society and MedTech Society (tickets to be released very soon)!

        More information on that below, so let's dig in!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack Volunteers' Briefing</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/M1IMK8l.png"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-04T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-04T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 311">
        <text>
            IC Hack 20 meeting for all volunteers who will be helping during the weekend. We will be going over the
            timetable, the run of the set up and clean up. Press going if you intend to consume some complimentary 'zza!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/116414096435945/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Education: Python for Beginners</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bVYZaq8.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-06T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-06T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 340">
        <text>
            Want to know how to code but have no idea where to start?
            Tried to learn on your own but not really made any progress?

            Whether you've dabbled in programming before, or you barely know what a computer is, DoCSoc (Department of
            Computing Society) is once again running a course for you!

            After our highly successful (and award-winning!) series last year, we'll be repeating our beginners coding
            course starting Thursday, 30th January.

            This year the course is open to everyone! Just make sure to grab a ticket on Eventbrite to ensure you have
            pizza at the event! Let us know about any dietary requirements by emailing us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk.

            If you think you're not a beginner, you might be interested in our intermediate course:
            https://www.facebook.com/events/471162783560184/. This course is for people who have an understanding of
            basic programming concepts (either from Python, or other languages i.e. R, Matlab, etc), and will focus more
            on actual real-world usages of Python. If you're not sure if you fit into this category, feel free to PM us!

            Don't worry if you can't come to a few sessions, we will be posting all the material on the event page!

            Any questions at all please leave them below, and we hope to see you at the first lecture on Thursday, in
            Huxley 144.

            [**We'd also appreciate if you filled out this
            form.**](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScwCB8knQrcKfNZs7jkIRahL5muCifxJ_7Eu2CA9QxAo7HYHQ/viewform)
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/209172486886394/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/python-for-beginners-tickets-91132322229">Eventbrite</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 Powered By Cisco</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/fatHtoV.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-08T10:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-09T17:00:00+00:00"
            location="Imperial College London">
        <text>
            Kick off the new decade right.
            Are you ready for IC Hack 20?

            The largest student-run hackathon in the UK returns to Imperial College better than ever before. Running for
            its 9th consecutive year, we’re bringing over 400 of the UK's most creative and talented students together
            for 24 hours of learning, building, fun, and networking on the weekend of 8-9th February 2020. Come create
            something cool!

            IC Hack 20 will be hosted on Imperial College London's South Kensington campus. Students from all
            universities can attend!

            Twitter: twitter.com/ichackuk
            Website: ichack.org
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/415614812680196/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://twitter.com/ichackuk">Twitter</link>
            <link href="https://ichack.org">Website</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Education: Intermediate Python</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6tHNN4g.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-10T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-10T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 340">
        <text>
            For those of you who have dabbled a little bit in programming before (Python or not) and want to learn more,
            DoCSoc is holding a free, 5-week course on intermediate Python!

            We expect you to know the basics of programming already - functions, conditionals, loops, basic data
            structures and types, etc, either from Python or other languages.

            We will cover a range of topics, such as object-oriented programming, good software engineering design, as
            well as applications of Python in statistics, sciences, machine learning/data science, and building web
            applications.

            The course will focus on enabling you to understand the underlying logic and thinking process of
            programming, in order for you to become self-sufficient in your own learning and future development.

            This event will be catered, but make sure to grab a ticket on Eventbrite to secure a couple of slices for
            yourself!

            Don't worry if you can't come to a few sessions, we will be posting all the material on the event page!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/471162783560184/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/intermediate-python-tickets-91166384109">Eventbrite</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Google Hashcode Imperial College London Hub</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6rBfuEh.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-20T17:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-20T21:30:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 221, 217, 218">
        <text>
            Hash Code is a team programming competition, organized by Google, for students and professionals around the
            world. You pick your team and programming language and we pick an engineering problem for you to solve. Join
            us at the Imperial College London Hub for the Online Qualification Round. Top teams will then be invited to
            a Google office for the Final Round.

            Sign up here: https://g.co/hashcode
            Remember to sellect Imperial College London Hub after you apply

            There are only 100 slots for our hub, so make sure you sign up as soon as possible
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/216819712683436/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://codingcompetitions.withgoogle.com/hashcode/">Register</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Ed Tech Hackday</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/mAbsEAn.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-22T11:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-22T17:00:00+00:00"
            location="TBA">
        <text>
            Join DoC on Saturday 22nd February for a one day Hackathon to help design and develop to your education
            tools (Materials, eMarking and more)

            This is an excellent occasion for people interested in working on the Edtech platforms with us over the
            summer to start exploring the code and make a first contribution

            Please RSVP here: https://forms.gle/foZwZKEN6XVrNVr68

            Lunch will be provided on the day, so let us know if you plan to attend by selecting "Going" and filling in
            the form above!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/194418778361279/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdQaMWltx44IvT1WfalwPYN-u5oFRRiI9u5Q70IuuHrjftGSQ/viewform">
                RSVP
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC HealthHack 2020</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/QcuKsfS.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-29T09:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-01T17:00:00+00:00"
            location="Imperial College London">
        <text>
            The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society, ICSM Coding Society and MedTech
            Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2020!

            We are back with HealthHack 20 bigger and better than ever!
            Combining skills in bioengineering, computer science, and medicine, HealthHack will bring together talented
            students to tackle the most current medical challenges through technology.
            This year, we are focusing on Medical Education as our overarching theme.
            Over the weekend of 29th February - 1st March 2020, teams will bring their awesome ideas to life and develop
            solutions to real-life health education challenges.

            Save the date and follow the event page for more details, including sponsors and schedule announcements.

            Website: https://ichealthhack.org/

            **Ticket release dates: 5th Feb and 13th Feb**
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2630916247137813/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://ichealthhack.org/">Website</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>


</email>