<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="55"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/VsDtOCH.jpgl"
            alt="Chocolate chip cookie"
            title=""/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Hi everyone!

        Preparations for IC Hack 20 are in full speed as the first batch of tickets released this Friday sold out in
        less than 20 seconds! For those of you who did not manage to secure a ticket the **second batch of tickets**
        will be released on the **17th of January at 1:30pm GMT**!

        Although working hard on organizing IC Hack 20, we will keep organizing our social events as promised. This
        Tuesday we will be holding a Pub Quiz night with Next Jump! For more information on what's ahead, make sure to
        follow our [social media channels](https://www.facebook.com/ICDoCSoc/) and read on!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## General Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Pintos Glasses Collection</heading>
    <text>
        If you're a second year and have still not collected your Pintos glass, collections will be kept on an ad hoc
        basis rather than certain times. The easiest way to grab yours will be to contact a member of committee email us
        at docsoc@ic.ac.uk.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DSI Online Competition for Insurance Pricing</heading>
    <text>
        We at the Data Science Institute, in collaboration with the Data Science Society, have organised an online
        competition on car insurance pricing.

        You will be using real-world data, on an industry task where ML and stats are used everyday!
        The competition winner is rewarded with a £50 amazon vouchers, while runners up will receive £30 and £20 pound
        vouchers respectively.

        **How to join:**\
        Join and design your best model (Python or R) to predict which drivers are at risk of having an accident, and
        compete for profit against others in a large-scale virtual insurance market.

        The competition sign-up is open now and will remain open until the end of the competition on Sunday 12th of
        January 2020, you are free to join at any point.
        Visit http://bit.ly/pricing-game-signup-2019 to sign up, after which you will receive more information and your
        starter pack.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Pub Quiz with Next Jump</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/CjiCMmy.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-14T19:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-14T23:00:00+00:00"
            location="Metric">
        <text>
            Come for a Pub Quiz with our sponsor Next Jump!
            ---

            You must be a member of DoCSoc by Tuesday 14th January in order to be admitted. Computing, JMC, and EIE
            students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30. Strictly 18+ only - we will be checking
            IDs.

            Please send an email to us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk if you intend to bring a non-Imperial plus one. Any Imperial
            plus-ones must have purchased membership, otherwise they will be denied entry.

            Our full barnight policy is linked here: http://docsoc.co.uk/barnightpolicy

            Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1686278001524698/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 General Meeting</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/M1IMK8l.png"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-16T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-16T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 217/218">
        <text>
            Interested in organising the biggest student-run hackathon in the UK? Join us for the first General Meeting
            for the IC Hack 20 organisation committee this Thursday!

            We will be discussing progress updates from the 4 main teams - Finance, Logistics, Branding and Hacker
            Experience, as well as bringing all volunteers on track with the organisation. New to volunteering? Don't
            worry, we welcome everybody who is passionate about being part of one of the biggest event on the Imperial
            College campus! For more details check https://docsoc.co.uk/ichack20kickoffcatchup.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/487749155451794/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 - Second Ticket Batch Release</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/eky2mzj.jpg"/>
    <event startDate="2020-02-08T10:00:00+00:00"
           endDate="2020-02-09T17:00:00+00:00"
           location="Imperial College London">
        <text>
            Kick off the new decade right.
            Are you ready for IC Hack 20?

            The largest student-run hackathon in the UK returns to Imperial College better than ever before. Running for
            its
            9th consecutive year, we’re bringing over 400 of the UK's most creative and talented students together for
            24
            hours of learning, building, fun, and networking on the weekend of 8-9th February 2020. Come create
            something
            cool!

            IC Hack 20 will be hosted on Imperial College London's South Kensington campus. Students from all
            universities
            can attend!

            The **second batch of tickets** will be released on the **17th of January at 1:30pm GMT**!
            Tickets sell out in seconds, so don't miss out! Did we mention it is completely free?
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://ichack20.eventbrite.com">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/415614812680196/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://ichack.org/">Website</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Facebook – Hack-a-project 2020</heading>
    <sponsor company="facebook">
        Facebook is launching their 6th run of **Hack-a-project**! Consider it an extended hackathon
        with learning and mentoring attached to it!

        This is a programme kicking off in Feb 2020, designed for 1st years of a three year degree and
        2nd years of a fourth year degree, looking to apply for a Software Engineering internship with
        Facebook.

        Selected students will come to the Facebook office, once a week in the evening to focus on
        understanding the whole development cycle, and build a project. Each session will consist of a
        talk, and practical applications with group mentoring support. Food will also be provided!

        In addition, we will be sharing tips on “how to crush your coding interview”, and also do a mock
        interview with you, where feedback will be provided to help you improve.

        **If interested in applying please follow the link below. You only need your CV to apply. All
        applications must be made by the 17th of Jan.**


        https://hack-a-project-spring-2020.splashthat.com/

    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Palantir Women in Technology Sponsorship</heading>
    <sponsor company="palantir">
        We launched the Palantir Women in Technology Scholarship in 2010 to celebrate and support women who are
        beginning careers in technology. We hope to encourage women to pursue computer science, engineering, and
        technical studies, and to become leaders in these fields.

        This year, 10 scholarship recipients will be chosen and invited to visit our London office for a full-day,
        all-expenses paid developmental workshop. Programming will include professional development sessions, breakouts
        with our engineers, and some fun social activities! All recipients are awarded grants of £5,500 to support their
        education.

        **The Women in Technology Scholarship (Europe) is open to students who:**
        - Are active, full-time undergraduate or Master's students enrolled in an accredited European college/university
        during the academic years that the scholarship is awarded, i.e., you must be enrolled in both the current
        (2019-20) and upcoming (2020-21) academic years
        - Are majoring in or plan to major in Science, Technology, Engineering or Math (STEM) fields
        - Identify as women
        - Have not been recipients in the past

        **To apply, please submit the following:**
        - [The Women in Technology Scholarship (Europe)
        Application](https://www.palantir.com/build/files/2020_Women_in_Technology_EU.docx) (Please download, complete
        and save as a PDF file.)
        - A copy of your CV
        - A copy of your transcripts (unofficial transcripts are acceptable)

        **[Apply here!](https://jobs.lever.co/palantir/2dce1c15-faca-4e91-a8aa-0c2c6a259d77)**

        **The 2020 application period is now open. The deadline to apply is Sunday 5 April 2020 at 11:59PM PST.**
    </sponsor>

    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>
</email>