<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  title="Spark University Blockchain Hackathon and Jane Street WiTT"
  agenda="false"
  logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone,

    Hope all is well with you!

    As we are nearing the end of the year, we have some more notices from our sponsors about summer
    and autumn opportunities.\
    We will be on the lookout for any available opportunities and will update you, so stay tuned!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Spark University Blockchain Hackathon</heading>
  <sponsor company="stakezero">
    Hey Guys! This is message from StakeZero, a sponsor of DoC Soc:

    If you're interested in blockchain, we'd like to invite you to take part in the Spark University
    Blockchain hackathon. It gives students and researchers 8 weeks to build a project or answer a
    technical challenge. Registration is open now!

    There is over £25k in cash prizes. If you don’t have a team and want to be connected to
    teammates, we will help during the first workshop!

    **Find out more here https://summerspark.encode.club/**
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jane Street Women in Trading and Technology Virtual Programme</heading>
  <sponsor company="jane_street">
    \
    **For: Women in their penultimate year of study in Autumn 2020**\
    **Dates: 21st - 23rd September 2020**

    This year Jane Street will be holding their Women in Trading and Technology (WiTT) programme
    online. This three-day programme is designed for women in their penultimate year of university
    as of autumn 2020. Participants will have an exclusive opportunity to explore careers within our
    firm and attend one of two educational programmes: quantitative trading and software
    engineering.

    The quantitative trading programme focuses on mathematical and financial topics—such as
    probability, market structure, and arbitrage. Participants will learn how we approach trading
    through classroom lectures, mentorship and activities.

    The software engineering programme focuses on the fundamentals of building electronic trading
    systems, OCaml, and the library and tools we use in our everyday work at Jane Street.
    Participants will receive an in-depth look into the ways we use computer science within our firm
    and learn the fundamentals of electronic trading systems and write a program that trades on a
    simulated stock exchange.

    Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative technology, a scientific
    approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our business. Founded in 2000, Jane
    Street employs more than 1,100 people with offices in New York, London, Amsterdam, and Hong
    Kong. We are always on the lookout for great new people to join our team.

    The environment at Jane Street is open, informal, intellectual, and fun. The dress code is
    casual, the kitchen is stocked, and discussions are always lively. Teaching and learning are
    central activities through classes, mentoring, and discussion.

    **[Apply To WiTT](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-witt/)**

  </sponsor>


</email>