<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="70"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/FsIpYQL.jpg"
    alt="Chocolate cookies next to flowers"
    title="Welcome!"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome to the Department of Computing!

    Whether you are a fresher, wondering what this email is, or a returning
    student, this is your first weekly digest of the year. It has lots of
    useful information to give you a headstart in the '20/21 academic year.
    Wherever you are in the world, we are happy to welcome you to the
    Department of Computing Society.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>What is DoCSoc?</heading>
  <text>
    The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc) is one of the most active
    societies at Imperial College and is here to improve your student life
    through a range of social and academic events. Our aim is to bring together
    all students in the Computing community, as well as provide students with
    amazing opportunities from our sponsors!

    **Introducing the committee for 20/21:**
    - **President**: Rayan Hatout
    - **Vice President**: Hilliam Tung
    - **Treasurer**: Rosemary Ng
    - **Secretary**: Stefan Radziuk
    - **Academic Events Coordinator**: Philip Koo
    - **Sponsors' Liaisons and Industrial Events Coordiators**: Alexander
    Goncharov, Jack Qiu
    - **Marketing &amp; Publicity Officer**: Chloe Lau
    - **Social Events Director**: Kriti Sapra
    - **Events Officers**: Eugene Lin, Sebastian Males, Noor Sawhney, Vincent
    Wang
    - **Postgraduate Officer**: Iulia Ivana
    - **Webmaster**: Karan Obhrai
    - **Hackathons and Large Events Coordinator**: Champion Pongpaew

    There is one vacant position on the DoCSoc committee – you can now nominate
    yourself to be the next **GameDev Events Coordinator** – more details
    below.

    You will also be supported by our departmental representatives (dep reps)
    who are responsible for representing the student body (you!) to the
    department.

    This year they are:

    - **Computing** – Academic : Codrin Cotarlan
    [(email)](mailto:computing.arn@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **Computing** – Wellbeing: Arjun Banerjee
    [(email)](mailto:computing.wbrn@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **JMC** – Academic: _position vacant_
    [(email)](mailto:jmc.arn@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **JMC** – Wellbeing: _position vacant_
    [(email)](mailto:jmc.wbrn@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **EIE** – Academic: Yusuf Ismail [(email)](mailto:eie.arn@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **EIE** – Wellbeing: _position vacant_
    [(email)](mailto:eie.wbrn@imperial.ac.uk)

    If you have any academic or wellbeing related queries, your dep reps are
    the people you can talk to.

    You can now nominate yourself for one of the vacant roles in the Imperial
    College Union [Autumn Elections
    2020](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/autumn-elections-2020).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>What do we do?</heading>

  <text>
    We at DoCSoc are very passionate about our annual events. Here's what
    to expect in 2020/2021:

    - **Talks and workshops** - DoCSoc runs many engaging and interactive talks
    and workshops together with our sponsors, usually in the evenings after
    lectures. In the past, we've run workshops such as a credit card skimming
    competition with Netcraft, a Palantir Decomposition Workshop and an evening
    with the COO &amp; CIO of the London Stock Exchange Group. (Do not confuse
    with the Department's Applications of Computing in Industry talks.)

    - **Sponsors' Exhibition** - One of our biggest events, where you can meet
    our sponsors (this year virtually) and interact with them in a friendly
    atmosphere. More details coming soon!

    - **Revel and End of Year Dinner** - The two formal events hosted by
    DoCSoc. Taking place at the end of second and third term respectively, both
    events set up a fancy theme for you to enjoy with your friends, and a party
    that you will remember long after you have graduated!

    - **IC Hack** - Imperial College's flagship hackathon is one of our biggest
    and most successful events running for nine consecutive years! For 24 hours
    we take over the campus to create the most amazing hacking atmosphere for
    our attendees, while running mini-events and workshops such as NextJump's
    sleeping and meditation classes, games rooms and our grand karaoke! Lots of
    coding, prizes, food and fun is guaranteed! Check out last year's montage
    [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IeCLwKQXxX8).

    - **DoCSoc Education** - We aim to share knowledge in a practical and
    engaging way and help students polish their professional and technical
    skills. Over the past year we ran successful events such as CV workshops,
    Internship 101, Building a personal website workshop, and our very well
    received Python lecture series.

    Throughout the year we also host a wide range of social events (such as pub
    quizzes, games nights) and academic events. Do you have suggestions for
    events? We're always looking for feedback so feel free to email us with
    anything you have in mind!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>How to get involved?</heading>

  <text>
    **Membership** - All of our events are members-only and as a departmental
    society, all students studying Computing, JMC or EIE are automatically
    DoCSoc members. For those _not_ on these courses, membership can be
    purchased on the [Union
    website](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/activities/a-to-z/computing).

    **ICU Autumn Elections** - Imperial College Union Autumn Elections 2020 are
    now accepting nominations – more details on [the Union
    website](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/autumn-elections-2020).
    This election cycle you can run for the DoCSoc GameDev Events Coordinator
    role as well as for JMC and EIE department representative roles.

    **IC Hack** - No other event can compare to the scope of IC Hack and each
    year we put in a lot of time into organising the hackathon. From navigating
    Nando's orders and keeping track of the logistics to contacting and
    interacting with sponsor companies, we have a lot of open positions that we
    need help for. If you aren't looking to compete in the hackathon, lending a
    hand is a great way to participate so make sure to keep yourself updated
    for when we seek volunteers!

    **Keeping Updated** - Our weekly digest is only one of the ways you can
    find out about DoCSoc events. The best place to stay updated about events
    is via our [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ICDocSoc/) and
    [Instagram](https://instagram.com/icdocsoc) pages. You can also find us on
    [Twitter](https://twitter.com/icdocsoc/).

    Don't forget that we run **group chats for every academic year** on
    Facebook Messenger. Other than Piazza (run by the department), Messenger is
    a central place for discussions so if you aren't part of this group chat,
    get in touch with us and we'll add you!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Virtual Welcome Fair</heading>
  <event startDate="2020-10-05T10:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2020-10-11T17:00:00+01:00"
    location="Virtual">
  <text>
    This year the Imperial College Union have adapted to the current
    circumstances and are holding their Welcome Fair virtually!

    Meet all the Clubs, Societies &amp; Projects online from 5-11 October 2020.
    It's a chance to connect with your fellow students, ask any questions and
    meet some ICU partners.
  </text>
  <links>
    <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1657628761068284">Facebook</link>
    <link href="https://imperialcollegeunion.org/welcome-fair">ICU website</link>
  </links>
</event>

<hr/>

<heading>Freshers' Games Night</heading>
<event startDate="2020-10-06T18:00:00+01:00"
  endDate="2020-10-06T19:00:00+01:00"
  location="Virtual">
<text>
  Come and Join DoCSoc in the first every VIRTUAL GAMES NIGHT for FRESHERS!
  Spend some time getting to meet new people, playing fun games and having a
  relaxing evening. 🎮

  Feel free to bring along your dinner and some drinks! By attending, you will
  be entered into our prize draw for Deliveroo vouchers! 🍴🎉
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://fb.me/e/2DUmXnS9Z">Facebook</link>
</links>
</event>

<hr/>

<heading>Mums and Dads Pub Quiz</heading>
<event startDate="2020-10-12T13:00:00+01:00"
  endDate="2020-10-12T14:00:00+01:00"
  location="Virtual">
<text>
  As a fresher, you will have already heard of our Mums and Dads (MaD)
  programme.  If you haven't heard of this programme, you'll find more details
  on the [MaD website](https://mad.docsoc.co.uk/) – you can still sign up to be
  assigned a DoCSoc family!

  We'll be kicking off the Mums and Dads programme with an opportunity for you
  to meet your MaD parents and have lunch with them! We will be offering free
  food and drinks, as well as issuing a number of challenges. You might even win
  a prize!

  Mums and Dads parent? Be sure to turn up to this event to meet your children!
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://fb.me/e/3g28CjoKW">Facebook</link>
</links>
</event>

<hr/>

<text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

<hr/>

<heading>Palantir's Fall Events</heading>
<sponsor company="palantir">
  We invite you to learn more about Palantir — straight from the source.

  Government agencies, commercial institutions, and non-profit organizations
  must wrangle an ever-growing amount of data – raising important ethical
  questions for software companies like Palantir that help these institutions
  harness data to advance their missions.

  But because Palantir is not a consumer-facing company, it’s not always easy
  to understand what we build and how our products are used. Here’s your chance
  to learn more directly from our software engineers. Engineers will share how
  their focus has shifted completely in the last 6 months to help in the fight
  against COVID-19 on a variety of different fronts. We’ll be sharing demos of
  our products and answering questions about Palantir and our engineering
  roles.

  Use the password ```20HobbitFallEMEA``` to register [here](https://fall2020eventsemea.splashthat.com/).
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>Microsoft Software Engineering roles</heading>
<sponsor company="microsoft">
  Microsoft is now accepting applications for their full time and intern
  software engineering roles.

  [Full Time Opportunities for Software
  Engineers](https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/878016/Full-Time-Opportunities-for-Students-and-Recent-Graduates-UK-Software-Engineering)

  [Internship Opportunities for Software
  Engineers](https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/878093/Intern-Opportunities-for-Students-UK-Software-Engineering)
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>Join Two Sigma</heading>
<sponsor company="twosigma">
  We’re looking for people who seebeauty in data—and the possibilities it
  reveals: Modelers who see connections in unexpected places. Engineers who can
  harness technology to channel massive amounts of data into powerful tools.
  And people across multiple disciplines to support it all.

  We are hiring for recent graduate and internship positions in London. Learn
  more at [twosigma.com/careers](twosigma.com/careers)
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>IMC Careers in Trading and Technology</heading>
<sponsor company="imc">
  IMC is a leading global market maker, using algorithmic trading and advanced
  technology to buy and sell securities on multiple trading venues worldwide.

  We put you in the center of the brightest minds in the trading world. You
  will be challenged to think globally, commit locally, problem-solve
  methodically and give back generously.
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>Netcraft opportunities</heading>
<sponsor company="netcraft">
  Netcraft is a world-leading internet security services company with offices
  in Bath and London. We conduct internet research and provide a range of
  security services, including cybercrime disruption, application security
  testing and automated penetration testing.

  Check out our recruitment booklet to find out about available
  roles: https://www.netcraft.com/NetcraftRecruitmentBooklet.pdf

  If you decide you’re interested in working with us, just send your CV to
  cv@netcraft.com.
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>Optiver opportunities</heading>
<sponsor company="optiver">
  Optiver is constantly on the lookout for top talent to join our team of
  engineers. As a leading global market maker driven by technology - we provide
  liquidity to financial markets using our own capital at our own risk. To do
  this we pioneer our own trading strategies and systems using clean code and
  sophisticated technology to trade a wide range of products.

  Our high performance, low-latency trading systems and algorithms are
  constantly evolving. We care about clean, pragmatic code and we strive to
  break complex problems down into simple solutions.

  OUR GRADUATE OPPORTUNITIES

  Would you like to work in a highly-skilled, passionate and driven environment
  where there is a high degree of freedom, responsibility and reward? If so, we
  have exciting opportunities awaiting you here at Optiver. These include the
  chance to start your career with us in a full-time role or gain an extended
  glimpse into Optiver and experience Technology here for yourself via our 8
  weeks Summer Internship programme.

  SOFTWARE ENGINEER SUMMER INTERNSHIP- AMSTERDAM

  If you plan to graduate in 2022, you can apply to be part of our summer
  internship where you will be responsible for your own project from day one,
  guided along the way by a senior developer assigned as your mentor interact
  closely with traders, researchers and fellow engineers, directly impacting
  the end-results of the company Join several lectures about trading and other
  departments to get a full understanding of our business.

  Have a look at this video to get a glimpse of the Optiver internship
  experience and a virtual tour of our Amsterdam office.

  GRADUATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER-AMSTERDAM

  You will be responsible for the full stack of applications and the full
  development cycle, granting a lot of ownership. From day one you will handle
  large sets of real-time data that require high performing and easily scalable
  systems. Our Tech Starters programme will help you develop

  your technical skills and enhance your knowledge on our business. You will be
  guided by a senior developer assigned as your mentor. For this role we are
  recruiting on a rolling basis, and we have a flexible start date.

  TO JOIN US IN TECH YOU HAVE:

  • An academic degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Information Systems or
  equivalent

  • Experience with programming in C++, C# or Java

  • An entrepreneurial attitude

  • Strong communication skills

  • The ability and desire to write simple and clean code

  • The ability to be a team player who enjoys creative freedom and
  independence

  Check our career page for Software Engineer Summer internship and fulltime
  graduate opportunities in our Amsterdam office! For any question feel free to
  reach out to Serena Riccomagno at serenariccomagno@optiver.com
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<text>
  That's all for this week! Stay tuned for the next weekly digest to keep
  yourself updated with all of the events we have planned for you.
</text>

<sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
  role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
  linkedin="stefanradziuk">
  Until next time,
    </sign>
</email>
