<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="80"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/3JyUS51.jpg"
            alt="A mixture of biscuits in a plate"
            title="If I could get all biscuits from the digests this year in here, I would!"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Hi everyone,

        We hope all of you are well and safe. This week we hosted our last workshops and events for the term. Overall, a
        very eventful three months, we organised some of the biggest and most successful editions of our flagship events
        like IC Hack 20 and Roaring Revel!

        We also elected our new committee this past week! We congratulate the new position-holders and are looking
        forward to their step in for the next academic year!

        As next week gives the start of the exam period for everybody, this digest will be short. But we still want to
        wish you all good luck in taking your exams and give you some final announcements for this term.\
        So for the last time in a while, let's dig into the digest!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Leadership Election Results</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/20evoQL.png"/>
    <text>
        Thanks to everyone who voted in the Leadership Elections 2020! We're excited to
        announce that the DoCSoc Committee for 2019/20 is as follows:
        - **President**: Rayan Hatout
        - **Vice President:** Hilliam Tung
        - **Treasurer:** Rosemary Ng
        - **Secretary:** Stefan Radziuk
        - **Webmaster:** Karan Obhrai
        - **Marketing &amp; Publicity Officer:** Chloe Lau
        - **Sponsor Liaisons and Industrial Events Coordinators:** Alexander Goncharov, Jackson Qiu
        - **Social Events Coordinator:** Kriti Sapra
        - **Events Officers:** Noor Sawhney, Vincent Wong
        - **Postgraduate and Alumni Officer:** Iulia Ivana
        - **Hackathons &amp; Large Events Coordinator:** Champion Pongpaew

        Congratulations to those elected and thanks to everyone who put themselves
        forward for these positions!

        Detailed results can be found here: https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/news/leadership-elections-2020-results

        The following roles will opened for Summer By-Elections: **Academic Events Coordinator, GameDev Events
        Coordinator, Events Officer**.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Merch on Sale Now!</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/d34WXUe.png"/>
    <text>
        DoCSoc merch on sale now!

        [**Click here to purchase your DoCSoc branded hoodies and cardholders
        from
        the Union
        Store!**](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/club-society-project-products/computing-products)

        The collection period will be in the summer term. We will also hold
        multiple collection sessions to accommodate for students on placement.
        Keep an eye on the Union Store, as there might be more merch going on
        sale soon! 👀
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>TheDataOpen - Citadel Spring Datathon</heading>
    <sponsor company="citadel">
        **Explore. Build. Win.**

        The Data Open brings together the best minds
        in mathematics, engineering, science, and
        technology to collaborate and compete using
        the world’s most important data sets.

        [Sign Up Now - Limited spots available!](http://thedataopen.com/)

        You can win $25000 in cash prizes and the winning team gains an
        automatic entry into the final
        Data Open competition.

        _Check out the attached PDF for more information._
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>WiTT at Jane Street</heading>
    <sponsor company="jane_street">
        \
        **We are excited to host our sixth year of WiTT at Jane Street!
        Will you be there?**

        Women in Trading and Technology (WiTT) is a three-day programme designed
        for women in their
        penultimate year of university as of autumn 2020. Participants will have
        an exclusive
        opportunity to explore careers within our firm and attend one of two
        educational programmes:
        quantitative trading and software engineering.

        Both programmes feature interactive classes and activities during the
        day, and evening social
        events to speak with Jane Street employees and other women attending the
        event in a more casual
        setting.

        The quantitative trading programme focuses on mathematical and financial
        topics—such as
        probability, market structure, and arbitrage—through a combination of
        short classroom lectures,
        group games, and mock trading sessions. There is a curriculum of core
        subjects with flexibility
        to explore alternative areas of interest, and plenty of opportunities
        for close interaction with
        our traders.

        The software engineering programme focuses on the fundamentals of
        building electronic trading
        systems, OCaml, and the library and tools we use in our everyday work at
        Jane Street.
        Participants will put these tools to use by writing the back end and UI
        for a computer game,
        along with a program that trades on a simulated stock exchange. These
        activities involve a
        combination of classroom lectures, group games and exercises, and
        one-on-one mentorship.

        Selected students will arrive in London on the evening of Sunday, 20
        September and will depart
        the evening of Wednesday, 23 September. Jane Street will provide all
        travel to and from London,
        accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food
        and drinks throughout
        the event.

        Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative
        technology, a scientific
        approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our business.
        Founded in 2000, Jane
        Street employs more than 1,100 people with offices in New York, London,
        Amsterdam, and Hong
        Kong. We are always on the lookout for great new people to join our
        team.

        The environment at Jane Street is open, informal, intellectual, and fun.
        The dress code is
        casual, the kitchen is stocked, and discussions are always lively.
        Teaching and learning are
        central activities through classes, mentoring, and discussion.

        Selected students will arrive in London on the evening of Sunday, 20
        September and will depart
        the evening of Wednesday, 23 September. Jane Street will provide all
        travel to and from London,
        accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food
        and drinks throughout
        the event.

        **Apply here: https://janestreet.com/apply-witt**

        **Who: Women in their second year of study in Autumn 2020\
        When: 20th - 23rd September 2020\
        Deadline to apply: Sunday, 5th July 2020 at 11.59pm BST**
    </sponsor>

    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>


</email>