<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            alt="Stack of digestives"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/JqBty0t.jpg"
            title="Did you know: The term 'Digest' comes from the word 'Digestives' relating to the biscuits we put at the at start of every email!"
            width="80"/>

    <text>
        Hi everyone,

        After a long weekend of co-running IC HealthHack 2020, we are saying
        farewell to our Hackathon February. We hope everyone who attended
        HealthHack
        (and all other hackathons we ran this month) enjoyed themselves and
        hopefully learned something useful and practical.

        Speaking of learning, we are in the final weeks of our Python and
        Raspberry
        Pi workshops. Certainly a successful term for DoCSoc Education, we hope
        that
        you found the courses useful (and we would love to hear feedback!).

        Next week, we will be holding Revel - our annual black-tie event! One
        last
        party before we all settle down into the exam season, Revel will not
        disappoint, being held in Quaglino's this year and also featuring the
        popular DJ Antics! Prepare your fancy outfits and bring your party
        attitude
        this Monday!

        More notices to follow below!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## General Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>The Hello World Hack: Looking for volunteers!</heading>
    <text>
        Want to improve your leadership and communication skills by helping to
        run
        coding activities and talks that will inspire the next generation of
        young
        women?

        Hello World Hack is a hackathon hosted by Imperial’s Computing and Maths
        Departments that aims to introduce girls in Years 3 to 5 (ages 7-10) to
        computer science and show them what can be achieved by learning to code!

        We’re looking for female volunteers from any STEM discipline to help
        host
        this EXCITING and INTERACTIVE event on Tuesday 24th March 2020

        **If you would like to get involved or find out more, please email Dr
        Jackie
        Bell (Jaclyn.bell@imperial.ac.uk) by 5pm on Thursday 12th March 2020**

        _See attached PDF for more information._
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Roaring Revel</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hlkVgkp.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-02T19:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-03T01:00:00+00:00"
            location="Quaglino's
                      16 Bury Street
                      London, SW1Y 6AJ">
        <text>
            **This event is for 18+ only.**

            A little party never killed nobody, so join RCSU and DoCSoc for an
            extravagant night of glitz, glam and a
            party fit for the 20's - here's to Roaring Revel!

            From Spanish rooftop bars to Parisian themed halls, we're now taking
            you back in time to the Prohibition
            era. Our chosen gin mill, Quaglino's, is decorated to the taste of
            the period and has a history as rich as
            the location of St James's.

            The evening will start with a cocktail reception with further drinks
            served later as the night progresses.
            We will also be serving canapés and providing entertainment
            throughout the evening. So wear your ritziest
            garms and get ready to party like it's the 20's!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2205576013084814/">
                Facebook
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>


    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc goes to Ballie Ballerson</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/V81LGZ2.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-04T18:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-04T21:30:00+00:00"
            location="53-54 Berwick St,
     London,
     W1F 8SP">
        <text>
            Take a break from all the deadlines and revision and come have some
            fun with DoCSoc at Ballie Ballerson
            Soho!!

            DoCSoc will be heavily subsidising tickets to just £6.00! We only
            have a limited number of tickets for this
            event, so make sure to try and get one.

            Each ticket include a welcome prosecco drink, a cocktail, a whole
            pizza and 3 hours access to the ball pits
            at Ballie Ballerson Soho! We will meet outside the venue at 6:30.

            We hope to see you there!

            --------------------------------------------------------------
            You must be a member of DoCSoc by Tuesday 25th November in order to
            be admitted. Computing, JMC, and EIE
            students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30.

            Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/282553589377804/">
                Facebook
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc: Meet the Candidates!</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/GakkYTh.png"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-05T13:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-05T14:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 311">
        <text>
            Committee nominations have closed on Friday 28th February and now
            it's time to Meet the Candidates!

            Join us in Huxley 311 from 1pm on Thursday 5th March to meet the
            candidates running for all of the positions in DoCSoc.

            This is your chance to ask any questions you may have, and hear more
            about what each candidate is campaigning for! Candidates for DoCSoc
            and Dep Reps will all be present.

            Candidates for contested positions: Please turn up and prepare a 1
            minute speech on why you think you'd be good for the position. After
            each pitch, up to 2 questions will be asked from the audience.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/625014798334906/">
                Facebook
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Women in Gaming Panel</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/ciyfOQu.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-10T18:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-10T19:30:00+00:00"
            location="Blackett LT 1">

        <text>
            We would like to invite you to the women in gaming panel, where we
            will try to increase the visibility and representation of women in
            gaming.

            The panel will be an hour long, including a 10-15 min Q&amp;A with
            the
            panelists, followed by an informal networking session with a catered
            reception.

            The panel will take place on Tuesday 10th March at 6:30pm in
            Blackett LT1, located on Imperial's South Kensington Campus.

            This event is part of Women's History Month at Imperial College
            London and is open to everyone! Just make sure to grab a ticket on
            Eventbrite to ensure you have food at the event! Let us know about
            any dietary requirements by emailing us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/520737038579661/">
                Facebook
            </link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/women-in-gaming-panel-tickets-96475766615/">
                Eventbrite
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>International Women's Day Conference 2020</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/jUs6CvK.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-11T12:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-11T18:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 308">
        <text>
            In honour of International Women’s Day, WiC are excited to announce
            a half-day conference at Imperial College London on the 11th of
            March. Join us to hear from STEM leaders across industry and
            academia about their career journeys followed by a panel on how
            discrimination can be tackled to make the tech industry a more
            welcoming place for minorities.
            Open to all!
            Graduate students are also invited to a CV+Interview lunchtime
            workshop run by Faculty.ai in room 218. Workshop is aimed at those
            preparing the transition from academia to industry and/or
            consulting.

            Confirmed speakers:
            Katerina Daminova, Business Strategy at Yobota
            Professor Nigar Hashimzade, Director of Research, Department of
            Economics and Finance, Brunel
            Professor Julie McCann, Head of Adaptive Emergent Systems
            Engineering (AESE) group, Imperial
            Becky Plummer, Team Leader, Software Infrastructure, Bloomberg
            Sepi Chakaveh, CEO/Founder of Pixsellar
            Christina Franzeskides, COO of Comind
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/195198955050488/">
                Facebook
            </link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/iwdc2020-in-conversation-with-tech-leaders-in-academia-and-industry-tickets-96877941531/">
                Eventbrite
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>TheDataOpen - Citadel Spring Datathon</heading>
    <sponsor company="citadel">
        **Explore. Build. Win.**

        The Data Open brings together the best minds
        in mathematics, engineering, science, and
        technology to collaborate and compete using
        the world’s most important data sets.

        [Sign Up Now - Limited spots available!](http://thedataopen.com/)

        You can win $25000 in cash prizes and the winning team gains an
        automatic entry into the final
        Data Open competition.

        _Check out the attached PDF for more information._
    </sponsor>

    <hr/>

    <heading>WiTT at Jane Street</heading>
    <sponsor company="jane_street">
        \
        **We are excited to host our sixth year of WiTT at Jane Street!
        Will you be there?**

        Women in Trading and Technology (WiTT) is a three-day programme designed
        for women in their
        penultimate year of university as of autumn 2020. Participants will have
        an exclusive
        opportunity to explore careers within our firm and attend one of two
        educational programmes:
        quantitative trading and software engineering.

        Both programmes feature interactive classes and activities during the
        day, and evening social
        events to speak with Jane Street employees and other women attending the
        event in a more casual
        setting.

        The quantitative trading programme focuses on mathematical and financial
        topics—such as
        probability, market structure, and arbitrage—through a combination of
        short classroom lectures,
        group games, and mock trading sessions. There is a curriculum of core
        subjects with flexibility
        to explore alternative areas of interest, and plenty of opportunities
        for close interaction with
        our traders.

        The software engineering programme focuses on the fundamentals of
        building electronic trading
        systems, OCaml, and the library and tools we use in our everyday work at
        Jane Street.
        Participants will put these tools to use by writing the back end and UI
        for a computer game,
        along with a program that trades on a simulated stock exchange. These
        activities involve a
        combination of classroom lectures, group games and exercises, and
        one-on-one mentorship.

        Selected students will arrive in London on the evening of Sunday, 20
        September and will depart
        the evening of Wednesday, 23 September. Jane Street will provide all
        travel to and from London,
        accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food
        and drinks throughout
        the event.

        Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative
        technology, a scientific
        approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our business.
        Founded in 2000, Jane
        Street employs more than 1,100 people with offices in New York, London,
        Amsterdam, and Hong
        Kong. We are always on the lookout for great new people to join our
        team.

        The environment at Jane Street is open, informal, intellectual, and fun.
        The dress code is
        casual, the kitchen is stocked, and discussions are always lively.
        Teaching and learning are
        central activities through classes, mentoring, and discussion.

        Selected students will arrive in London on the evening of Sunday, 20
        September and will depart
        the evening of Wednesday, 23 September. Jane Street will provide all
        travel to and from London,
        accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food
        and drinks throughout
        the event.

        **Apply here: https://janestreet.com/apply-witt**

        **Who: Women in their second year of study in Autumn 2020\
        When: 20th - 23rd September 2020\
        Deadline to apply: Sunday, 5th July 2020 at 11.59pm BST**
    </sponsor>
    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>
</email>