<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
        title="Final Reading Group this FRIDAY - An Introduction to WebAssembly (WASM)"
        agenda="false"
        logos="false">
    <text>
        Hey everyone,

        After a very successful year of holding Reading Groups, time has come
        for the final one, carried out by Philippa Gardner and Conrad Watt. The
        topic will be "An Introduction to WebAssembly" and we kindly invite you
        to **Huxley 218 this Friday at 1PM**.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Reading Group by Philippa Gardner and Conrad Watt</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1pBf70A.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-06T13:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-06T14:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 218">
        <text>
            An Introduction to WebAssembly

            WebAssembly (Wasm) is a stack-based, statically typed byte code
            language. It is the first new language to be natively supported on
            the Web in nearly 25 years, following JavaScript. Interestingly, the
            Wasm standard is written as a small-step operational semantics
            (remember your Models of Computation course!) with changes and
            extensions only permitted if they are formalised. Two of the key
            people formalising the Wasm standard are Andreas Rossberg, one of
            the originators of Wasm, and Conrad Watt, a current PhD student at
            Cambridge and a former Imperial student, who has done a mechanised
            specification of Wasm in Isabelle/HOL.

            For this Reading Group, please read the main paper on Wasm:
            https://bit.ly/2PERozu

            Bringing the Web up to Speed with WebAssembly, PLDI’17, written by
            people at Google (including Rossberg, now at DFINITY), Mozilla,
            Microsoft and Apple.

            We will give the historical context of the paper, lead a discussion
            on Wasm, and describe current and possible future roles of formal
            (even mechanised) specification of language standards.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/550401265593745/">
                Facebook
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>
</email>