<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/4sMRQML.png"
    alt="Cookies at the Southbank Food Market"
    title="Cookies at the Southbank Food Market" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We hope you enjoyed last week's Sponsors Exhibition! It was great seeing
    over 500 of you there, thank you to everyone who came!

    We have more events with our sponsors coming up, including DIY takedowns
    with Netcraft, Next Jump Olympics and C++ optimisation with Optiver!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Netcraft - Do It Yourself Takedowns for Fun &amp; Profit</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/VIZerge.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-10-22T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2020-10-22T19:00:00+01:00">
  <text>
    Netcraft will be running an interactive online workshop on Zoom. Places are
    limited so make sure you register
    [here](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd48Cie0pAWXmDm8pprk4POcmV4r9T7b7CWCjrbWaNpOZf4yQ/viewform?usp=sf_link).

    Netcraft takes down around 80 types of cybercrime for many of the world's largest companies.

    In order to carry out these takedowns, we rely on someone, somewhere, doing
    the right thing. And we hope that by contacting as many relevant people as
    possible we will find that person and thereby curtail the attack.

    In the vast majority of cases, this works. Netcraft has used this paradigm
    to successfully complete well over a million takedowns against cybercrime
    such as phishing, malicious JavaScript, advance fee frauds and conventional
    Windows malware infrastructure.

    In some cases, however, all of the relevant entities are criminals: the
    site owner, the domain registrar, the hosting provider, and the DNS
    provider.

    ### So, who do you trust when everyone’s a crook?

    Rationally, you would trust only yourself. Instead of asking others for
    assistance you would look carefully at the attack to see what opportunities
    there might be to stop it. If you don’t believe others will do it for you,
    you do it yourself.

    Some kinds of criminal tools, such as web shells, phishing kits and fake
    shops, have kill switches as part and parcel of their functionality, and
    these can be invoked. Then, like bona fide software developers, criminal
    developers make mistakes. Our analysis of fake shop and phishing kits
    uncovers unintentional functionality that provides the opportunity to stop
    the attack by making use of bugs and vulnerabilities. Finally, there is no
    honour amongst thieves. Criminal software developers frequently create
    backdoors in their code, so that they can steal credentials stolen by their
    customers. These back doors can be used too.

    By employing HTTP requests which make use of these vulnerabilities, one can
    seize the opportunity to immediately halt an attack, recover credentials,
    and eliminate the criminal’s infrastructure.

    Your challenge, after a short talk illustrating the concepts, is to compete
    against your peers to research vulnerabilities in authentic criminal
    software tools and kits, and then take down as much criminal-controlled
    infrastructure as possible in the time available.

    The team with the largest number of takedowns is the winner.

    ### Do not try this at home against the live Internet

    Within the UK, the Computer Misuse Act 1990 constrains the opportunity to
    act on these vulnerabilities, and legislates against activities which may
    be characterised as “hack back” or vigilante in nature.
  </text>
  <links>
    <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2316367721842288/">Facebook</link>
    <link href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd48Cie0pAWXmDm8pprk4POcmV4r9T7b7CWCjrbWaNpOZf4yQ/viewform?usp=sf_link">
      Sign up form
    </link>
  </links>
</event>

<hr/>


<heading>Optiver Tech Talk - Low Latency C++ Workshop</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/NdFA4lk.png"/>
<event startDate="2020-10-20T18:00:00+01:00"
  endDate="2020-10-20T21:00:00+01:00">
<text>
  Do you want to learn how to write the fastest and best performing code
  possible from a leading global electronic market maker? Are you ready to
  dive into assembly, cache internals and squeeze the last nanosecond out
  of your code? If so, then join our low-latency workshop on code
  optimisation!

  During this workshop one of our engineers will demonstrate some of the
  profiling and micro-benchmarking techniques used when developing
  low-latency code. Through concrete code examples, we will share some of
  the performance tips and tricks attained from our vast experience in
  writing fast, maintainable and modern C++ code. We will look into
  assembly generated by the compiler to understand how seemingly small code
  changes affect the work a processor needs to do.

  Whether you write games, mobile applications or trading software, these
  techniques will help you to write faster and more efficient code!

  _Please note this webinar is suited for students with at least some
  pre-existing C++ knowledge_

  Zoom Link:
  https://optiver-ams.zoom.us/j/99684948167?pwd=bFRhMUcvNm14TURXUXRqcHNkT0NtZz09

  Meeting ID: ```996 8494 8167```

  Password: ```VV*J08Yi```
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1057480651354737">Facebook</link>
  <link href="https://optiver-ams.zoom.us/j/99684948167?pwd=bFRhMUcvNm14TURXUXRqcHNkT0NtZz09">Zoom</link>
</links>
</event>

<hr/>

<heading>Python 101</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/scdMdeq.jpg"/>
<event startDate="2020-10-20T16:00:00+01:00"
  endDate="2020-10-20T18:00:00+01:00">
<text>
  One of the key attributes DoCSoc hosts is the Python 101 Introductory
  Workshop for not only DoC students, but all members of Imperial College
  London. We invite everyone from any disciplines and level of education.
  This will be a beginners level course for anyone who has very little to
  none knowledge in Python. Please click "Going" on Facebook so we can
  estimate the size of the interactive workshops.

  Dates: every Tuesday 4-6pm GMT from Oct 20th to Nov 24th

  Syllabus:

  * Oct 20th - Introduction, variables, user I/O

  * Oct 27th - Control Flow (if statements, for and while loops), lists and
  list comprehension

  * Nov 3rd - Error Handling, Imports, Functions, Recursion (?)

  * Nov 10th - Advanced control flow (break, continue, pass), Data Structures
  (Tuple, Dictionary, Set), Plotting data w/matplotlib

  * Nov 17th - Assert, Classes with OOP, Lambdas

  * Nov 24th - (extra session) Q&amp;A, Fundamentals of CS (theoretical, more for
  1st year Computing)
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/276914916715070">Facebook</link>
</links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Next Jump Olympics</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/O3kPkwm.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-10-21T18:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2020-10-21T21:00:00+01:00">
  <text>
    Join us for a night of fun and game on the inaugural Next Jump x DoCSoc
    Olympics.

    Team up with your friends and course mates (up to 6 per team) to challenge
    yourself to 3 + 1 rounds of brain-teasing and creativity-requiring
    challenges. Winning at the end of the event will get £20 Amazon voucher
    each and a chance to join one of our Community Online Academies to learn
    from by world-class trainers and thought leaders.

    You can expect:

    * Pub Quiz Challenge
    * Pictionary
    * Treasure Hunt
    * Mystery Head-to-Head round

    Don’t worry if you have not had a team yet as we can team you up at the
    event too. It is a perfect way to get to know others in the course and
    socialise with them too.
  </text>
  <links>
    <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/263482351651310">Facebook</link>
  </links>
</event>

<hr/>

<text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

<hr/>

<heading>#NextJumpLogoChallege</heading>
<sponsor company="next_jump">
  ![Kriti's submission](https://i.imgur.com/XH8tRsV.png)

  ### @cookiesandcode\_ wins \#NextJumpLogoChallenge!

  Next Jump is proud to announce the winner of our Logo Challenge 2020 is
  Kriti with her innovative use of carrots to match our logo's orange colour.
  Kriti will receive a brand new Polaroid OneStep 2 camera as a prize for
  hercreativity. Don't miss out on our future events and competitions like
  this in the next few weeks.

  Just in case you missed the Sponsor's Exhibition that happened this week,
  we want to let you know that we are hiring! We offer internships,
  placements, and full-time positions as a Software Engineer in Web
  Development. Apply to us by **23rd October** to be fast-tracked to our phone
  interviews.

  Software Engineers:
  https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/UWulrrsRCG/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications?source=icl-mail-blast

  Business Associates:
  https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/WIEYayG7YQ/Business-Associate?source=icl-mail-blast
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>
  Bank of America - GIS Summer Analyst Programme - Camberley and Chester
</heading>
<sponsor company="baml">
  Are you interested in a career in cyber security? Join our Global
  Information Security (GIS) team – a group of cyber security problem solvers
  thriving in an inclusive workplace. Start your career in an environment
  that creates opportunities for employees to grow, recognizes and rewards
  performance, and supports employees’ all-around wellness.

  Our Summer Analyst programme is designed to offer you a broad and exciting
  experience of work as a full time Technology Analyst. During the summer,
  you will be placed within one team and have the opportunity to participate
  in the real delivery of technology security solutions.

  Your training and development is our top priority, with extensive formal
  training offered at the start of the program in addition to on the job
  support, educational speaker events and mentorship throughout.

  As a Summer Analyst, you will be a member of the GIS team, providing you
  with the opportunity to be part of a world-class information security
  workforce. Our teams cover all aspects of Information Security including
  cyber forensics and we look forward to finding the right opportunity for
  you.

  ### Meet the GIS Graduates:

  ![Guneet Sawhney](https://i.imgur.com/BqTWH5W.jpg)

  **Guneet Sawhney**

  Technology Analyst

  **What is your current role?**

  I am working in Cyber Security Technology on a tool that manages and
  organises application access across the bank.

  **University, degree name and internship**

  BSc Computer Science and Mathematics,
  University of Edinburgh

  I interned in Chester at Bank of America in 2019. I was working in Global
  Information Security, on an identity access management project, allowing me
  to apply both my technical and mathematical skills from University.

  **What did you enjoy most about the internship?**

  The internship provided an insight into the working world, it presented the
  opportunity to understand how a business operates and how you can contribute
  to the growth and change of the company.

  The highlight of my internship was the strong intern community that was
  formed; coming back to the bank knowing some familiar faces really helped me
  to settle in.

  **What was working life like in your internship?**

  The bank provided a lot of support and were always encouraging of us to
  network and learn. There were also many opportunities to volunteer and
  partake in cultural events.

  Interning in Chester was an enjoyable experience, it gave me some insight on
  how I wanted to navigate my career after University.

  ![Jared Skivington](https://i.imgur.com/qV6xexN.jpg)

  **Jared Skivington**

  Cyber Threat Intelligence Analyst

  **What is your current role?**

  Cyber Threat Intelligence Analyst – gathering and analysing information about
  the current threat landscape.

  **University, degree name and internship**

  BSc Computer Science, University of Warwick

  **What did you enjoy most about the internship?**

  I enjoyed being able to meet and work alongside a variety of teams with
  vastly different skillsets, giving me a much greater understanding of the
  security profession and potential career options.

  **What was working life like in your internship?**

  Work life was well balanced between tasks that felt integral to the business
  and projects that allowed me to explore personal areas of interest. The
  culture was very welcoming, making me feel confident about asking for help
  and always receiving that support when it was needed. The culture was also
  incredibly friendly, which helped me to settle in quickly.

  ### To apply for our GIS Summer Analyst Programme (Camberley and Chester) please click [here](https://campus.bankofamerica.com/careers/global_technology_summer_analyst_program_EMEA.html)

  **Application Deadline 6th November 2020**
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>Shape Your World with Bank of America</heading>
<sponsor company="baml">
  ### Meet the Technology Teams

  Technology touches everything we do and underpins
  each deal we make. In fact, our mainframe environment
  is the third largest in the world. That said, we
  don’t believe that there is a tech ‘type’. You don’t
  need finance experience to join us and D&amp;I is at
  our core. Our Global Technology and Operations
  (GT&amp;O) division gives our business the
  competitive edge to solve business problems by
  delivering high quality and practical solutions.

  Join our Meet the Technology Teams session to speak
  directly to members of our Imperial Tech School Team.
  The event will provide an open forum where you will
  have the opportunity to ask questions on a range of
  topics including careers in Global Technology, how to
  apply and general working life at Bank of America.
  Please come prepared with your questions to be
  addressed at this session.

  Register your interest
  [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/lang-en-GB/candidate/postings/5855)!

  **Let’s shape the world together**

  **Date**: 21st October, 2020

  **Time**: 14:00 – 15:00 (GMT+1)
</sponsor>

<sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
  role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
  linkedin="stefanradziuk">
  Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
