<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email agenda="false" logos="false">

    <image
            src="https://i.imgur.com/fatHtoV.jpg"
            title="IC Hack 20 is only three days away!"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        **IC Hack 20 Powered by Cisco** is only a few days away! We hope you are just as excited as we are because this
        year
        IC Hack is bigger than ever!

        This email contains some **key information** for you to go through before arriving on our campus on Saturday,
        so make sure to read through it carefully!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        ## Join Our Slack!

        Join our Slack team using [this
        link](https://join.slack.com/t/ichack20/shared_invite/enQtOTIyNDc0MjY4Mjc3LTkxZGI5ZjljYTUxZmQwOGI0ODQzZDg3MWU1NDcwNjEzYzEwMTNiMjNhZGNkYTc3M2JjODNmNDA0M2NmMDBiMWI).
        We use the Slack team to **make important announcements** (on the *#announcements* channel)
        and you can use the team to talk to organisers, sponsors and fellow hackers. We also maintain a
        *#team-forming* channel for those of you searching for teammates.

        Keep an eye on our sponsor (*#sp-[sponsor]*) channels to find out more about them and take
        part in their challenges.
        Make sure you **join the team before the weekend** so you don't miss any important
        information.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        ## What to Bring

        On the day, be sure to have your Eventbrite ticket ready (you can find a link to download your tickets at the end
        of the email) and a valid
        form of Government ID (driving license or passport). Please note **you must be over 18** on the day of the event
        to attend.

        Also don't forget to bring chargers for your devices (including your phone and
        laptop) to keep them powered on overnight. Bringing some warm clothes is also encouraged, as it gets chilly
        overnight!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        ## Ticket Cancellations

        If you find you are unable to attend, we kindly ask you to cancel your ticket [via
        Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/mytickets/) or by emailing us
        as soon as possible so your space can be released. Please note that tickets are **non-transferable**.
    </text>


    <hr/>

    <text>
        ## Getting There

        IC Hack is hosted at **Imperial College South Kensington Campus**. The registration
        will take place at the **main entrance** on Exhibition Road, SW7 2BX. The best way
        to reach the venue is via tube to South Kensington Station (District, Circle and
        Piccadilly lines), then either walking up the subway (exiting at the end of the
        subway and turning left) or up Exhibition Road.

        Alternatively, you can take buses **9, 23, 52, 70, 452**, which stop opposite the
        Royal Albert Hall. The Imperial College main entrance is then a short, five-minute
        walk south from there. There are limited car parking spaces nearby, so we
        recommend using public transport.

        **Registration starts from 10:00am**. Please **do not be late** as the Opening Ceremony
        starts at 10:45am! (Don't forget a form of ID!)

        Below is a [map of the campus](https://i.imgur.com/DUNIT32.png) and of all the rooms where IC Hack will be
        hosted. A physical copy of this will be inside the lanyard booklet given to you at the event.
    </text>

    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/DUNIT32.png"
           width="80"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        ## 2019-nCov Guidance

        We would like to reassure all attendees that we have worked with the College extensively to ensure that those
        are attending are safe in all aspects. As part of this, we are monitoring the coronavirus outbreak and attendees
        should feel reassured that the risk to individuals in the UK is low.

        However, following College restrictions and Public Health England advice, those who have returned from Wuhan or
        Hubei Province in the last 14 days are asked to stay home and not to attend the event. Please contact us if you
        are in this situation and we will work with you to mediate this. There are no other advisories in place at the
        time of writing. Further information can be found on the [Imperial College
        website](http://www.imperial.ac.uk/alerts/).

        As an overnight hackathon in a closed environment, we do ask that attendees maintain a high standard of hygiene
        and to stay home if you are feeling unwell regardless of this outbreak. For further queries about this, please
        don't hesitate to email us.
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Finally, make sure to check out our website at ichack.org. There you can find the full schedule for the event
        as well as links to our [Twitter](https://twitter.com/ICHackUK) and
        [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/events/415614812680196/) pages.

        If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know by emailing
        ichack@ic.ac.uk.

        We look forward to seeing you at IC Hack 20!

        _- The IC Hack 20 team_
    </text>

</email>