<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="80"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/b1XOyFL.jpg"
            alt="A plate of fortune cookies"
            title="Happy Lunar New Year!"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Hi everyone!

        As our committee is working hard to organise IC Hack 20, we hope all of you are excited for the long-awaited
        hackathon! If you did not manage to secure a ticket for IC Hack 20 but want to part of the experience, becoming
        a volunteer is always an option! You will not only be part of the magic on the day of IC Hack, but will also be
        a contributor to the largest student-run hackathon in the UK!

        Over the next few weeks, we'll be also be starting our *free* Python workshops, both for beginners and
        intermediates (open to non-members too), as well as our Google Hash Code Hub. Read on for more details!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## General Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc EGM - Social Events Coordinator By-Elections</heading>
    <text>
        By-Elections for the Social Events Coordinator positions will take place on **Tuesday 28th January from 6:05pm
        in Huxley 311.** Voting will be done by paper ballot and the evening will being straight with voting, followed
        by announcement of results.\
        Requirements are as follows:
        - Only DoCSoc members may vote.
        - **Please bring your college ID card** or a reasonable form of identification where you can be verified as a
        DoCSoc member.
        - Arrive promptly as voting can close as early as 6:20pm. It only takes a few minutes to vote.


        **For candidates and manifestos, refer to the email sent earlier this week.**
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Imperial College Speakers Open House</heading>
    <text>
        Imperial College Speakers Club is a student-led organisation based at Imperial College London that helps people
        of all ages and backgrounds improve their public speaking skills.

        If you are interested in developing your public speaking skills, IC Speakers Club will be holding an Chinese New
        Year Open House event on **Thursday January 30th at 6:15 pm at room 121 of the Sir Alexander Fleming Building**.
        This even is open to students from other universities as well as the general public.

        RSVP here: https://www.eventbrite.com/e/year-of-the-rat-toastmasters-open-house-tickets-91179467241

        For more information check out the [Facebook Event](https://www.facebook.com/events/201095877599790/).
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 General Meeting</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/M1IMK8l.png"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-27T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-27T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 217/218">
        <text>
            Interested in organising the biggest student-run hackathon in the UK? Join us for our General Meeting for
            the IC Hack 20 organisation committee this Monday!

            We will be discussing progress updates from the 4 main teams - Finance, Logistics, Branding and Hacker
            Experience, as well as bringing all volunteers on track with the organisation. New to volunteering? Don't
            worry, we welcome everybody who is passionate about being part of one of the biggest event on the Imperial
            College campus! For more details check https://docsoc.co.uk/ichack20kickoffcatchup.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/597032490872421/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Education: Python for Beginners</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/bVYZaq8.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-30T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-30T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 144">
        <text>
            Want to know how to code but have no idea where to start?
            Tried to learn on your own but not really made any progress?

            Whether you've dabbled in programming before, or you barely know what a computer is, DoCSoc (Department of
            Computing Society) is once again running a course for you!

            After our highly successful (and award-winning!) series last year, we'll be repeating our beginners coding
            course starting Thursday, 30th January.

            This year the course is open to everyone! Just make sure to grab a ticket on Eventbrite to ensure you have
            pizza at the event! Let us know about any dietary requirements by emailing us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk.

            If you think you're not a beginner, you might be interested in our intermediate course:
            https://www.facebook.com/events/471162783560184/. This course is for people who have an understanding of
            basic programming concepts (either from Python, or other languages i.e. R, Matlab, etc), and will focus more
            on actual real-world usages of Python. If you're not sure if you fit into this category, feel free to PM us!

            Don't worry if you can't come to a few sessions, we will be posting all the material on the event page!

            Any questions at all please leave them below, and we hope to see you at the first lecture on Thursday, in
            Huxley 144.

            [**We'd also appreciate if you filled out this
            form.**](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScwCB8knQrcKfNZs7jkIRahL5muCifxJ_7Eu2CA9QxAo7HYHQ/viewform)
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/209172486886394/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/python-for-beginners-tickets-91132322229">Eventbrite</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Education: Intermediate Python</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6tHNN4g.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-10T18:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-10T20:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 340">
        <text>
            For those of you who have dabbled a little bit in programming before (Python or not) and want to learn more,
            DoCSoc is holding a free, 5-week course on intermediate Python!

            We expect you to know the basics of programming already - functions, conditionals, loops, basic data
            structures and types, etc, either from Python or other languages.

            We will cover a range of topics, such as object-oriented programming, good software engineering design, as
            well as applications of Python in statistics, sciences, machine learning/data science, and building web
            applications.

            The course will focus on enabling you to understand the underlying logic and thinking process of
            programming, in order for you to become self-sufficient in your own learning and future development.

            This event will be catered, but make sure to grab a ticket on Eventbrite to secure a couple of slices for
            yourself!

            Don't worry if you can't come to a few sessions, we will be posting all the material on the event page!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/471162783560184/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/intermediate-python-tickets-91166384109">Eventbrite</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Google Hashcode Imperial College London Hub</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6rBfuEh.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-20T17:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-20T21:30:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 221, 217, 218">
        <text>
            Hash Code is a team programming competition, organized by Google, for students and professionals around the
            world. You pick your team and programming language and we pick an engineering problem for you to solve. Join
            us at the Imperial College London Hub for the Online Qualification Round. Top teams will then be invited to
            a Google office for the Final Round.

            Sign up here: https://g.co/hashcode
            Remember to sellect Imperial College London Hub after you apply

            There are only 100 slots for our hub, so make sure you sign up as soon as possible
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/216819712683436/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://codingcompetitions.withgoogle.com/hashcode/">Register</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>


</email>