<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Getting to Grips with Golang" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <text>
    ![Poster](https://i.imgur.com/BQ8VlbY.png)

    ### Are you new to Golang?

    Learn how to use Golang w/ Next Jump and have a chat with our team
    afterwards!

    As a company, we were an early adopter of Go and have stuck with it ever
    since. So we’d like to show you why we love using it so much and give you
    an intro into how you can use it too!

    We’d love to bring some of that Golang fun to Imperial DocSoc. It will be
    an awesome evening for Go coding and a chance to get to know us!

    Make the most of it by downloading Go beforehand from
    https://golang.org/.  You can then code along during the event.

    We’re really excited to meet all of you, so we hope to see you there!

    Join via Zoom: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/88093284203
  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>
    ### Who is Next Jump?

    Next Jump is a global tech company with an award-winning culture. We help
    to transform companies from all sectors (Finance, Tech, Military) to
    build high performing teams; and our E-commerce platform is used by 70%
    of the Fortune 1000 (including Facebook, Bloomberg and the BBC) making
    $2B in sales a year. Over the last 12 months, our core and social
    businesses have been growing rapidly. We are looking for developers who
    want to design, build and market amazing mobile apps and web platforms -
    built with React Native, Go, PHP, Vue.js, AWS and more - to our 3 million
    UK customers from their first day on the job.

    The deadline for our applications is by midnight Sunday, 22nd November -
    catch our interest and we’ll chat to you, send you a coding test and
    invite you to our Super Saturday assessment day at the end of the year.

    We are looking to fill the vacancies in our Intern Class 2021 as well as
    Graduate Class 2021.

    ### Apply Now!

    If you are looking for a ‘not-your-typical graduate job/internship’, then
    Next Jump’s the place for you! http://nxj.me/imperialjobs
  </text>
</email>
