<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/Gv1H80S.jpg"
    alt="Biscuit dipped in milk"
    title="Drowning"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    With only four weeks left until the end of the term, we're hoping you've
    enjoyed last week's Golang and quantum computing talks.

    This week, you'll have the opportunity to meet Arrival - a London-based
    electric vehicle startup and hear from DoC Alumni in Industry!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Arrival - Who?</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9fZzXmm.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-25T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-25T19:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Discover the product portfolio of LinkedIn's Hottest Startup of 2020.
      Learn about Arrival’s innovative approach to the design and assembly of
      electric vehicles and explore their unique culture and job opportunities.

      Join Zoom Meeting
      https://zoom.us/j/92289229602?pwd=Nzl4RlhpZ1h0QVdrTTQzOFIvTzJyUT09

      Meeting ID: `922 8922 9602`

      Passcode: `1UizEc`
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://fb.me/e/QnU1ssOO">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://zoom.us/j/92289229602?pwd=Nzl4RlhpZ1h0QVdrTTQzOFIvTzJyUT09">Zoom</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>CGCA x DoCSoc: Alumni in Industry Panel</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/5rC5ycp.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-26T18:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-26T19:30:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Interested in knowing more about our Alumni in Industry?

      Join DoCSoc and CGCA for our DoC Alumni in Industry Panel, where we
      invite some of our alumni to talk about their experiences since they
      recieved their shiny degree certificates.

      We will be revealing one panellist each day leading up to the event, so
      make sure to click "Interested" or "Going" to see our updates!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://fb.me/e/16ILPzFeT">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Python 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/scdMdeq.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-24T16:30:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-24T18:30:00+00:00">
    <text>
      One of the key attributes DoCSoc hosts is the Python 101 Introductory
      Workshop for not only DoC students, but all members of Imperial College
      London. We invite everyone from any disciplines and level of education.
      This will be a beginners level course for anyone who has very little to
      none knowledge in Python. Please click "Going" on Facebook so we can
      estimate the size of the interactive workshops.

      **This week's lecture will begin at 4:30 PM, half an hour later than usual.**
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/276914916715070">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Bank of America | Technology Summer Analyst (Chief Technology Organization) | Chester</heading>
  <sponsor company="baml">
    ![Header](https://i.imgur.com/83w6jjy.png)

    ### Shape your world with Bank of America.

    #### Technology Summer Analyst (Chief Technology Organization) | Chester

    Our Summer Analyst program is designed to offer you a broad and exciting
    experience of work as a full time CTO Analyst. During the summer you will
    be placed within one team and have the opportunity to participate in real
    delivery of technology solutions.

    Your training and development is our top priority with extensive formal
    training offered at the start of the program in addition to on the job
    support, educational speaker events and mentorship throughout.

    As a Summer Analyst, your key tasks and responsibilities may include but
    are not limited to:

    * Design infrastructure used by multiple lines of business, handling
    billion dollars of transactions per day

    * Take responsibility for deploying and supporting core infrastructure that
    underpins the daily operations of the entire bank

    * Support the design and implementation of our next generation data-centres

    * Develop mobile solutions to enable our employees to work effectively in
    geographically diverse locations

    * Be responsible for global incident management and event management
    processes

    * Work with various platform teams and Business Technology Groups to help
    build out automated processes

    * Have exposure to the business management functions

    [Apply
    now!](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-0/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/1/opp/6073-EMEA-Chester-Global-Technology-Summer-Analyst-Programme-Technology-Infrastructure/en-GB)

    **Application Closing Date**: 29th November, 2020
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading></heading>
  <sponsor company="jane_street">
    ![Header](https://i.imgur.com/A4arfkF.png)

    This January, we are excited to host our fourth Jane Street Symposium.
    We're inviting current and recent PhD students to spend two days learning
    about the rich set of problems we face as a quantitative trading firm and
    how we apply mathematical and computational techniques to solve them. The
    program will consist of lectures by Jane Street researchers, short talks by
    the symposium attendees, and an interactive workshop. Due to the COVID-19
    pandemic, the program will be remote this year.

    Applications will close on **December 1st at 11:59pm ET**.

    If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to email
    symposium@janestreet.com.

    ## [APPLY](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-symposium/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=symposium2021&amp;utm_term=symposium&amp;utm_content=registration)

    #### About Jane Street

    [Jane Street](https://www.janestreet.com/) is a research and
    technology-based quantitative trading firm with over 1000 employees and
    offices in New York, London, Hong Kong, and Amsterdam. We employ
    mathematicians and scientists from top academic programs to create models
    that allow us to trade billions of dollars around the world every day.
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
</sign>
</email>
