<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/YkYegdq.jpg"
    alt="Chocolate chip cookie on a blue plate"
    title="Chocolate chip cookie on a blue plate" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We hope you're ready for a week full of events!

    Coming up we have a Meet Your Family Week, events with DRW and Nvidia, a
    workshop with CrowdStrike, as well as a Software Industry Q&amp;A and a
    DoCSoc Games' Night!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Meet Your Family Week</heading>
  <text>
    With lockdown just having begun in England, we realise it is more important
    than ever to stay connected to one another. That is why we have made this
    week Meet Your Family Week! We encourage you to meet up with your DoCSoc
    families and do an activity together such as play Among Us, virtual dinner
    and drinks, play an escape room, or something completely different! If your
    family still has not reached out to you, please email us and we will try
    reallocate some parents and children.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Sponsors' Portal</heading>
  <text>
    Searching for internships or placements? Check out our Sponsors Portal,
    where you can find out more details about our sponsors, read their blog
    posts and see their open internship/placement positions. You can also
    upload your CV and directly apply to our Gold and Silver tier sponsors!

    You can access the portal at: https://portal.docsoc.co.uk/
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DRW - Who We Are?</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/htkmpKf.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-09T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-09T19:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Join DRW as the head of their London office, Neil Dunn, will come in to
      discuss how traders, software developers and researchers interact with
      one another and what their day-to-day looks like. We’ll also have a
      recruiter there to discuss the interview process.

      DRW is a diversified trading firm with decades of experience bringing
      sophisticated technology and exceptional people together to operate in
      markets around the world and across many asset classes. We value autonomy
      and the ability to quickly pivot to capture opportunities, and so we
      operate using our own capital and trading at our own risk. Headquartered
      in Chicago with offices in the U.S. and Canada as well as Europe and
      Asia, we trade all the things you’d expect from a leading firm, including
      Fixed Income, Equities, FX, Commodities and Energy. We also have
      leveraged our expertise and technology to expand into three
      non-traditional strategies: real estate, venture capital and
      cryptoassets.

      Phone one-tap:
      US: +13126266799,,97938614413#,,1#,691795# or +16465588656,,97938614413#,,1#,691795#

      Meeting URL: https://drw.zoom.us/j/97938614413?pwd=SGNwQkIwS1R5RnFqbm5nckRvMkNNQT09

      Meeting ID: `979 3861 4413`

      Password: `691795`
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/994825404333234/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://drw.zoom.us/j/97938614413?pwd=SGNwQkIwS1R5RnFqbm5nckRvMkNNQT09">Zoom</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>CrowdStrike: Help! My University Has Been Hacked!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/qxb0BwX.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-11T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-11T19:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Where did the hacker go? He must have RAN SOMEWHERE

      Mission: Can you defend Imperial College London and its COVID-19 Vaccine
      Top Secret Information or will it be stolen by the Bad Guys?

      What’s Involved: Take part in a tabletop challenge with CrowdStrike experts
      to see if you can save your university from the eventuality of being
      hacked! With the guidance of our team, we’ll take you through a real-life
      scenario and help lead an investigation to see if you can save the day and
      restore Imperial College London back to a safe state of play.

      Logistics: This workshop will run for 1hr 30 minutes. Each student will be
      split into teams of 3-4 and entered into breakout rooms to discuss
      plausible solutions, to the attack that is underway. You’ll then in return
      hear from our experts to help pave the way for what we do next. We hope you
      find a solution so your university isn’t left to ransom! Prizes will be
      given to the best and most unique suggestions for saving your university!
      We look forward to seeing you!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1158706514547871/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Software Industry Q&amp;A - Internships, CVs and the Pandemic</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/4pJn2CD.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-11T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-11T14:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Do you want to know about internships, how they changed during the
      pandemic &amp; how to put up a stunning CV? Join us in this live Q&amp;A
      Session about the Software Industry!

      We have already prepared some standard pre-recorded material to bring you
      up to speed here: https://tinyurl.com/DoCSocIndustry101

      However, for any other questions you may have, we will bring together a
      group of students ready to answer whatever questions you might have about
      the industry!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1261929284172897">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Games' Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/nbT8O7b.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-12T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-12T20:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Come and Join DoCSoc in the first ever VIRTUAL GAMES NIGHT for EVERYONE!
      Spend some time getting to meet new people, playing fun games and having
      a relaxing evening. 🎮

      Feel free to bring along your dinner and some drinks! By attending, you
      will be entered into our prize draw for Deliveroo vouchers! 🍴🎉

      Join our discord server here to participate on the day:
      https://discord.gg/hc24ud6
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/394419125266076">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://discord.gg/hc24ud6">Discord</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Accelerating Scientific Discovery in Health &amp; Life Sciences</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/BVL0wj8.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-10T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-10T19:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      In this talk Jonny Hancox, Senior Data Scientist from Nvidia’s Healthcare
      team, will showcase the many tools and techniques that can be used to
      reduce the time it takes to move from ideation to insight. Much of this
      acceleration comes from the developments in hardware, but also the
      algorithmic developments that these hardware innovations have unlocked.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/960675894341472/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/accelerating-scientific-discovery-in-health-life-sciences-tickets-128048114357">Eventbrite</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Python 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/scdMdeq.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2020-11-10T16:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-11-10T18:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      One of the key attributes DoCSoc hosts is the Python 101 Introductory
      Workshop for not only DoC students, but all members of Imperial College
      London. We invite everyone from any disciplines and level of education.
      This will be a beginners level course for anyone who has very little to
      none knowledge in Python. Please click "Going" on Facebook so we can
      estimate the size of the interactive workshops.

      Dates: every Tuesday 4-6pm GMT from Oct 20th to Nov 24th.

      This week's lecture will cover advanced control flow, data structures and
      plotting data with matplotlib.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/276914923381736">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
</sign>
</email>
