<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="DoCSoc Mums and Dads - Parents Sign Up Now Open!" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <text>
    It's that time of the year again - DoC is about to be joined by a new
    cohort of first years!
      &lt;br/&gt;
    Hence, the Mums and Dads 2020/21 parent applications are now open!

    If you're unfamiliar with the Mums and Dads scheme, every year DoCSoc
    members can become the "adoptive parents" of up to five freshers and
    form a family. It is not only a great way to welcome freshers and help
    them settle into university life, but for everyone involved to make
    some friends and enjoy some events together. Each family will get a
    termly budget that they can decide how to spend themselves.

    **You can sign up as a parent [here](https://mad.docsoc.co.uk/parent)!**

    Do not hesitate and sign up soon - the number of parents who can sign up is
    limited and the assignments will be made on a first-come, first-served basis.

  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>
    FAQ:

    **How does it all work?**
      &lt;br/&gt;
    Parents are existing 2nd, 3rd, and 4th year Computing and JMC students in
    DoC. Each family will consist of two parents and up to five freshers.  This
    year, due to the unusual circumstances, family activities in the Autumn
    term will be held remotely. There will be a range of opportunities for you
    to bond with your family, starting with a virtual pub quiz. Each term there
    is also a small budget for each family (around 20 pounds) to use as
    appropriate.

    **Can I sign up as a solo parent?**
      &lt;br/&gt;
    No, unfortunately, you can't. You will need to sign up with a partner -
    this is done to ensure the best possible experience for incoming
    freshers. If you sign up without choosing a partner, your registration
    will be ignored.

    **How will freshers be allocated?**
      &lt;br/&gt;
    Based on the interests filled in, we do our best to assign each fresher
    to fellow freshers and parents with similar interests. If you're
    interested to find out more, the source code of this application is
    available on [GitHub](https://github.com/docsocsf/mad2).

    If you have any other questions, please feel free to message us on
    [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ICDoCSoc),
    [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/icdocsoc/) or [send us an
    email](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk)!
  </text>
</email>
