<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

  <image
    width="80"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/TE1451i.jpg?1"
    alt="Macaroons"
    title="Today was sunny although a bit windy!"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>

    Last week of February is here! We had a quite eventful week full of Python and Raspberry Pi
    workshops alongside our Committee Elections talk, HashCode Hub, and Valentine's bar night all
    taking place last Thursday! We have more events in the coming weeks, as next week IC HealthHack
    and Revel (two of our biggest events) will take place. There are also **a number of Revel
    tickets
    still up for grabs**, but more on this and other news in this digest!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Leadership Elections Nominations close this Friday!</heading>
  <text>
    Leadership Elections 2020 are just around the corner and nominations for all positions,
    including DoCSoc committee roles close this **Friday 28th February at 12:00PM**.

    We have written a **detailed blog post** which includes the responsibilities for
    every role and other information you should know when running for a committee position.
    If you are looking to run for a DoCSoc committee position, we strongly recommend
    you read this.

    Read the blog post here: https://docsoc.co.uk/articles/2020-02-19-election-positions/

    If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk
    or get in touch with a current committee member!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Raspberry Pi Workshops</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/97B3YPK.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2020-02-25T13:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-02-25T14:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      Have you ever wanted to know more about a Raspberry Pi? Or are you a first year Computing
      student whose
      summer project will closely involve the Raspberry Pi? Then come join us at our new 4-week
      Raspberry Pi
      course where you will get to learn what this small computer is capable of!

      We will introduce the Pi, its architecture and do multiple demos for VNC Connections, Python +
      Assembly
      programming and coding a tiny bootloader!

      These workshops are open to everyone!
      Make sure to grab your Eventbrite ticket to get free pizza!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1442439432589537/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/raspberry-pi-workshops-tickets-91677775695">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Human Centred Design for Early Stage Start Ups</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/9YLZ8OS.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2020-02-25T18:15:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-02-25T19:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 311">
    <text>
      Human Centred Design is an essential product design methodology driving innovation in software
      companies including start-ups.

      Come join us in this talk where will see how Human Centred Design methods are used to develop
      new product innovations with a case study of Samsung Electronics Product Innovation Team.

      This talk will be given by Lucas Braunschvig, an Imperial Alumni who has worked as a
      Innovation Manager at Samsung Electronics for over four years and has recently founded an
      early stage start-up called Stroll Hunt.

      Lucas will also give a talk about how he used Lean Start-up methods to validate his accidental
      start-up idea: The case study of Strollhunt.

      This talk is open to everyone! Just make sure to grab a ticket on Eventbrite to ensure you
      have pizza at the event! Let us know about any dietary requirements by emailing us at
      docsoc@ic.ac.uk.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2680575425355259/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/human-centred-design-for-early-stage-start-ups-tickets-95454185037">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC HealthHack 2020</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/QcuKsfS.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2020-02-29T09:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-03-01T17:00:00+00:00"
    location="Imperial College London">
    <text>
      The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society, ICSM Coding Society and
      MedTech
      Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2020!

      We are back with HealthHack 20 bigger and better than ever!
      Combining skills in bioengineering, computer science, and medicine, HealthHack will bring
      together talented
      students to tackle the most current medical challenges through technology.
      This year, we are focusing on Medical Education as our overarching theme.
      Over the weekend of 29th February - 1st March 2020, teams will bring their awesome ideas to
      life and develop
      solutions to real-life health education challenges.

      Save the date and follow the event page for more details, including sponsors and schedule
      announcements.

      Website: https://ichealthhack.org/
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2630916247137813/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://ichealthhack.org/">Website</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Roaring Revel: Limited Number of Tickets Left!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hlkVgkp.jpg"/>
  <event
    startDate="2020-03-02T19:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-03-03T01:00:00+00:00"
    location="Quaglino's
                      16 Bury Street
                      London, SW1Y 6AJ">
    <text>
      We hope you are ready for this year's edition of our glamorous black-tie event Roaring
      Revel! We had a great demand for tickets with our first batch selling out in less than 15
      seconds! If you did not manage to secure a ticket, we are delighted to announce a **final
      batch
      of limited tickets for DoCSoc members at £28**.

      To grab yours go to:
      https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/roaring-revel-docsoc-tickets-92928960021 and once you've
      registered with Eventbrite navigate to the [Union website to purchase the
      tickets](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/club-society-project-products/computing-products/30339/revel-late-release-ticket).

      Note that you may purchase a +1 ticket for anyone for any Imperial or non-Imperial student
      (except RCSU members must buy RCSU tickets and DoCSoc members must buy DoCSoc tickets), but
      tickets are limited to two per member. These last few tickets are limited, so make sure to
      secure them soon!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2205576013084814/">Facebook</link>
      <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/roaring-revel-docsoc-tickets-92928960021">
        Eventbrite
      </link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>International Women's Day Conference</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/5HuoxdH.png"/>
  <event
    startDate="2020-03-11T12:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2020-03-11T18:00:00+00:00"
    location="Huxley 308">
    <text>
      In honour of International Women’s Day, WiC will be celebrating by hosting a half-day
      conference at Imperial College London on the 11th of March. Join us to hear from STEM leaders
      across industry and academia about their career journeys followed by a panel on how
      discrimination can be tackled to make the tech industry a more welcoming place for minorities.

      PhDs+Postdocs are also invited to a CV+Interview lunchtime workshop run by Faculty.ai in room
      218. Workshop is aimed at those preparing the transition post-PhD to industry and/or
      consulting.


      Agenda:
      - 12:00-13:15 CV+Interview lunchtime workshop in Huxley 218 (PhDs and Postdocs only, lunch
      provided)
      - 13:15-15:30 Speakers from academia, industry and consulting in Huxley LT 308 (with
      tea/coffee
      break)
      - 15:30 - 16:45 Panel discussion on Positive Discrimination for Equality in STEM in Huxley LT
      308
      - 16:45 - 18:00 Drinks+canapes

      Confirmed speakers:
      - Julie McCann, Professor of Computer Systems, Imperial College London
      - Katerina Daminova, Strategy at Yobota

      More speakers TBA


      **If you plan on attending, please sign up here: https://forms.gle/y9ACTxTpRX6YiYKs8**

      All genders welcome!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://forms.gle/y9ACTxTpRX6YiYKs8">RSVP</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Next Jump is hiring – Deadline this SUNDAY!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/BjhQGZD.png"/>
  <sponsor company="next_jump">
    \
    **Next Jump is hiring – Deadline this SUNDAY!**

    5 Fun facts about Next Jump:
    - Our technology impacts 10 million users everyday
    - 70% of the Fortune 1000 companies use our technology
    - We record $3 billion in sales every single year
    - Our Intern Class 2019 worked on core infrastructure of our hugely-popular Cinema App
    - All our full-time employees travel to America twice a year for parties

    **Who are we?**\
    You might have known us from ICHack, Breakfast or Bar Night, Next Jump is a global tech company
    with an award-winning culture. We help to transform companies from all sectors (Finance, Tech,
    Military) to build high performing teams; and our E-commerce platform is used by 70% of the
    Fortune 1000 (including Facebook, Bloomberg and the BBC) making $2B in sales a year. Over the
    last 12 months, our core and social businesses have been growing rapidly. We are looking for
    developers who want to design, build and market amazing mobile apps and web platforms - built
    with React Native, Go, PHP, Vue.js, AWS and more - to our 3 million UK customers from their
    first day on the job.

    The deadline for our Spring Super Saturday is **Sunday, 23rd February** - catch our interest and
    we'll chat to you, send you a coding test and invite you to our Super Saturday assessment day on
    the 29th Feb 2020.

    We are looking to fill the vacancies in our Intern Class 2020 as well as Graduate Class 2020.

    **Apply Now!**

    If you are looking for a 'not-your-typical graduate job/internship', then Next Jump's the place
    for you!
    - Graduate Class 2020:
    https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/UWulrrsRCG/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications?source=Imperial+Blast
    - Intern Class 2020:
    https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/wYfZzpCivx/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications-Internship?source=Imperial+Blast
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>TheDataOpen - Citadel Spring Datathon</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    **Explore. Build. Win.**

    The Data Open brings together the best minds
    in mathematics, engineering, science, and
    technology to collaborate and compete using
    the world’s most important data sets.

    [Sign Up Now - Limited spots available!](http://thedataopen.com/)

    You can win $25000 in cash prizes and the winning team gains an automatic entry into the final
    Data Open competition.

    _Check out the attached PDF for more information._
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities Internships and Graduate Positions</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    **Citadel** is a leading investor in the world’s financial markets. For over a quarter of a
    century,
    we have sought to deliver industry-leading investment returns to clients including corporate
    pensions, endowments, foundations, public institutions, and sovereign wealth funds.

    **Citadel Securities** is an award-winning global market maker that helps meet the liquidity
    needs
    of asset managers, banks, broker-dealers, hedge funds, government agencies, and public pension
    programs.

    Applications open for both internships and graduate roles for the following positions:
    - Investment &amp; Trading
    - Quantitative Strategies
    - Software Engineering

    Apply via our websites citadel.com &amp; citadelsecurities.com
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>WiTT at Jane Street</heading>
  <sponsor company="jane_street">
    \
    **We are excited to host our sixth year of WiTT at Jane Street!
    Will you be there?**

    Women in Trading and Technology (WiTT) is a three-day programme designed for women in their
    penultimate year of university as of autumn 2020. Participants will have an exclusive
    opportunity to explore careers within our firm and attend one of two educational programmes:
    quantitative trading and software engineering.

    Both programmes feature interactive classes and activities during the day, and evening social
    events to speak with Jane Street employees and other women attending the event in a more casual
    setting.

    The quantitative trading programme focuses on mathematical and financial topics—such as
    probability, market structure, and arbitrage—through a combination of short classroom lectures,
    group games, and mock trading sessions. There is a curriculum of core subjects with flexibility
    to explore alternative areas of interest, and plenty of opportunities for close interaction with
    our traders.

    The software engineering programme focuses on the fundamentals of building electronic trading
    systems, OCaml, and the library and tools we use in our everyday work at Jane Street.
    Participants will put these tools to use by writing the back end and UI for a computer game,
    along with a program that trades on a simulated stock exchange. These activities involve a
    combination of classroom lectures, group games and exercises, and one-on-one mentorship.

    Selected students will arrive in London on the evening of Sunday, 20 September and will depart
    the evening of Wednesday, 23 September. Jane Street will provide all travel to and from London,
    accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food and drinks throughout
    the event.

    Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative technology, a scientific
    approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our business. Founded in 2000, Jane
    Street employs more than 1,100 people with offices in New York, London, Amsterdam, and Hong
    Kong. We are always on the lookout for great new people to join our team.

    The environment at Jane Street is open, informal, intellectual, and fun. The dress code is
    casual, the kitchen is stocked, and discussions are always lively. Teaching and learning are
    central activities through classes, mentoring, and discussion.

    Selected students will arrive in London on the evening of Sunday, 20 September and will depart
    the evening of Wednesday, 23 September. Jane Street will provide all travel to and from London,
    accommodation at a hotel near the office, and of course, plenty of food and drinks throughout
    the event.

    **Apply here: https://janestreet.com/apply-witt**

    **Who: Women in their second year of study in Autumn 2020\
    When: 20th - 23rd September 2020\
    Deadline to apply: Sunday, 5th July 2020 at 11.59pm BST**
  </sponsor>

  <sign
    name="Radostin Petrov"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
    facebook="radostin.petrov99">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>