<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
        title="Next Week - Women in Computing and Women in Gaming Events"
        agenda="false"
        logos="false">
    <text>
        As International Women's Day is closing in and as part of Women's
        History Month, we will be co-hosting two panels next week
        celebrating diversity in Computing and Gaming.

        More information on these events you can find below, including the
        Eventbrite links to RSVP.\
        Everyone is welcome!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Women in Gaming Panel</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/ciyfOQu.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-10T18:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-10T19:30:00+00:00"
            location="Blackett LT 1">
        <text>
            We would like to invite you to the women in gaming panel, where we
            will try to increase the visibility and representation of women in
            gaming.

            The panel will be an hour long, including a 10-15 min Q&amp;A with the
            panelists, followed by an informal networking session with a catered
            reception.

            The panel will take place on Tuesday 10th March at 6:30pm in
            Blackett LT1, located on Imperial's South Kensington Campus.

            This event is part of Women's History Month at Imperial College
            London and is open to everyone! Just make sure to grab a ticket on
            Eventbrite to ensure you have food at the event! Let us know about
            any dietary requirements by emailing us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/520737038579661/">
                Facebook
            </link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/women-in-gaming-panel-tickets-96475766615/">
                Eventbrite
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>In Conversation with Tech Leaders Across Academia and Industry
    </heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/jUs6CvK.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-11T12:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-11T18:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 308">
        <text>
            In honour of International Women’s Day, WiC are excited to announce
            a half-day conference at Imperial College London on the 11th of
            March. Join us to hear from STEM leaders across industry and
            academia about their career journeys followed by a panel on how
            discrimination can be tackled to make the tech industry a more
            welcoming place for minorities.
            Open to all!
            Graduate students are also invited to a CV+Interview lunchtime
            workshop run by Faculty.ai in room 218. Workshop is aimed at those
            preparing the transition from academia to industry and/or
            consulting.

            Speaker Bios
            ---------------------------------------------------------------

            Professor Julie McCann, Head of Adaptive Emergent Systems
            Engineering (AESE) group, Imperial College London

            Julie A. McCann is a Professor in Computer Systems at Imperial
            College. Her research centres on highly decentralized and
            self-organizing scalable algorithms for wireless sensing networks.
            or cyber-physical systems. She leads the Adaptive Emergent Systems
            Engineering Research Group and Directed the Intel Collaborative
            Research Institute for Sustainable Cities, and is currently working
            with IBM, CISCO and others on substantive smart cities research. She
            has received significant funding though national and international
            bodies such as the UK’s EPSRC, NERC and EU 2020 funding and has a
            number of her team housed in A* in Singapore working with I2R and
            Singapore's HDB. Julie is an elected peer for the EPSRC. She has
            actively served on, and chaired, many conference committees and is a
            Fellow of the BCS and Charted Engineer.

            Dr Sepi Chakaveh, CEO/Founder of Pixsellar

            Dr. Sepideh (Sepi) Chakaveh, is a Senior Associate Tutor &amp;
            Departmental Lecturer in Data Science &amp; Artificial Intelligence at
            the University of Oxford and the CEO &amp; Founder of Pixsellar
            Technologies a Big Data Video Analytics Start-up company. Sepi holds
            a BSc in Electronics &amp; Electrical Engineering and a PhD in
            Astrophysics &amp; Space Sciences. Sepi has worked both in the UK and
            Germany as Senior Scientist/Academic at Imperial College London, Max
            Planck Institute in Heidelberg, Fraunhofer Society &amp; the University
            of Southampton where she was the co-founder &amp; the former Director of
            Southampton Data Science Academy, the first UK online Data Science
            academy. Sepi is a member of the Open Data Institute, associated
            researcher of the Fraunhofer Society and was recently titled Persian
            Woman in Tech Data Science Thought Leader at a ceremony in Google HQ
            London as well as the winner of the FDM Everywoman in technology
            Innovator Award 2020.

            Katerina Daminova, Business Strategy at Yobota

            After graduating from the London School of Economics, Ekaterina
            began her career in capital markets, working on the trading floors
            of Goldman Sachs, UBS and Leonteq. As an experienced cross-asset
            sales person, she realised the drawbacks of legacy banking systems
            and pioneered the distribution of automatic trading solutions and
            was on the forefront of bringing crypto-backed structured products
            to institutional investors. Discovering a passion for technology and
            innovation, and armed with a unique skill set, she moved
            enthusiastically into fintech. Currently she is working in a
            business development and product management role at Yobota, a
            fast-growing fintech startup. A passionate ambassador for female
            empowerment in tech, Kat is an active member of Code First Girls,
            and she spends her free time at hackathons, encouraging students to
            also join the fintech movement.


            Panel members
            ---------------------------------------------------------------

            Professor Nigar Hashimzade, Director of Research, Department of
            Economics and Finance, Brunel

            Becky Plummer, Team Leader, Software Infastructure, Bloomberg

            Christina Franzeskides, COO of Comind
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/195198955050488/">
                Facebook
            </link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/iwdc2020-in-conversation-with-tech-leaders-in-academia-and-industry-tickets-96877941531/">
                Eventbrite
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>
</email>