<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/O85oVhT.png"
    alt="Star-shaped gingerbreads on marble tabletop"
    title="Only two weeks to go before you can focus on gingerbread baking full-time"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone, hope you're doing well!

    With only two weeks to go before the winter break, we're keeping this
    week's digest short. Read on to hear from Women in Computing and StarLeaf.

    Good luck to everyone sitting exams and submitting projects next week!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Women in Computing</heading>
  <image width="40"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dHHFMfV.png"
    alt="Women in Computing"
    title="Women in Computing"/>
  <hr/>
  <text>
    Women in Computing is expanding to include events run for and by
    undergraduate students of Computing and JMC. If you would like to get
    involved as part of the committee, or simply have ideas of events you would
    like to see and participate in, please don’t hesitate to reach out to Aydan
    Gasimova (a.gasimova16@imperial.ac.uk). We look forward to hearing from
    you!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>StarLeaf Industrial Placement</heading>
  <sponsor company="starleaf">
    ### Cloud R&amp;D Watford, England, United Kingdom

    #### Description

    We are interested in speaking with students from Imperial College London
    that are looking for a place to complete their industrial placements in
    2021. We can consider students looking for either four or 6-month
    placements.

    #### What you can expect

    As an Intern in one of our software engineering groups, you will be
    assigned an experienced software engineer as your mentor and be given a
    desk within the group. We will identify a project suited to your level of
    experience that will deliver a feature or a tool that is directly
    applicable to our business. Your experience as an intern will be as close
    as possible as a full-time member of our team. We are confident that this
    experience will give you a valuable understanding of how a software
    engineering team functions in a commercial environment.

    Our software teams design and implement complex systems across a wide range
    of technologies and programming languages, including C, C#, C++, Java,
    Python, SQL, and Javascript. We make extensive use of continuous
    integration and deployment methodologies based on tools such as Salt,
    Jenkins, pytest, Catch, and homegrown automated system test frameworks. We
    place emphasis on high quality, well-tested code and a quick turnaround
    time for adding new features to our products. We believe that this is an
    ideal environment for you to take your first steps in commercial software
    engineering

    ### You can find more details and apply by following [**this link**](https://apply.workable.com/starleaf/j/12FA12111C/)
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
