<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/tdLQTyC.jpg"
    alt="Halloween biscuits next to an October 2020 calendar page"
    title="Boo!" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We hope you’ve had a great week and enjoyed our events!

    In the upcoming week we're bringing you an Escape Room Night and exciting
    events with our sponsors - G-Research and London Stock Exchange Group.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

<heading>Escape Room Night</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/zGquoy9.png"/>
<event startDate="2020-10-26T18:00:00+00:00"
  endDate="2020-10-26T19:00:00+00:00">
<text>
  Come and Join DoCSoc in the first ever ESCAPE ROOM NIGHT!! Come register as a
  team and go head-to-head with other teams to escape FIRST! There will be two
  types of Escape Rooms to chose from and winners might have some prizes coming
  their way 👀

  Each team is only allowed to have a maximum of 6 people! Make sure you
  register your team before the event.

  Event will take place on the DoCSoc Microsoft Teams Team. Register [here](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=B3WJK4zudUWDC0-CZ8PTB4BymOWFa9VFtQLZQgz9br9UMjJHRlpFOElFMk9OSFc3NFJQRTNKQ0g3WC4u).
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/494918434799292">Facebook</link>
  <link href="https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=B3WJK4zudUWDC0-CZ8PTB4BymOWFa9VFtQLZQgz9br9UMjJHRlpFOElFMk9OSFc3NFJQRTNKQ0g3WC4u">Registration Form</link>
</links>
</event>

<hr/>

<heading>G-Research Coding Challenge</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/xC8DMPA.png"/>
<event startDate="2020-10-27T18:00:00+00:00"
  endDate="2020-10-27T20:00:00+00:00">
<text>
    Join us for the G-Research Coding Challenge, where you'll compete in teams
    in a series ofprogressively more difficult software development challenges.

    Tuesday 27th October, 6:00 - 8:00 pm (GMT)

    Open to CompSci/Mathematics students in their penultimate or final years,
    the event will have teams of 3-5 people competing to build a natural
    language calculation engine (no prior NLP experience required). The
    challenges will cover things like evaluation of arithmetic expressions to
    unit conversions and equation solving.

    To register, just fill out the form at
    http://bit.ly/gr-coding-challenge-oct. Wewill allocate teams the week
    before the event (or if you would like to join asa team with friends, just
    let us know when you register).

    Please note, you will need a fully charged laptop, a good
    internet connection, Chrome or Safari, and headphones to take part.

    Once you have registered you will receive a unique link to join the event
    which you should use to log in by 5:45 pm (GMT), so that you can meet your
    teammates and learn how to navigate the online event space.  More
    information on the event will be emailed to you one day before.

    Once the game is complete, you will have the opportunity to stay online
    for some virtual networking where you can discuss the event and life at
    G-Research with members of our team.

    We'll be handing out prizes to the top three teams, with each member getting
    an Amazon voucher (£50 for first, £25 forsecond, £10 for third).
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/353261152625880">Facebook</link>
  <link href="http://bit.ly/gr-coding-challenge-oct">Registration Form</link>
</links>
</event>

<hr/>

<heading>DoCSoc x LSEG: My Journey to the London Stock Exchange Group</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/VmY9JWY.png"/>
<event startDate="2020-10-29T18:00:00+00:00"
  endDate="2020-10-29T20:00:00+00:00">
<text>
  London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) has a long, prestigious heritage that few
  organisations can rival, dating back to 1698. Since then, we’ve grown to
  become one of the world’s foremost financial market infrastructure and
  capital markets groups. As a global leader in financial technology, LSEG
  continues to play a pivotal role within the financial markets during these
  challenging and unprecedented times.

  Join Ziyou Zang, a Technology Graduate in Enterprise Cloud for a LSEG Virtual
  Event with the Imperial College DoCSoc on 29th October from 6pm–8pm to find
  out about Ziyou’s journey to LSEG. Ziyou recently graduated from Imperial
  College in 2020 with a MSc in Computer Science. You’ll get the chance to put
  your questions to Ziyou &amp; an Early Years Careers Lead as well as learning
  more about how you can shape the future of LSEG through our technology spring
  week, internship and graduate programmes.

  Join Zoom Meeting:

  https://lseg.zoom.us/j/88429687188?pwd=QUpWNU90WEpWT2dpNzlFeVlmbzNGQT09

  Meeting ID: `884 2968 7188`

  Passcode: `5KeeFk`
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/357754118974051">Facebook</link>
  <link href="https://lseg.zoom.us/j/88429687188?pwd=QUpWNU90WEpWT2dpNzlFeVlmbzNGQT09">Zoom Meeting</link>
</links>
</event>

<hr/>

<heading>Python 101</heading>
<image src="https://i.imgur.com/scdMdeq.jpg"/>
<event startDate="2020-10-27T16:00:00+00:00"
  endDate="2020-10-27T18:00:00+00:00">
<text>
  One of the key attributes DoCSoc hosts is the Python 101 Introductory
  Workshop for not only DoC students, but all members of Imperial College
  London. We invite everyone from any disciplines and level of education.
  This will be a beginners level course for anyone who has very little to
  none knowledge in Python. Please click "Going" on Facebook so we can
  estimate the size of the interactive workshops.

  Dates: every Tuesday 4-6pm GMT from Oct 20th to Nov 24th.

  This week's lecture will be on control flow (if statements, for and while
  loops), lists and list comprehensions.
</text>
<links>
  <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/276914916715070">Facebook</link>
</links>
  </event>

<hr/>

<text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

<hr/>

<heading>Graphcore - Poplar SDK 1.3 Released</heading>
<sponsor company="graphcore">
  **Poplar SDK 1.3 Released**

  ![Poplar SDK 1.3
  Released](https://www.graphcore.ai/hs-fs/hubfs/Graphcore%20releases%20Poplar%20SDK%201.3%20version.jpg)

  We just released Poplar SDK 1.3 which includes multiple optimisations and new
  features to help IPU developers run their ML models faster and more
  efficiently. We also launched [version 2.1 of the PopVision™ Graph Analyser
  Tool](https://www.graphcore.ai/posts/major-update-released-for-poplar-application-analysis-tool).

  Read the blog [here](https://www.graphcore.ai/posts/graphcore-releases-new-poplar-sdk-1.3).
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>LSEG - WIN Breakfast Series</heading>
<sponsor company="lseg">
  **The history of London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) can be traced all the way
  back to 1698. The financial markets have evolved significantly since then,
  and so too has the nature of our business. LSEG has grown to become one of
  the world’s foremost financial markets infrastructure groups, and a globally
  recognised leader in emerging financial technology, or FinTech.**

  Join the LSEG Women’s Inspire Network (WIN) for a **series of interactive
  sessions** that will give you a greater insight into our work at the centre
  of financial markets. As well as hearing from senior leaders on specific
  topics, you will have the opportunity to network with representatives within
  LSEG and learn more about the opportunities that we offer.

  SUSTAINABLE INVESTMENT 26 October, 09:30–10:30

  TECHNOLOGY 27 October, 09:30–10:30

  POST TRADE 29 October, 09:30–10:30

  This unique opportunity to hear from and network with our WIN members is open
  to students interested in applying to our graduate and intern programmes. To
  register for these events click
  [here](https://www2.lseg.com/WIN-breakfast-series); registration for each
  event will close five days before the event.

  To discover more about our programmes and to apply, visit
  www.lseg.com/graduates.
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<heading>Palantir’s Virtual Puzzlehunt</heading>
<sponsor company="palantir">
  Hello!

  We invite you to participate in Palantir’s first Virtual Puzzlehunt happening
  on Saturday 31 October. Registration is now open, please read on to learn
  more about what puzzlehunt is and how you can participate!

  Date: 31 October

  Time: 1:00 PM London time

  Website: https://palantirpuzzlehunt.com/foodforthought/

  What is a puzzlehunt?

  Think of a puzzlehunt as a treasure hunt where you need to solve a puzzle in
  order to move on to the next location. Each puzzle usually solves to a single
  word or short phrase and can range from your standard logic puzzles,
  knowledge of idioms, to finding clues in a set of pictures.Teams of 4-6
  people will go (virtually) from location to location competing against other
  teams all around the world! The goal is to finish each puzzle in the
  shortest amount of time possible. There will be a winning team for each
  individual puzzle, and then a winning team of the entire puzzlehunt.


  What should I know about the event?

  The hunt will kick off at 1:00 PM London time. We will begin the event with a
  brief kickoff where we’ll share an overview of the event, what to expect, and
  how to request help throughout the hunt.If you have to join later than 1:00
  PM London time, that is okay! Just note that there will only be live support
  from 1:00-9:00 PM London time. The length of the hunt is about 8 hours, but
  teams can skip certain puzzles if they’d like to shorten the event to about 4
  hours instead. The hunt will be in English.

  How do we sign up?

  To register once you’ve assembled your gang of motley puzzle solvers, have
  one person go to the website (palantirpuzzlehunt.com) and register a team
  username and password which will be a shared login for everyone on the
  team. You will need a hunt code to register. The hunt code is “ON YOUR
  MARKS”. You can enter all your team members when you register the team or
  login and add them afterwards. Registration will be closing on Friday, 29
  October at 10:00 PM London time.

  If you have any questions about the hunt or the registration process, send us
  an email at foodforthought@palantir.com.

  Thanks, and we hope to see you there!
</sponsor>

<hr/>

<sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
  role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
  linkedin="stefanradziuk">
  Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
