<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="80"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/OULgDJZ.jpg"
            alt="Heart-shaped biscuits"
            title="Happy Valentine's Day/Week"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Hi everyone,

        Now that we have settled well into second term, we hope you're all coping with your coursework. Although, we
        kept it silent this week (post IC Hack rest), we are coming back with more events than ever for you!\
        Besides, the hackathons and workshops that we run in February, we added some social events for next week, so you
        can take a moment to relax from all the universitycd ..
        work. Reading groups are also back! Also, we will be selling
        our second batch of tickets for Revel (first batch sold out in less than 15 seconds!) on **Monday 17th at
        1:30**.

        Read on for more information!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## General Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Run for DoCSoc's 2020/21 Committee</heading>
    <text>
        **Leadership Elections 2020** are now open and nominations are now open for
        DoCSoc's 2020/21 committee. Nominations will run **until 12:00 on Friday 28th
        February**.

        We will be running a short presentation this Thursday detailing the responsibilities of every role and other
        information you
        should know when running for a committee position(details below). We strongly recommend you attend the event, if
        you are planning on standing for a role within DoCSoc.

        If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us at docsoc@imperial.ac.uk
        or get in touch with a current committee member!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Leon x DesSoc Hackathon</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6aozzku.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-22T09:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-24T18:00:00+00:00"
            location="Leon HQ, Southward">
        <text>
            Join the us on Saturday 22nd and Sunday the 23rd of February for an exciting weekend of hacking and hands-on
            prototyping. All teams will present their work at an event in the evening on Monday the 24th of February to
            the Leon CEO and team. The event welcomes all students enthusiastic about sustainability, future
            technologies (including robotics) and UX/UI design and engineering.

            This event is sponsored by Leon and will be hosted at their HQ in Southwark.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/181059803232259/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/leon-x-imperial-desing-engineering-society-hackathon-2020-tickets-94873197287">
                Eventbrite
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Games Night with G-Research</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/nXAzT11.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-17T18:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-17T20:30:00+00:00"
            location="EE Building 407A/B">
        <text>
            Please click GOING if you're likely to attend so we can order enough pizza 🍕🍕🍕

            ---

            Ever wondered what is it like to work at G-Research, or what G-Research does anyway? Come to our casual
            Games
            Night on Monday 17th February to play some of our favourite board games and have a chat. We are hiring and
            would
            love to answer any question/worry that you have when it comes to applying. We also love to just have a fun
            time
            with you too.

            Free pizzas and drinks are available. Be sure to beat our Head of Engineering on his favourite board games!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/495821034458700/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Raspberry Pi Workshops</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/97B3YPK.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-18T13:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-18T14:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 308">
        <text>
            Have you ever wanted to know more about a Raspberry Pi? Or are you a first year Computing student whose
            summer project will closely involve the Raspberry Pi? Then come join us at our new 4-week Raspberry Pi
            course where you will get to learn what this small computer is capable of!

            We will introduce the Pi, its architecture and do multiple demos for VNC Connections, Python + Assembly
            programming and coding a tiny bootloader!

            These workshops are open to everyone!
            Make sure to grab your Eventbrite ticket to get free pizza!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1442439432589537/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/raspberry-pi-workshops-tickets-91677775695">Eventbrite</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Reading Groups by Prof Abbas Edalat and Antonio Rago
    </heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/Kw6OlOQ.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-19T13:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-19T14:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 145">
        <text>
            Reading groups are back this term! Reading groups are sessions where researchers come and talk about their
            current work to expose current undergraduate students to research! These talks are open to everyone!

            Session 1 by Prof Abbas Edalat at 1-1.30 pm
            Title
            Algorithmic Human Development: What is it and why do we need it now?

            Abstract
            In the face of our current existential problems and challenges, I
            will argue by making a comparison with the origin of AI that we
            now actually need to develop algorithms to enhance emotional and social intelligence and creativity in the
            human
            individual. These non-invasive protocols would be based on neuroplasticity and long term potentiation and
            represent an interactive play between two internal agents: the emotion-driven Child and the thought-driven
            Adult
            equipped with an action programme. The protocols aim at neural retraining for optimal redevelopment and
            emotion
            self-regulation in the individual regarded as a biological cybernetic system with the targeted goals of
            becoming
            (i) compassionate, (ii) cheerful and (iii) creative. Our proposed framework, named Self-attachment, has
            parallels with Machine Learning as it employs the the basic paradigms of "rebooting", "substitution",
            "iteration" and "prior updating"
            in the human individual. I will give the results of a pilot project
            on the subject and describe two Bayesian computational brain models for it: one based on Hebbian artificial
            neural networks and one on the Free Energy Principle. I will finally argue that learning to laugh, in
            particular
            to laugh at oneself, is the number one learning task in our age and present novel protocols, based on
            logical
            theories of laughter, to explain how this learning can be acquired.

            Session 2 by Antonio Rago at 1.30-2 pm
            Title
            Argumentation as a Framework for Conversational AI

            Abstract
            As AI becomes ever more ubiquitous in our everyday lives, its ability to explain to and interact with humans
            is
            evolving into a critical research area. The explanation of a result, e.g. a prediction or a recommendation,
            in a
            way which allows a user to anthropomorphise a system is, therefore, a pivotal functionality in a user’s
            experience. We show how argumentative abstractions underpinning AI methods can provide the structural
            scaffolding for conversational explanations. We illustrate how the dialectical reasoning and conflict
            management
            capabilities of argumentation empower conversational repertoires in two different settings, recommender
            systems
            and automated review aggregation. We then demonstrate how the resulting explanations may be equipped with
            feedback mechanisms that guarantee that the system’s accuracy will improve with time or may simply be
            designed
            to induce trust in and provide transparency to users.
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/790582004759283/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>So you want to run for DoCSoc Committee?</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/7GD7thB.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-20T13:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-20T14:00:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 217/218">
        <text>
            Thinking of running for DoCSoc committee in this year's Leadership Elections? Come along to this talk,
            presented by current members of the committee, where we'll be detailing what exactly goes into DoCSoc and
            what each role entails.

            Read more about the Leadership Elections here:
            https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/your-union/leadership-elections-2020

            Nominate yourself here: https://vote.union.ic.ac.uk/

            Don't forget to read the Candidates' Pack &amp; Election Rules:
            https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/information-for-candidates#Candidates%20Pack. Breaking election rules
            can result in disqualification.

            See you there!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/119451139488700/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Google Hashcode Imperial College London Hub</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/6rBfuEh.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-20T17:30:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-20T21:30:00+00:00"
            location="Huxley 221, 217, 218">
        <text>
            Hash Code is a team programming competition, organized by Google, for students and professionals around the
            world. You pick your team and programming language and we pick an engineering problem for you to solve. Join
            us at the Imperial College London Hub for the Online Qualification Round. Top teams will then be invited to
            a Google office for the Final Round.

            Sign up here: https://g.co/hashcode
            Remember to select Imperial College London Hub after you apply

            There are only 100 slots for our hub, so make sure you sign up as soon as possible
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/216819712683436/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://codingcompetitions.withgoogle.com/hashcode/">Register</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>


    <heading>The Valentine's Bar Night</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/OeRjs8p.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-20T19:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-20T23:00:00+00:00"
            location="Metric">
        <text>
            You've made it halfway through term - come celebrate with us at the Valentine's Bar Night! Whether you've
            been bitten by the love bug or you're living life carefree, everyone's welcome for some free drinks.

            Drinks tokens will be given upon entry for FREE to DoCSoc members. Tokens are valid for both alcoholic and
            non-alcoholic drinks. We have the right to refuse tokens to members at our discretion.

            You are entitled to bring one non-Imperial plus one. ID must be shown at entry to prove this. You must stay
            with your plus one at all times and they will not be given any drinks tokens. Imperial plus ones must be
            DoCSoc members in order to attend.

            We may decide to head to Belushi's after the event; if this is the case, DoCSoc often buys attendees a round
            of drinks, so if you're unable to come to the bar night, bear in mind there is still a chance members will
            go out after!

            ----------------------

            You must be a member of DoCSoc before Saturday 15th February in order to be admitted. Computing, JMC, and
            EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership is £30. Strictly 18+ only - we will be checking
            IDs.

            Please send an email to us at docsoc@ic.ac.uk if you intend to bring a non-Imperial plus one. Any Imperial
            plus-ones must have purchased membership, otherwise they will be denied entry.

            Our full barnight policy is linked here: http://docsoc.co.uk/barnightpolicy

            Find out more: http://docsoc.co.uk/join
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2656351507943000/">Facebook</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Ed Tech Hackday</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/mAbsEAn.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-22T11:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-02-22T17:00:00+00:00"
            location="TBA">
        <text>
            Join DoC on Saturday 22nd February for a one day Hackathon to help design and develop to your education
            tools (Materials, eMarking and more)

            This is an excellent occasion for people interested in working on the Edtech platforms with us over the
            summer to start exploring the code and make a first contribution

            Please RSVP here: https://forms.gle/foZwZKEN6XVrNVr68

            Lunch will be provided on the day, so let us know if you plan to attend by selecting "Going" and filling in
            the form above!
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/194418778361279/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdQaMWltx44IvT1WfalwPYN-u5oFRRiI9u5Q70IuuHrjftGSQ/viewform">
                RSVP
            </link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC HealthHack 2020</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/QcuKsfS.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-02-29T09:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-01T17:00:00+00:00"
            location="Imperial College London">
        <text>
            The Department of Computing Society (DoCSoc), Bioengineering Society, ICSM Coding Society and MedTech
            Society proudly present the IC HealthHack 2020!

            We are back with HealthHack 20 bigger and better than ever!
            Combining skills in bioengineering, computer science, and medicine, HealthHack will bring together talented
            students to tackle the most current medical challenges through technology.
            This year, we are focusing on Medical Education as our overarching theme.
            Over the weekend of 29th February - 1st March 2020, teams will bring their awesome ideas to life and develop
            solutions to real-life health education challenges.

            Save the date and follow the event page for more details, including sponsors and schedule announcements.

            Website: https://ichealthhack.org/
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2630916247137813/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://ichealthhack.org/">Website</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Roaring Revel: Second Batch of Tickets</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/hlkVgkp.jpg"/>
    <event
            startDate="2020-03-02T19:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-03-03T01:00:00+00:00"
            location="Quaglino's
                      16 Bury Street
                      London, SW1Y 6AJ">
        <text>
            **This event is for 18+ only.**

            A little party never killed nobody, so join RCSU and DoCSoc for an extravagant night of glitz, glam and a
            party fit for the 20's - here's to Roaring Revel!

            From Spanish rooftop bars to Parisian themed halls, we're now taking you back in time to the Prohibition
            era. Our chosen gin mill, Quaglino's, is decorated to the taste of the period and has a history as rich as
            the location of St James's.

            The evening will start with a cocktail reception with further drinks served later as the night progresses.
            We will also be serving canapés and providing entertainment throughout the evening. So wear your ritziest
            garms and get ready to party like it's the 20's!

            Ticket prices:

            DoCSoc: £28

            RCSU: £35

            **Second batch releases on 17th February: 1:30pm!**
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2205576013084814/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/roaring-revel-docsoc-tickets-92928960021">Eventbrite</link>
        </links>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Next Jump is hiring – Deadline next week!</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/BjhQGZD.png"/>
    <sponsor company="next_jump">
        **Who are we?**\
        Next Jump is a global tech company with an award-winning culture. We help to transform companies from all
        sectors (Finance, Tech, Military) to build high performing teams; and our E-commerce platform is used by 70% of
        the Fortune 1000 (including Facebook, Bloomberg and the BBC) making $2B in sales a year. Over the last 12
        months, our core and social businesses have been growing rapidly. We are looking for developers who want to
        design, build and market amazing mobile apps and web platforms - built with React Native, Go, PHP, Vue.js, AWS
        and more - to our 3 million UK customers from their first day on the job.

        The deadline for our Spring Super Saturday is **Friday, 21st February** - catch our interest and we'll chat to
        you,
        send you a coding test and invite you to our Super Saturday assessment day on the 29th Feb 2020.

        We are looking to fill the vacancies in our Intern Class 2020 as well as Graduate Class 2020.

        **Apply Now!**
        If you are looking for a 'not-your-typical graduate job/internship', then Next Jump's the place for you!
        - Graduate Class 2020:
        https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/UWulrrsRCG/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications
        - Intern Class 2020:
        https://nextjump.applytojob.com/apply/wYfZzpCivx/Software-Engineer-Web-Applications-Internship
    </sponsor>


    <hr/>

    <heading>Bloomberg Industrial Placement &amp; Graduate Positions</heading>
    <sponsor company="bloomberg">
        Bloomberg's applications for the [Industrial
        Placements](https://careers.bloomberg.com/job/detail/76941) and [Graduate
        Positions](https://careers.bloomberg.com/job/detail/76939) are open.

        Bloomberg's diverse community of engineers take on some of the world’s most interesting and important technical
        challenges. We develop impactful solutions to complex, real-world problems. With new systems being rolled out
        daily, we make an immediate impact on global markets and we look for the best software engineers to build them.
    </sponsor>

    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>

</email>