<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/C2qH4qe.jpg"
    alt="Chocolate chip biscuits and coffee grains"
    title="A stack of biscuits, with one popped off the stack and bitten" />
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Welcome to the second digest of the year!

    We've got some great events prepared for you this week, including our
    annual Sponsors' Exhibition!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## General Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Autumn Elections - Year Rep Nominations Open</heading>
    <text>
      Nominations in the Union Autumn elections are **NOW OPEN** and close at
      **noon on Tuesday 13 October**!

      It is an opportunity to make your voice heard within the College and the
      Union.

      Every year students vote for an Academic Year Representative and
      Wellbeing Year Representative.

      The Academic Year Representative receives and collates feedback from
      their cohort, passing this information to the Departmental
      Representatives or staff as appropriate. Academic Representatives have
      made long-lasting improvements in many areas such as the content of
      curricula, feedback quality and timeliness, exam timetables and formats,
      and online learning resources.

      Wellbeing Year Representatives are part of the Wellbeing Representation
      Network, which aims to tackle issues such as stress and pressure, mental
      health, the quality of personal tutoring, how students are supported to
      be resilient and independent, transitioning back into study after time
      off, and more. Wellbeing Representatives will work with College staff,
      Welfare Officers, and Academic Representatives.

      Year reps make **real change within the department**, with a place on
      regular Staff Student Committee meetings, voicing their concerns to
      teaching fellows and staff.

      To nominate yourself and for more information on the mentioned and other
      roles available, visit the Union's [Autumn Elections
      page](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/news/autumn-elections-2020).
    </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Virtual Sponsors' Exhibition</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/oGrpzJK.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-10-14T13:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2020-10-14T16:00:00+01:00">
    <text>
      This year, our flagship Sponsors Exhibition that attracts over 500 students
      each year has gone virtual, here on Hopin!

      Whether you are looking for an internship or graduate role, or simply want
      to know more about industry, we really recommend you come along and tune in
      as it’s a great way to get in direct contact with recruiters and engineers
      from highly regarded companies and should provide invaluable insight into
      the recruitment process.
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/730389634219857/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Mums and Dads Pub Quiz</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/ztSYkg2.png"/>
  <event startDate="2020-10-12T15:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2020-10-12T17:00:00+01:00">
    <text>
      It's time for DoCSoc's Mum's and Dad's first meet up! Come along to meet
      your families and engage in a competitive PUB QUIZ 🍻 with the other
      families! This is a great opportunity for freshers to ask any questions
      they might have and be introduced into DoC.

      Keep an eye out for prizes for the top 3 teams!!

      Links will be posted on Facebook closer to the time.

      Mums and Dads parent? Be sure to turn up to this event to meet your children!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2666493770267344/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Python 101</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/scdMdeq.jpg"/>
  <event startDate="2020-10-20T16:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2020-10-20T18:00:00+01:00">
  <text>
    One of the key attributes DoCSoc hosts is the Python 101 Introductory
    Workshop for not only DoC students, but all members of Imperial College
    London. We invite everyone from any disciplines and level of education.
    This will be a beginners level course for anyone who has very little to
    none knowledge in Python. Please click "Going" on Facebook so we can
    estimate the size of the interactive workshops.

    Dates: every Tuesday 4-6pm GMT from Oct 20th to Nov 24th

    Syllabus:

    * Oct 20th - Introduction, variables, user I/O

    * Oct 27th - Control Flow (if statements, for and while loops), lists and
    list comprehension

    * Nov 3rd - Error Handling, Imports, Functions, Recursion (?)

    * Nov 10th - Advanced control flow (break, continue, pass), Data Structures
    (Tuple, Dictionary, Set), Plotting data w/matplotlib

    * Nov 17th - Assert, Classes with OOP, Lambdas

    * Nov 24th - (extra session) Q&amp;A, Fundamentals of CS (theoretical, more for
    1st year Computing)
  </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/276914916715070">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Netcraft – Applications of Computing in Industry Talk</heading>
  <sponsor company="netcraft">
    Netcraft will be giving an ACI talk on Tuesday about the final year project
    of an ex-DoCSoc student made in partnership with Netcraft and now
    integrated in our systems. Netcraft have found that criminal infrastructure
    often purports to be located in jurisdictions with less effective legal
    systems, uncooperative law enforcement or anonymous company registrations.
    In reality, the infrastructure is often located in countries with good
    Internet connectivity and reasonable legal systems, like the Netherlands.
    In this talk, James will discuss the development of the system, its
    deployment at Netcraft, and some of the engineering challenges which have
    been overcome.

    If you’re interested in a career with Netcraft or collaborating on a final year
    project with us and want to find out more about what we do and how to
    apply, please check out our recruitment brochure at:
    https://www.netcraft.com/NetcraftRecruitmentBooklet.pdf
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Bloomberg Masterclass – A New Era Of Python Parsing</heading>
  <sponsor company="bloomberg">
    Date: Wednesday, 14 October 2020

    Time: 15:00-16:00 London Time

    Apply: via [Yello](tinyurl.com/y6jbwy6t)

    The Parser was one of the first pieces that were created for Python and it
    has served very efficiently for many years; but implementing new rules in
    the language syntax is becoming more difficult or even impossible in some
    cases.

    In this talk, we will explain the problems with the old parser, how
    the new parser works, what are its benefits, and what to expect from the
    Python grammar in the future.
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>


  <heading>Shape your world with Bank of America</heading>
  <sponsor company="baml">
    Technology touches everything we do and underpins each deal we make. In
    fact, our mainframe environment is the third largest in the world. That
    said, we don’t believe that there is a tech ‘type’. You don’t need finance
    experience to join us and D&amp;I is at our core. Our Global Technology and
    Operations (GT&amp;O) division gives our business the competitive edge to solve
    business problems by delivering high quality and practical solutions.

    Join our Meet the Technology Teams session to speak directly to members of
    our Imperial Tech School Team. The event will provide an open forum where
    you will have the opportunity to ask questions on a range of topics
    including careers in Global Technology, how to apply and general working
    life at Bank of America. Please come prepared with your questions to be
    addressed at this session.

    Register your interest
    [here!](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/lang-en-GB/candidate/postings/5855)

    Let’s shape the world together

    Date: 21st October, 2020

    Time: 14:00 – 15:00 (GMT+1)
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>London Stock Exchange Group Events and Opportunities</heading>
  <sponsor company="lseg">
    **London Stock Exchange Group – Grow your career at market speed.**

    London Stock Exchange Group **(LSE.L)** has a long, prestigious heritage that
    few organisations around the world can rival, dating back to 1698. Since
    then, we have grown to become one of the world’s foremost financial market
    infrastructure and capital markets groups, and a global leader in new
    financial technology (FinTech). Headquartered in London, our geographic
    footprint extends to more than 25 cities worldwide, and more than 60
    nationalities are represented by our 5000-strong workforce.

    We understand that this is a challenging and unprecedented time for
    everyone, but our graduate and internship programmes –and the development
    of new talent –remains critical to our future business success. As we
    continue to expand and diversify, we are looking for the next generation of
    talented, ambitious graduates to help us shape the future of LSEG. You will
    get direct exposure to the exciting innovations happening within finance
    and technology, putting your ideas and problem-solving skills to use and
    helping to drive our growth.

    _You can find more information about LSEG events and opportunities in pdfs
    attached to this email._
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jane Street Estimathons 2020!</heading>
  <sponsor company="jane_street">
    **What is an Estimathon?!**

    The Estimathon is a team-based contest that combines trivia, game theory,
    and mathematical thinking. Teams have 30 minutes to work on a set of 13
    estimation problems, the winning team being the one with the best set of
    estimates. Since debuting the Estimathon in 2013, Jane Street has run over
    200 Estimathon contests.

    The answer to each problem is a positive number. Your team will submit
    intervals for each problem. Intervals may not contain negative numbers or
    zero.

    You may not use the internet, or your calculator/smartphone, or any other
    type of external reference material.


    **Scoring**

    An interval is good if it contains the correct answer. After the 30 minutes
    is over, the final score for your team will be:

    ![(10 + sum of (floor of (max / min)) over good intervals) * 2 ^ (13 - # of
    good intervals)](https://i.imgur.com/yAJFK2G.png)

    That is, for every problem you get wrong (or leave blank), your score
    doubles.

    The winning team is the team with the LOWEST SCORE.

    **Submitting intervals**

    Every team can submit up to 18 total intervals. Submit your intervals at
    any time throughout the contest.  There will be a scoreboard that will be
    updated in real time based on the intervals that are being submitted.

    **Re-submitting**

    Given that each has 18 answers and that there are only 13 problems, it is
    possible to submit intervals for a given problem more than once. If you do
    this, only the last submission for any given problem is the one that will
    count towards your final score. To put it another way: each submission
    (right or wrong) overrides any previous submissions for a given problem.


    If you could like to take part in one of our online Estimathons or
    CEstimathons (where questions are based on the world of computing and
    trivia) please visit our events page to register or click on the dates
    below. You can register as a team of 3-5 or as an individual and we will
    assign you a team on the day - please note that all team members are
    required to register for the event.

    **Dates:** [13th October
    2020](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSclzmHOuHCg44bv2we3cKMImo161tsZmlxbMZmLBq-S7hiCZw/viewform?usp=sf_link)
    (Estimathon), [27th October
    2020](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfMZvqD518v2cEfj8ITT2P8DppnX-V8KeLx7qVHrfC2zoKSjw/viewform?usp=sf_link)
    (CEstimathon) and [11th November
    2020](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdByJvJPCXX9UM3dT_9jk3oaJfHa3nhaAIU4akqpclIPmNWOQ/viewform?usp=sf_link)
    (Estimathon) \
    **Time:** 18.00-19.00 BST
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Palantir Virtual Autumn Events</heading>
  <sponsor company="palantir">
    **[Palantir](https://www.palantir.com/students/)** will be hosting a series of
    virtual events over the next few weeks to help students learn more about
    Palantir’s work, opportunities and to prep for applying to open positions.
    To sign-up, please register using **[this
    link](https://fall2020eventsemea.splashthat.com/)** and the password
    `20HobbitFallEMEA`. More info on the specific events below!

    **Panel Q&amp;A: The Ins &amp; Outs of Palantir’s Interview Process:** Whether you’ve
    already applied to Palantir or you are considering starting an application,
    we invite you to join us a for a panel discussion where we demystify
    Palantir’s interview process and provide tips on how you can prepare!
    You’ll hear from interviewers, hiring managers, recruiters and engineers
    who’ve all gone through our interview process and landed a gig at Palantir.
    Attendees will walk away with tangible learnings that can be applied to
    their own interviewing experiences this recruiting season. 

    **Info Session: Palantir 101 + Product Demo** is an opportunity to learn more about
    Palantir straight from the source. Government agencies, commercial
    institutions, and non-profit organizations must wrangle an ever-growing
    amount of data – raising important ethical questions for software companies
    like Palantir that help these institutions harness data to advance their
    missions. But because Palantir is not a consumer-facing company, it’s not
    always easy to understand what we build and how our products are used.
    Here’s your chance to learn more directly from our software engineers.
    Engineers will share how their focus has shifted completely in the last 6
    months to help in the fight against COVID-19 on a variety of different
    fronts. We’ll be sharing demos of our products and answering questions
    about Palantir and our engineering role.
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
  role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
  linkedin="stefanradziuk">
  Until next time,
  </sign>
</email>
