<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Google Inside Look Program and Jane Street Internship"
       agenda="false">

    <text>
        Hi everyone,

        First of all, congratulations to all of us on finishing exams! Certainly
        a big feat that we should all be proud of!

        We have a few messages for opportunities that you might be interested in
        and you can can a look below for more details.

        We hope that everyone is safe during this period and we will continue
        updating you with messages and notices from our sponsors and more!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Inside Look Program Applications are Now Open</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/ol3w4KL.png"/>
    <text>
        **Calling all students!**

        We hope you’re staying safe during this unsettling time. We know many of
        you might be working or studying in different situations to what you’re
        used to, or adapting to a new way of living. We wanted to reach out and
        say we’re right with you.

        The [Inside Look program](https://buildyourfuture.withgoogle.com/programs/inside-look/) was created to bring together a like minded
        group of students from all over Europe, the Middle East and Africa, to
        connect over their passion for technology and a desire to learn more
        about life in a tech role at Google. This year, the program will be
        going fully digital for the first time. We believe that we can deliver a
        really special experience for students over our digital platforms, and
        we’d love to see an application from you.

        **What is Inside Look and when does it take place?**

        We're excited to invite students graduating later than August 2021,
        studying computer science or a related subject to apply for Inside Look.
        This year, we’re pleased to announce that we’ll be hosting Inside Look
        Goes Digital on 27th &amp; 28th August. Selected attendees will be
        invited
        to join an immersive two-day virtual program, including tech talks,
        panels, technical interview practice, fun social activities, and — in
        true Google fashion — the chance to get your hands on some Google
        freebies, delivered directly to you at home!

        While we are unable to host every applicant at Inside Look Goes Digital,
        we’ll also be holding Inside Look: YouTube Live on 21st September, where
        all applicants will be invited to hear from Google engineers on how they
        build products at scale, plus top tips from our hiring team.

        The Inside Look program is committed to supporting diversity at Google
        and the tech industry as a whole. Students who are members of any group
        that has been historically underrepresented in the tech industry are
        encouraged to apply!

        **Sounds great! How do I apply?**

        [Click here to apply
        now](https://services.google.com/fb/forms/insidelook2020/), including an
        up-to-date CV. **Applications are open until 23:59 BST on 1st June**

        **Wait, what if I don’t have an updated CV?**\
        No problem! We want to give you the best possible chance of success when
        applying for this competitive program, so we’ve recorded - from our
        homes - a [video guide](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dA3NX-Tpe4E&amp;feature=youtu.be)
        to writing a great CV. We know it’s hard to convey
        all the things you’re proud of in a concise way, so we’re here to help!

    </text>

    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/1WHKR2c.png"/>

    <text>
        If you have questions please visit [our
        website](https://buildyourfuture.withgoogle.com/programs/inside-look/)
        or email
        [inside-look-2020@google.com](mailto:inside-look-2020@google.com).

        Many thanks,

        Google University Programs Team

    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Jane Street Autumn Internship</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/uRH3cBM.png"/>
    <text>
        **Jane Street invites you to apply to
        our autumn software engineering internship!**

        **About the Position**\
        We are big believers in functional programming, using OCaml, a
        statically-typed functional programming language, as our primary
        development language. We also believe in the value of open source
        software, using it in our daily work and releasing hundreds of thousands
        of lines of our own code as open source.

        **About You**
        - Top-notch programming skills.
        - Deep experience with—and love for—technology. There’s no specific
        checklist; we use code to approach a variety of problems, so we’re
        interested in everything from machine learning to systems administration
        to programming language design.
        - Strong interpersonal skills. Software development at Jane Street is
        highly collaborative, and we are looking for people who can work
        effectively in small, close-knit teams.

        We don’t expect you to have experience with functional programming,
        OCaml, or finance; we’re happy to hire talented engineers and teach them
        what they need to know.

        If you'd like to get an idea of what we cover in our software
        engineering interview process, you can read this [blog
        post](https://blog.janestreet.com/what-a-jane-street-dev-interview-is-like/),
        and to get
        an idea of projects software engineering interns work on you can read
        [this
        post](https://blog.janestreet.com/what-the-interns-have-wrought-2019/)
        highlighting a few of our Summer 2019 projects.

        We hope to host this internship in our new London office. However, both
        our employees' and interns' safety and well-being are our main priority,
        and we may move this to a remote internship nearer the time. This
        internship is intended for those based in Europe and the UK.

        **[APPLY
        HERE](https://www.janestreet.com/join-jane-street/apply/4720341002/)**

        [Keep up with Jane Street recruiting events by following our Facebook
        page.](https://www.facebook.com/JaneStreetRecruit)

    </text>

    <hr/>

</email>
