<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email
  agenda="false"
  logos="false">

  <image
    src="https://i.imgur.com/EmoUOrl.jpg"
    title="IC Hack 20 Important Reminder"/>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi there,

    Congratulations on securing your tickets to **IC Hack 20 Powered by Cisco**! IC Hack is back
    bigger than ever this year with over 450 expected attendees!

    In order for your hackathon weekend, to go flawless we are sending this email with **important
    attendee information**, so please take your time to go through its contents.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    ## CV Upload

    IC Hack 20 is a great opportunity for you to meet recruiters and engineers from our sponsoring
    companies in person.

    As our sponsors are looking to recruit students from the event for various roles, we recommend
    you upload your CV using [this
    form](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd5uKv6g3juHYFCkZTTcNna0pchFdfiaSpFTg3suiVmwhxPjQ/viewform).\
    Deadline for CV submission is **this Friday 31st January**!
  </text>


  <hr/>

  <text>
    ## Equipment Requests

    If you require any specific hardware 🛠 for your hack, please email us with your specifications
    and we'll get back to you on how we can help your hack. Deadline for this is **Friday 31st
    January**, as we will require time to order any special parts.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    ## What to Bring

    On the day, be sure to have your Eventbrite ticket ready (either digital or
    printed - up to you!) and a **valid form of Government ID** (driving license
    or passport). Please note you must be **over 18** on the day of the event to attend.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    ## Ticket Cancellations

    If you find you are unable to attend, we kindly ask you to cancel your ticket [via
    Eventbrite](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/mytickets/)
    or by [emailing us](mailto:ichack@ic.ac.uk) as soon as possible so your space can be
    released. Please note that tickets are **non-transferable**.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>
    That is for now, but we will be releasing more information as we get closer to the event (Slack
    workspace details coming soon).
    Make sure that you have submitted your CV and any hardware requirements you may have by this
    Friday!

    If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know by emailing
    ichack@ic.ac.uk

    We look forward to seeing you at IC Hack 20!

    _- The IC Hack 20 team_
  </text>

</email>