<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Origin - Growing Fintech Looking To Hire Graduate Product Managers &amp; Software Engineers" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <text>
    ![Origin is hiring](https://i.imgur.com/Wexhce2.gif)

    ![Origin is hiring](https://i.imgur.com/pXUIKlo.png)

    ### ORIGIN IS HIRING SOFTWARE ENGINEERS AND PRODUCT MANAGERS

    Origin’s software has transformed the debt capital markets, completely
    streamlining the way companies and investment banks work together to raise
    capital. Having launched just over 4 years ago, Origin is now used by over
    20 investment banks and 90 borrowers in over 50 cities worldwide. Our
    clients include some of the largest investment banks and borrowers
    globally, including Barclays, Citi, and Telefonica. We have recently
    secured our Series A funding round lead by Clearstream and the Luxembourg
    Stock Exchange, and our CEO was named in the top 10 leaders transforming
    finance in Europe by Business Insider.

    At Origin, you’ll get to work with exciting modern technologies: Django to
    write our backend services, Angular8 to create our web app, Kubernetes and
    Docker to schedule and run our services, and AWS to run our infrastructure.

    Origin is looking for smart and driven graduates to join our team as we
    rapidly grow our product offering in the following roles:

    **Graduate Product Manager 2021** - Your primary responsibility will be to
    understand the nuanced customer requirements and translate those into an
    outstanding user experience via well thought out user journeys and designs.

    **Graduate Software Engineer 2020/2021** - You will be peer mentored,
    trained and expected to rapidly develop your skillset. You will gain
    exposure to both the backend and frontend and over time you'll choose which
    one to specialize in.

    Please apply below:

    https://www.originmarkets.com/careers

    We have a strong track-record in rapidly scaling up junior so be ready to
    grow fast!
  </text>
</email>
