<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">

    <image
            width="90"
            src="https://i.imgur.com/WZJa6LG.jpg"
            alt="Container of Danish butter cookies"
            title="Happy new term!?"/>

    <hr/>

    <text>
        Welcome back to another term!

        Hope all of you got a well-deserved rest and enjoyed the holiday season. This term, in addition to our social
        events and bar nights, DoCSoc will be organising our yearly flagship events, mainly IC Hack 20 and Revel.
        Tickets for IC Hack 20 will be **going live on Friday the 10th of Jan at 1:30 pm**, so make sure to stay updated
        over our social media channels (especially Facebook). As always, all of our announcements will be sent out in
        our weekly digest, so make sure to read on!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <text>## General Notices</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>DoCSoc Merch Update</heading>
    <text>
        DoCSoc merch will go on sales soon via the IC Union website. As usual, there will be the hoodies and with “Class
        of 2020” printed for our leavers. In addition, there will be some new merch with limited quantities going on
        sale. We will announce the merch sales in a separate email when it is released on the union website! DoCSoc will
        be sponsoring the merch as always. So stay tuned!
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 Meme Sticker Competition</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/AJWYtkd.png"/>
    <text>
        33 days count down to IC Hack 20, are you ready!! This year, we’ll be introducing the “IC Hack 20 Meme Sticker
        Competition”! We will select one winning entry for this competition. The winning entry will then be printed and
        distributed during the hackathon. Winner will receive a guaranteed ticket to the hackathon! Here’s the link to
        the submission form: https://forms.gle/KcqqZySepSyzSX7NA

        There is no limit on the entries submitted. You can always come back and submit more. We will consider all the
        entries you have submitted. Please submit your entry in pdf, jpg or png files. The deadline will be on 25th
        January.

        Entry condition:
        - “IC HACK 20" shown on the entry
        - Keep the size of the file under 100mb

        [**Please check out and utilise all the relevant files in this folder, including a template of the
        entry.**](https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1dEg6SBlSoy-kbYQAddYe3EIMmKoOZ-lS?usp=sharing)
    </text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>Conf42 - Chaos Engineering Conference - Special DoCSoc Tickets</heading>
    <event
            startDate="2020-01-23T08:00:00+00:00"
            endDate="2020-01-24T16:30:00+00:00"
            location="1a Oxendon St, London SW1Y 4EE">
        <text>
            Learn how companies such as Netflix and PagerDuty intentionally break their systems at scale
            to build more resilient, scalable systems.
            Conf42 (https://conf42.com) is giving away heavily discounted tickets to DoCSoc members and
            Imperial College students. Conf42 will take place on 23rd January 2020 at The Comedy Store in
            Soho, with a day of talks from industry leaders in chaos engineering, followed by networking
            drinks at The Comedy Pub.
            The following special tickets are available for all Imperial College students (bring your
            friends!):
            all students can purchase a conference ticket for a **heavily discounted price of £19**
            (standard
            price £339);
            students from underrepresented groups in technology who are unable to attend without financial
            assistance can apply for free tickets. (DoCSoc is also able to subsidise the cost of travel
            for attendees who are eligible for this category.)
            To obtain a special ticket, email docsoc@imperial.ac.uk.
        </text>
    </event>

    <hr/>

    <text>## On-Campus Events</text>

    <hr/>

    <heading>IC Hack 20 - First Ticket Batch Release</heading>
    <image src="https://i.imgur.com/eky2mzj.jpg"/>
    <event startDate="2020-02-08T10:00:00+00:00"
           endDate="2019-02-09T17:00:00+00:00"
           location="Imperial College London">
        <text>
            Kick off the new decade right.
            Are you ready for IC Hack 20?

            The largest student-run hackathon in the UK returns to Imperial College better than ever before. Running for
            its
            9th consecutive year, we’re bringing over 400 of the UK's most creative and talented students together for
            24
            hours of learning, building, fun, and networking on the weekend of 8-9th February 2020. Come create
            something
            cool!

            IC Hack 20 will be hosted on Imperial College London's South Kensington campus. Students from all
            universities
            can attend!

            The **first batch of tickets** will be released on the **10th of January at 1:30pm GMT**!
            Tickets sell out in seconds, so don't miss out! Did we mention it is completely free?
        </text>
        <links>
            <link href="https://ichack20.eventbrite.com">Tickets (Eventbrite)</link>
            <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/415614812680196/">Facebook</link>
            <link href="https://ichack.org/">Website</link>
        </links>
    </event>


    <sign
            name="Radostin Petrov"
            role="DoCSoc Secretary '19/20"
            facebook="radostin.petrov99">
        Until next time,
    </sign>
</email>