<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.postimg.cc/cLX0zb6V/digestive.jpg"
    alt="Digestive biscuits"
    title="A classic."/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone, hope you've had a great week!

    In this week's digest you can find out more about:
    * joining the DoCSoc committee,
    * Imperial Young Professionals' mentorship programme,
    * LGBT+ Careers Panel
    * and Jane Street Insight Programmes!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IYP Tech Mentorship Program</heading>
  <text>
    The Imperial Young Professionals network have reached out to us to announce
    that applications are open for their IYP Tech Mentorship Program!

    The mentorship program will connect you with current Imperial alumni
    working in software engineering, data science, machine learning and even
    less technical areas such as, business analysts, business development,
    product managers, project manager etc...

    The aim of the program is to help Imperial students get an inside look into
    Tech careers and maximise their chances of landing that dream job.

    The program will run officially through March and April in which time you
    will meet individually with your mentors as well as take part in kick off
    and round-off events to get to know other participants.

    Sound like something you’re interested in?

    [Apply](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/124Rlq9IlGwgCHs1aqPdBuCW20jBG4aBESmmgatt889o/viewform)
    before Friday 26th February.

    ## What is IYP Tech?

    IYP Tech is a program which aims to cultivate a community of Imperial
    Alumni working in Tech and connect them to Imperial students, increasing
    their exposure to various career paths. The IYP Tech program includes a
    series of webinars &amp; panels as well as a mentorship program to increase
    your understanding of what a career in Tech could look like and connect you
    with current alumni working in the field.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>LGBT+ Careers Panel</heading>
  <text>
    Tuesday 23 February 18:30 – 20:00 (GMT)

    February is [LGBT History
    Month](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/campaigns/lgbt-history-month-2021)
    in the UK and as part of our events we’re hosting an LGBT+ Careers Panel in
    partnerships with [IQ, (LGBT+ Student
    Society)](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/activities/a-to-z/iq-imperial-college-lgbt)
    on 23 February from 18:30 – 20:00 GMT. The careers panel will include
    conversations with LGBT+ employees from various organisations including
    AstraZeneca, Arup, Accenture, FTI Consulting and Enterprise.  We’ll hear
    about their careers and explore that it’s possible to be comfortable and
    successful at work while being yourself regardless of sexual orientation or
    the gender identity.

    Any student who identifies as LGBT+ or who is an ally of the community is
    welcome to attend. You can find out more and [book a ticket through
    Eventbrite](https://imperialcollegelondon-lgbtcareerspanel2021.eventbrite.co.uk/).
    You’re welcome to register and access the event using a personal email
    address if you’d like anonymity.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>So you want to run for DoCSoc?</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/I0ULLEJ.png"/>
  <event startDate="2021-02-24T15:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2021-02-24T16:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      So you want to run for DoCSoc? Not sure about which role to run? Have
      questions you want to ask with the current committee members?

      Join us virtually to learn more before you make your decision to stand
      for a DoCSoc Committee position!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://fb.me/e/6qQbXlqOG">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Jane Street Programmes</heading>
  <sponsor company="jane_street">
    ![Discover](https://i.imgur.com/wfYPx6Z.png)

    Discover is a one day Insight-style programme hosted by Jane Street for
    students at any point in their university studies. This is an opportunity
    to learn how math, computer science, and probability concepts have a
    real-world impact on the work we do. Participants will hear from traders
    and technologists to learn how they apply their STEM backgrounds in their
    day to day work at Jane Street. The next Discover session will run on
    Wednesday, 10 March, 2021.

    Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative technology,
    a scientific approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our
    business. Founded in 2000, Jane Street employs more than 1,300 people with
    offices in New York, London, Amsterdam, and Hong Kong. We are always on the
    lookout for great new people to join our team.

    The environment at Jane Street is open, informal, intellectual, and fun.
    The dress code is casual, the kitchen is stocked, and discussions are
    always lively. Teaching and learning are central activities through
    classes, mentoring, and discussion.

    There is no prior knowledge of finance required for this programme — just
    intellectual curiosity and a genuine interest in what a career at Jane
    Street might look like. While this session is virtual, it is intended for
    students currently located in Europe. Interested students can apply below.
    We look forward to meeting you soon!

    [Apply](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-discover?utm_source=email&amp;utm_campaign=discover)

    **The deadline to apply is Thursday, 4th March, 11:59pm GMT.**

    ![Insight](https://i.imgur.com/IbxUepZ.png)

    This April 7th-9th, Jane Street is excited to host our INSIGHT programme
    for students across Europe. We’re inviting self-identifying women and
    gender expansive people to spend three days learning more about what we do
    and how we do it through a set of trading and programming classes and
    activities. Attendees will receive an in-depth look into the ways we use
    maths and computer science, as well as insight into the different roles
    that exist within our firm. Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the program will
    be remote this year.

    In the trading program, students will learn about mathematical and
    financial topics such as probability, market structure, and arbitrage
    through a combination of short lectures, group games, and mock trading
    sessions. These activities are structured to provide a foundation for and a
    broad overview of our work, and there will be plenty of opportunities for
    close interaction with our traders.

    Students selected for the software engineering program will receive an
    in-depth look into the ways we use computer science within our firm. They
    will learn OCaml, and the libraries and tools we use in our daily work, and
    how to put them to use by building a computer game. Participants will also
    learn the fundamentals of electronic trading systems.

    Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that uses innovative technology,
    a scientific approach, and a deep understanding of markets to guide our
    business. We are a global liquidity provider and market maker. With offices
    in New York, London, Hong Kong and Amsterdam, we operate around the clock
    and around the globe.

    Founded in 2000, Jane Street employs over 1300 people. We are always
    recruiting top students and the environment at Jane Street is open,
    informal, intellectual and fun. The dress code is casual and discussions
    are always lively. Teaching and learning are central activities through
    classes, mentoring and discussion.

    Apply here to be considered for a spot in the program.

    [Apply](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-insight-ldn?utm_source=email&amp;utm_campaign=insight)

    After the application deadline, selected applicants will receive an
    invitation to complete a puzzle or coding challenge based on which group
    you applied for.

    **The deadline to apply for this event is 14th March, 11:59pm GMT.** If you
    have any questions, please don't hesitate to email
    JSINSIGHT@janestreet.com.

    Good luck with the application process and we hope to meet you soon!

    ![In Focus](https://i.imgur.com/khFAOX4.png)

    This April 14th-16th, Jane Street is excited to host our IN FOCUS event for
    students in Europe. We're inviting students to spend three days learning
    more about what we do and how we do it through mentorship, programming,
    mock trading, classroom lectures, and activities. Due to the COVID-19
    pandemic, the program will be remote this year.

    This program is for undergraduate students, inclusive of first year and
    penultimate year students, who self-identify with a historically
    underrepresented minority group. It does not require a prior knowledge of
    finance, only an interest in seeing what a career in finance and at Jane
    Street might look like.

    Attendees participating in the software development program will receive an
    in-depth look into the ways we use computer science within our firm. They
    will learn OCaml, and the libraries and tools we use in our daily work, and
    how to put them to use by building a computer game. Participants will also
    learn the fundamentals of electronic trading systems and write a program
    that trades on a simulated stock exchange.

    Attendees participating in the trading program will learn about
    mathematical and financial topics such as probability, market structure,
    and arbitrage through a combination of short classroom lectures, group
    games, and mock trading sessions. These activities are structured to
    provide a foundation for and a broad overview of our work, and there will
    be plenty of opportunities for close interaction with our traders.

    Apply here to be considered for a spot in the program.

    [Apply](https://www.janestreet.com/apply-in-focus-ldn)

    After the application deadline, selected applicants will receive an
    invitation to complete a puzzle or coding challenge based on which group
    you applied for.

    **The deadline to apply for this event is 14th March @ 11:59pm GMT**. If
    you have any questions, please do not hesitate to email
    FOCUS@janestreet.com.
  </sponsor>


  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
