<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/CP3whIO.jpg"
    alt="Shortbread cookies on a tabletop"
    title="Emoh Edam"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Hope you've had a great week!

    In this digest you'll find info about a Virtual Games Social organised by
    Women in Computing, an update from The Equality, Diversity and Culture
    Committee and opportunities from our sponsors.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Women in Computing - Virtual Games Social</heading>
  <text>
    ![WiC Poster](https://i.imgur.com/I7FD8Lw.png)

    Join WiC for a **Virtual Games Social** to celebrate International Day of Women
    and Girls in Science! Meet new people and socialise over board games with a
    host of Women in STEM groups across UK universities.

    Running over two days: on [**WEDNESDAY, FEBRUARY 10, 2021 AT 7 PM
    UTC**](https://www.facebook.com/events/340736066998711) and on [**SATURDAY,
    FEBRUARY 13, 2021 AT 1 PM
    UTC**](https://www.facebook.com/events/854793095366333)

    If you'd like to attend, [**sign up
    here**](https://forms.gle/4NVdoUij6jHPNivG7). All genders welcome!

    In collaboration with ICL WiM, ICL WiP, ICL WiEE, ICL WSET, Cambridge WiS,
    Cambridge WiC, Cambridge WiP, KCL WiS, Warwick WES, Durham WiS, Edinburgh
    Hoppers, Manchester WiSE
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>The Equality, Diversity and Culture Committee</heading>
  <text>
    Do you want to help encourage diversity and equality in Computing and
    represent your view? The Equality, Diversity and Culture Committee (EDCC)
    strive to continually maintain and improve equality and diversity amongst
    staff and students. Their current objectives are:

    No staff or student should be disadvantaged because of their gender,
    ethnicity, sexual orientation, disability or any other protected
    characteristics (Equality Act 2010).

    * The Department should provide an inclusive environment for all staff and
    students.

    * The Department should strive for diversity of staff and students along
    all dimensions.

    * The EDCC welcomes anyone to come and attend their bi-termly meeting to
    discuss such matters - all discussions are open!

    If you feel you have experienced something you would like to discuss
    however do not feel comfortable attending the meeting please do one or all
    of the following:

    * Talk to your year reps as they can discuss the issue for you.

    * Submit anonymous feedback by form here:
    https://edcc.doc.ic.ac.uk/contact/

    * Email anonymously to doc-equality@imperial.ac.uk - the exchange will be
      kept private
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities - Upcoming Spring Events</heading>
  <sponsor company="citadel">
    Citadel &amp; Citadel Securities have some exciting events coming up! You
    can find event descriptions below, please see the flyers attached for
    further details.

    Europe Regional Datathon (February 15 – 22): do you love working with data
    and building data driven apps to problem solve? Then this is for you! Work
    in a team to tackle challenges that touch the global markets, with the
    opportunity to win cash prizes and reach the Data Open final.

    Europe Regional Terminal (March 8 - 15): a games based coding competition
    working in teams - watch your algorithm compete and have the opportunity to
    win cash prizes!
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Bank of America Quantitative Management Analyst Programme (QMAP)</heading>
  <sponsor company="baml">
    The programme consists of two one-year rotations in quantitative
    disciplines along with customized training and continuing education. Upon
    completion of the program, QMAP graduates have a broad range of global
    career opportunities within the bank.

    As an analyst within Quantitative Management based in London, you will:

    * Join a 2 year rotational programme focusing on capital markets,
    instrument pricing/valuation, and counterparty credit risk management

    * Apply quantitative analysis to business problems

    * Develop solutions for Derivatives and Exotics, Price Valuation,
    Model Risk Management, Risk Analytics, Automated Solutions, Counterparty
    Credit Risk

    * Implement solutions applying both qualitative and quantitative
    aspects in capital markets, finance, and risk management

    * Use modelling techniques to quantify and determine solutions to
    business problems

    * Gain real, in-depth experience applying quantitative knowledge to
    specific financial challenges

    Apply
    [here](https://bankcampuscareers.tal.net/vx/brand-0/candidate/so/pm/1/pl/1/opp/6182-EMEA-London-Global-Quantitative-Management-Program-Full-Time-Analyst-Programme/en-GB)

    Application Closing Date: 26th March 2021
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Palantir Scholarship and Event Opportunities!</heading>
  <sponsor company="palantir">
    [Palantir Scholarship](https://www.palantir.com/students/scholarship/) and
    [Event
    Opportunities](http://www.palantir.events/palantirevents-spring2021)!

    At Palantir, we strongly believe that true innovation stagnates in the
    absence of representation, and it's our mission to contribute to meaningful
    growth and change within the technology sector. As a part of this mission
    we launched our Scholarship programs to provide opportunities for future
    leaders in tech to thrive and impact the world through their work.

    The 2021 application period is now open and we are accepting applications.
    We strongly encourage you to apply!

    ### [Women in Technology Scholarship](https://www.palantir.com/students/scholarship/wit-europe/)

    ### [Global Impact Scholarship](https://www.palantir.com/students/scholarship/global-impact/)

    Lastly, we invite you to learn more about life at Palantir, straight from
    our internal affinity group communities. We will host an information
    session and product demo in February, and discussions on topics of identity
    in March. We will share event dates and details in the coming weeks - [sign
    up here](http://www.palantir.events/palantirevents-spring2021) if you'd
    like to be included in the event updates!

    For any questions, please view our
    [website](https://www.palantir.com/students/) for more details and contact
    information. You can also find our current openings for interns and new
    graduates listed on our [careers page](https://www.palantir.com/careers/).
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
