<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Summer internships at Thought Machine" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <text>
    **tl;dr 10-week software engineering summer internships for
    second and third years, London-based or remote depending on
    COVID, deadline 7th February**

    We're currently searching for the perfect candidates to join us
    for a paid 10-week software engineering internship this summer.

    You will work in a team within Engineering, using cutting-edge
    technology to deliver both client-facing and internal projects.
    You will develop ownership and responsibility for your own work
    and learn how to build software in an agile manner during weekly
    sprints. Our new program will support your growth and
    development whilst working alongside some of the brightest minds
    in FinTech.

    📅 Internships will run from Monday 5th July 2021 to Friday 10th
    September 2021📅

    💰 This is a paid internship paying £30,000 pro rata, plus
    benefits 💰

    🎓 We’ll consider applications from second and third year
    students studying Computing, JMC, EIE or some other engineering
    subject 🎓

    🌍 In our central London office if COVID allows, otherwise
    remote 🦠

    ⚠️ **The deadline for applications is Sunday 7th February 2021** ⚠️

    ### Who are we?

    Thought Machine is solving one of the biggest problems in
    banking. Since we launched in 2014, our mission has been to
    liberate banks from outdated, legacy technology which makes it
    difficult for them to innovate in a world where the biggest tech
    brands such as Netflix and Spotify are operating in the cloud.

    Our flagship product, Vault, is a cloud-native, core banking
    engine built to run any type of bank - from established global
    banks all the way to new challenger banks. Vault is used by the
    likes of Lloyds Bank, Atom Bank, Curve and Standard Chartered.

    With a founding team drawn from Google, we have a deep culture
    of engineering excellence and we believe it is this which
    delivers a solution compelling enough to engender a seismic
    shift in the banking industry.

    We were ranked as the most desirable London fintech to work at
    by Sifted when comparing employee reviews on Glassdoor and named
    in Fintech 50 (2020). We pride ourselves on having an excellent
    internal culture, where we take cultural fit as important as
    technical fit when we make new hires. At Thought Machine, we
    strive hard to create a fast-paced, supportive and fun working
    environment to enable the team to produce the best technical
    work in the industry.

    ### How to apply

    Apply through the [DoCSoc Sponsors Portal](https://portal.docsoc.co.uk/)
    or send your CV to internships-2021@thoughtmachine.net. Don't worry about a
    cover letter.

    If you have any questions, drop us an email at
    internships-2021@thoughtmachine.net.

    **The deadline to apply is Sunday 7th February 2021.**

    ### Benefits
    * On top of your £30,000 pro rata salary, you will also get:
    * Pension plan
    * Private health insurance (including dental &amp; optical)
    * Discounted onsite gym
    * Sports and hobby clubs, subsidised by Thought Machine
    * All the latest tech you need
    * Start the day properly with fresh fruit and cereals\*
    * Huge range of healthy (and not so healthy) snacks, smoothies, juice, tea, coffee and soft drinks on tap\*
    * A talented &amp; experienced team as your colleagues
    * An environment where we encourage learning and progress
    * Weekly food pop up\*
    * Monthly social with arcade games\*
    \* COVID-allowing 🤞🤞🤞

    ### Requirements
    * You are studying towards a Computing, JMC, EIE, or other Engineering degree and in your second or third year.
    * You have some experience and a passion for one of, Python, Go, Java or building applications with JavaScript (e.g. React).
    * You have contributed to an open-source project or taken part in a University project of considerable scale (this includes things like Pintos and WACC compiler).
    * We will give preference to those graduating in 2022.

    You should also be excited to work with new technologies, push your
    engineering skills to the limit, and be ready to work across engineering,
    design and business development to build the next generation of financial
    applications.

    Thought Machine is committed to making a measurable positive impact on
    people's everyday lives. We are an equal opportunity employer and value
    diversity at our company. We actively hire for cultural growth. We welcome
    people of all ages, backgrounds and value people who take a journey unique
    to them. We provide everyone with equal access to professional development.
    You are encouraged to apply even if your experience doesn't precisely match
    the job description.
  </text>
</email>
