<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/7JMDf3l.png"
    alt="A stroopwafel sitting in a teacup"
    title="A cupful of waffles"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Hope everyone's exams went well and you've had some time to relax!

    In this week's digest you can find out about:
    * potential campus meetups for freshers and final year students
    * Women In Science Mentoring Scheme
    * Cocktail Masterclass Date Change
    * a Software in Biotech talk hosted by DoCSoc and SynBIC
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>First and Final Year Campus Meetups</heading>
  <text>
    We are hoping to host campus meetups for first and final year students once
    the social distancing restrictions are lifted.

    If you are interested in attending, please fill out the relevant form to
    help us plan the event:
    * First Year: https://forms.office.com/r/6N2uL0ixzx
    * Final Year: https://forms.office.com/r/2v8zGEJTcX
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>WiC – Women In Science Mentoring Scheme</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/3u1cMp8.png"/>
  <text>
    We are really excited to join the new Women In Science Mentoring Scheme, in
    collaboration with Women in Science societies from the Universities of
    Bristol, Cambridge, East Anglia, Glasgow, Warwick and York!

    There are 3 tiers in the program:

    1\) The mentoring of postgraduates by postdocs

    2\) The mentoring of undergraduates by postgraduates

    3\) The mentoring of female and non-binary students in years 10-13/S4-6 by
    undergraduates

    To be eligible as a mentor or mentee, you must be a self-identifying female
    or non-binary student or academic at the University of Bristol, Cambridge,
    East Anglia, Glasgow, York, or Warwick or Imperial College London, or be a
    self-identifying female or non-binary student in years 10-13/S4-6.

    Whether you are in need of some advice or want to help other people, this
    scheme has an option for you! Pairings will be made in mid-June.

    Check out this link for more information and to sign up:
    https://lnkd.in/dZSHJm4
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Cocktail Masterclass Date Change</heading>
  <text>
    Just a reminder that due to unforeseen circumstances, we've had to push the
    cocktail masterclass to Saturday 22nd of May at 6pm.

    Sorry for any inconvenience, we hope you can still join us then! If you can
    no longer make it please [get in touch with us](mailto:docsoc@ic.ac.uk).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Industry Talk: Software in Biotech</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/MRd2qKY.png"/>
  <event startDate="2021-05-25T17:00:00+01:00"
    endDate="2021-05-25T18:30:00+01:00">
  <text>
    Biotech companies are reaching unprecedented heights of innovation by
    embracing software, machine learning, and robotics in every part of their
    work. From genetic engineering and drug discovery to autonomous labs, there
    is a growing need for software engineers in the life sciences. Join us for
    an exciting industry talk co-hosted by Imperial College DoCSoc and SynBIC
    to hear from leaders in the field about how software engineers are making
    an impact and what the future will look like.

    Speakers:
    * Yaoyu Yang - Principal Software Engineer, Ginkgo Bioworks
    * Zeoy Herm - Senior Scientis, Ryffin
    * Daniel O'Donovan - AI Technical Lead, Healx

    You can register on Hopin [here](https://hopin.com/events/software-in-biotech).
  </text>
  <links>
    <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2918344491770968/">Facebook</link>
  </links>
</event>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
