<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/KoQ8VGB.jpg"
    alt="A stack of sesame crackers"
    title="Crisp"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    As we're approaching the end of '20/21, this week's digest brings you info
    on the DoC Summer Term Wellbeing Survey, WiC's list of awards and
    opportunities and G-Research's Women in Finance event for PhD students.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Summer Term Wellbeing Survey</heading>
  <text>
    Filling out this survey about your mental health and wellbeing this term
    will help your representatives and DoC address any issues.

    https://bit.ly/2TOxMOf
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Women in Computing – awards and opportunities</heading>
  <text>
    In search of various opportunities in the past year, two DoC girls (Christy
    Chan [EIE III, WiC] and Chloe Lau [Computing II, DoCSoc]) have compiled a
    list of awards, opportunities and mentorships for female, non-binary and/or
    ethnic minority students here:
    https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1eR953pIvhC4ZXbDwlOygmBXQUcfRdm7KTSSlK8OmD1o/edit

    If you are interested in contributing to the list please contact
    christy.chan18@imperial.ac.uk or chloe.lau19@imperial.ac.uk.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>G-Research – Women in Quant Finance – August 2021</heading>
  <sponsor company="g_research">
    G-Research is committed to growing the range of voices and perspectives
    within our industry. We are therefore excited to announce the continuation
    of our Women’s Engagement Programme with our latest Women in Quant Finance
    event. After two very successful events in Europe and North America, our
    next event will be focused on the UK.

    This event will include a range of introductory and technical talks, as
    well as collaborative skills courses and interview prep sessions. Our goal
    is to give women studying for a PhD the chance to learn more about working
    in quantitative research in finance, while providing them with the chance
    to build a network of their peers.

    The event will be held at our offices in Central London, with an
    introductory dinner on Sunday 22 August, followed by a day of talks and
    workshops from 09:30 to 18:00 on Monday 23 August.

    The main day will feature a mix of activities, including:

    * A talk by one of our quant researchers, focused on the financial industry
    * A panel discussion and Q&amp;A session
    * An interactive case study, giving you the chance to get hands-on with the type of work we do
    * A drinks and networking session
    * A games night

    If you are selected to take part in the event, we will cover your
    accommodation (including the night of the 23rd), food, and travel expenses.
    You will also be guaranteed an interview with G-Research (for either an
    internship or permanent position).

    More information about the event and application process can be found on
    our website
    [here](https://www.gresearch.co.uk/article/women-in-quant-finance-august-2021/).
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
