<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/dLrsu4d.jpg"
    alt="Peanut Butter Biscuits"
    title="Your weekly digest, best enjoyed with some quality PB!"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone, hope you're doing well!

    IC Hello World, our introductory hackathon, is coming up soon and the first
    batch of tickets is going to be released tomorrow at 1pm! Read on to find
    out how to get yours!

    With International Women's Day just around the corner, below you can find
    out about events taking place during Women at Imperial Week 2021.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Hello World!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/4sna7QA.png"/>
  <text>
    ### Want to get a chance to participate in our introductory hackathon IC Hello World?

    Remember to get your tickets at our Eventbrite on Monday 1pm GMT!

    ➡️ [**Get tickets here!**](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ic-hello-world-tickets-143461698803?utm-medium=discovery&amp;utm-campaign=social&amp;utm-content=attendeeshare&amp;aff=escb&amp;utm-source=cp&amp;utm-term=listing)

    This is a great chance for you to join your first hackathon (virtually), we
    welcome everyone of any background from Imperial!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Women at Imperial Week 2021</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/H5muSit.png"/>
  <text>
    Women at Imperial is an annual event that takes place around International
    Women’s Day (8 March). Over the course of a week we celebrate female staff
    and students at Imperial, past and present, and raise awareness of the
    support available in College for women.

    You can find more details about the upcoming events
    [**here**](https://www.imperial.ac.uk/equality/activities/women-at-imperial/).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>WiC - Create and deploy your online CV</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/7KUOF8d.png"/>
  <text>
    In this increasingly online world, personal webpages have become key to
    showcase one’s qualifications and knowledge.

    Women in Computing is inviting everyone to take part in this event to learn
    how to create your own personal website using GitHub pages or Wix - for you
    to choose.

    The structure of the event is as follows:
    * Intro: 15 minutes
    * Website building: 50 minutes - where you will have time to build your own website
    * Showcase: 15 minutes - where volunteers will present their final product!

    Women highly encouraged to take part!

    The session will be facilitated by:
    * Hanne Hoitzing - Cyber Security Data Scientist, Imperial Ph.D. alumna
    * Aydan Gasimova - Imperial College London
    * Guadalupe Gonzalez - Imperial College London

    Please register
    [here](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/build-your-online-cv-tickets-144660157425).

    Event in partnership with the Imperial College Developer Student Clubs -
    [DSC webpage](https://dsc.community.dev/imperial-college-london/).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>WiC - What can your voice reveal about you</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/tZDiS4L.png"/>
  <text>
    Voice recognition systems have a wide use within businesses, in the medical
    field, and even in your home! Although speech technologies are commonly
    used to transcribe speech samples to text, each individual’s voice can be
    analyzed to reveal their emotional state, their gender, their accent, and
    even underlying medical conditions.

    What to know more? In this session, we’ll see how speech signals work, and
    move on to Python code to see how they can be used to infer personal
    attributes. We’ll also try some machine learning techniques that help hide
    those revealing features.

    If you ever wondered how speech processing works in practice, join Dominika
    on Friday 12th March

    Dominika Woszczyk is a 2nd Year PhD student at Imperial College working on
    security for voice services at Apss Lab, supervised by Dr. Soteris
    Demetriou. She completed her MSc at the University of Southampton in
    Artificial Intelligence and her BSc in Data Science at Maastricht
    University, The Netherlands. Her interests lie in speech processing,
    Natural Language Understanding, and applying it to the real world, as well
    as entrepreneurship.
    https://dominikawoszczyk.com

    Please register
    [here](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/what-your-voice-can-reveal-about-you-tickets-144472638551).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc x WiC - Diversity in Industry</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/pCw17IV.png"/>
  <event startDate="2021-03-10T15:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2021-03-10T16:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      As part of the Women @ Imperial series.

      DoCSoc, partnered with Women in Computing (WiC) is delighted to invite
      you for a Panel session, which consists of questions around Diversity in
      the Software Engineering and Financial industries, alongside a Q&amp;A
      session.

      We also invite you to send us questions to ask at the session (the form
      will close on Tuesday at 6pm): https://forms.gle/GjsfZGNMPReAMDxV8
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/267756571396069">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Optiver - Technology Insights Days</heading>
  <sponsor company="optiver">
    ![Poster](https://i.imgur.com/6pMEkAh.png)

    The Optiver Technology Insights days are a fantastic chance to discover
    where your skills and interests can find a home at one of the world’s
    leading tech driven market-making firms. During the 2-day experience,
    you’ll get a clear understanding of what we do and how we do it in an
    ultra-high-performance environment. You’ll also get to speak directly with
    our engineers and traders and learn more about their journeys. We also have
    multiple interactive activities planned that’ll give you hands-on
    experience, including the chance to create algorithm in order to trade on
    our very own simulated trading platform Optibook.

    Please note:

    * In order to be eligible to apply you need to be a first-year student
    (graduating in 2023)

    * The virtual event will take place on the 8th and 9th April 2021

    * Please apply as soon as possible by submitting your CV and cover letter.
    Our recruiters will reach out to you regarding the next steps

    * Please note that applications without cover letter will not be taken into
    consideration


    You can find more details and apply
    [**here**](https://www.optiver.com/working-at-optiver/career-opportunities/2935264/)
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Connect with Jane Street</heading>
  <sponsor company="jane_street">
    ![Poster](https://i.imgur.com/VQMW8sI.png)

    ## Connect with Jane Street!

    ### Friday 12th March @ 1:00pm - 2:00pm GMT

    ### Event:
    Virtual Employee Panel

    ### Audience:
    Self identifying women, transgender, and gender-expansive students

    Interested in learning more about Jane Street and how we think? Join us for
    this 60-minute virtual event!

    We invite women, transgender, and gender-expansive people to join us and
    meet Streeters on our employee panel. You will have an opportunity to learn
    about the roles within our firm and how we solve challenges at Jane Street.
    This event is for students at any point in their academic career from any
    degree background.

    Please sign up by **Wednesday 10th March** if you're interested in
    attending.  We will confirm attendees and provide Zoom meeting details by
    Thursday 11th March. We hope to see you there!

    ## [Sign up](https://forms.gle/JcNUiX5nXRz6cpnz9)

    **Want to check out Jane Street ahead of the event?** Visit our [Virtual
    Info Booth](https://www.janestreet.com/join-jane-street/info-booth/).
    Navigate to video content, Signals &amp; Threads podcast, office tours,
    puzzles, and more!
  </sponsor>


  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
