<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/mnKzNFN.jpg"
    alt="A heart-shaped waffle on a blurry background"
    title="Happy Valentine's Day!"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Hope you're doing well!

    In this week's digest you'll find updates about the Women's Panel and the
    EDCC as well as info about our Research Q&amp;A and Freshers' Games Night.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Women's Panel</heading>
  <text>
    Thursday 18th February – 18:00 – 19:30 (GMT)

    Meet inspirational women ready tell you about how they carved their unique
    career paths and who’ll be available to answer your questions. This event
    is hosted on MS Teams and will include brief introductions followed by a
    chat-show style discussion and questions submitted by the audience.

    Our inspiring female speakers include panelists from:

    * Institution of Civil Engineers

    * Facebook

    * Imperial College London

    The event is organised by the Careers Service and will be co-hosted by Pria
    Pretheshan, ICU Gender Equality Officer.

    Booking is required via JobsLive to receive the join link, book here -
    https://imperial.targetconnect.net/leap/event.html?id=15509&amp;service=Careers+Service
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>The Equality, Diversity and Culture Committee</heading>
  <text>
    Do you want to help encourage diversity and equality in Computing and
    represent your view? The Equality, Diversity and Culture Committee (EDCC)
    strive to continually maintain and improve equality and diversity amongst
    staff and students. Their current objectives are:

    No staff or student should be disadvantaged because of their gender,
    ethnicity, sexual orientation, disability or any other protected
    characteristics (Equality Act 2010).

    * The Department should provide an inclusive environment for all staff and
    students.

    * The Department should strive for diversity of staff and students along
    all dimensions.

    * The EDCC welcomes anyone to come and attend their bi-termly meeting to
    discuss such matters - all discussions are open!

    If you feel you have experienced something you would like to discuss
    however do not feel comfortable attending the meeting please do one or all
    of the following:

    * Talk to your year reps as they can discuss the issue for you.

    * Submit anonymous feedback by form here:
    https://edcc.doc.ic.ac.uk/contact/

    * Email anonymously to doc-equality@imperial.ac.uk - the exchange will be
      kept private
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>To Research or Not To Research?</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/HPrGer4.png"/>
  <event startDate="2021-02-17T15:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2021-02-17T16:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      This is the question!

      Have you thought about doing a PhD and/or going into academia but you’re
      a bit uncertain what this is going to be like?

      We’ll be hosting Q&amp;A panel between academics and people that have a
      lot of experience in the industry (Robert Chatley, Paul Kelly and many
      others) answering your questions about a research career. Be that in
      academia or private companies, this type of career choice usually comes
      along with a lot of stereotypes and myths so we’re here to break it for
      you!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/870217897099937">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Freshers' Games Night</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/FW5f3kQ.png"/>
  <event startDate="2021-02-17T18:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2021-02-17T20:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      We'll be hosting a games night for all 1st years next Wednesday on
      Discord!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://discord.gg/hc24ud6">Discord</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
