<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/J1l814I.jpg"
    alt="Churros served in a newspaper"
    title="Curly biscuits?"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone, hope you're doing well!

    As we're entering the last week of the term, we're looking for 3rd/4th year
    undergraduates and postgraduates to become mentors at our upcoming
    hackathon - IC Hello World. You can find some more details and the sign up
    link below.

    Read on to find out about upcoming events by American Express, Optiver and
    Bloomberg!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Hello World - mentors wanted!</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/a4iAhvN.png"/>
  <text>
    ### Are you a coding wiz? Willing to exchange some help for some introductory hackers for some free food?

    [Sign up here](https://forms.office.com/r/esNJL3v3dp) to be a mentor at IC
    Hello World! We welcome 3rd, 4th, and postgrad students to help out!

    All mentors will receive a £20 Deliveroo or Amazon voucher. The sign up
    form will close Monday at noon.

    We will be hosting our first meeting next Wednesday at 2pm and will go
    through the logistics throughout the event.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Upcoming Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc x AmEx - PowerPoint Karaoke</heading>
  <image src="https://i.imgur.com/mLsulC4.png"/>
  <event startDate="2021-03-24T16:00:00+00:00"
    endDate="2021-03-24T18:00:00+00:00">
    <text>
      Join American Express and DoCSoc for an amazing night!

      You might ask - what is PowerPoint Karaoke?

      Well, PowerPoint-Karaoke (also known as Battle Decks) is a game with very
      simple rules:

      The presenter gets on stage and must convincingly present a deck of
      PowerPoint slides he has never seen before.

      The main purpose is to have as much fun as possible.

      No preparations required – but come over and have fun!
    </text>
    <links>
      <link href="https://www.facebook.com/events/742440589804882/">Facebook</link>
    </links>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Sponsor Notices</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Clash of the solvers</heading>
  <sponsor company="optiver">
    The exciting world of electronic trading is a problem solver’s paradise.
    Optiver, one of the world’s leading global market makers, will be hosting a
    remote coding challenge for University students. Get ready for Clash Of The
    Solvers!

    This is an excellent opportunity to test your coding skills under pressure.
    Using your knowledge of Python, you’ll develop a trading algorithm and put
    it to work against the other competing teams on Optiver’s proprietary
    simulated trading exchange: Optibook. You’ll get to experience what modern
    trading is really like and get a taste of the complex problems our traders
    and engineers face every day. The members of the top performing teams will
    be awarded with some great prizes!

    Our mission is to constantly improve financial markets across the globe. We
    do this with a team of some of the brightest minds around. They collaborate
    every day to push technological and analytical possibility. Your future
    could be among them as a graduate trader or software engineer.

    The event details are as follows: Date – Thursday 15 April 2021 Venue –
    Virtual Meeting via Zoom

    To apply for a place at the coding challenge click on below button.

    We look forward to welcoming you and seeing you perform.

    [**Sign up now**](https://www.optiver.com/clash-of-the-solvers/)
  </sponsor>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Join us for Bloomberg's Engineering Expo!</heading>
  <sponsor company="bloomberg">
    At Bloomberg, we strive to create a working environment that values
    difference, fosters inclusion and promotes collaboration. Our global
    community of diverse engineers take on some of the world’s most interesting
    and important technical challenges.

    We are running a Bloomberg Engineering Expo and workshop on Wednesday, 24 March 2021.

    ### What to expect?

    * Find out what we do at Bloomberg and what it is like to work in our
    London office

    * See how the Bloomberg Terminal works

    * Meet our interns and graduates

    * Gain tips on how you can apply and interview for a role in tech with
    convenience

    * Take part in Bpuzzled challenge - Bpuzzled is a puzzle competition
    created by Bloomberg engineers, where teams use problem solving, creative
    thinking, and teamwork to solve challenging and intricate puzzles

    ### When is it?

    Date: Wednesday, 24 March 2021

    [**Register here**](https://tinyurl.com/yc9caj2k)

    Feel free to join any of the sessions:

    * 11:00am - 12:00pm London, UK time | Intro into BB and Terminal Demo

    * 12:05pm : 13:05pm London, UK time | Meet Our Interns &amp; Grads - Panel Discussion

    * 16:00pm - 17:00pm London, UK time | Technical Interview Workshop

    * 17:00pm - 18:00pm London, UK time | Bpuzzled Challenge
  </sponsor>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
