<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Weekly Digest">
  <image width="90"
    src="https://i.imgur.com/10wd0ks.png"
    alt="Gingerbread figure on snow"
    title="Enjoy the snow!"/>
  <hr/>

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Welcome back to Imperial!

    Hopefully you've managed to get up to speed in the first two weeks. Read on
    below to get the latest updates about DoCSoc.
  </text>

  <hr/>
  <text>## Announcements</text>
  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Constitution Update</heading>
  <text>
    Last week the DoCSoc Committee has ratified the following changes to the
    society's constitution (with additions **in bold** and deletions ~~crossed out~~):

  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>

    _Hackathons and Large Events Coordinator_ will become _Hackathons
    Coordinator_ with updated job description:

    “The Hackathons ~~and Large Events~~ Coordinator shall oversee
    the long-term organisational planning of annually recurring
    hackathons ~~not covered by the Social Events Coordinator,
    focusing on~~ **such as** IC Hack and Health Hack. ~~(liaising
    with the GameDev Events Coordinator), and providing additional
    oversight to other large events, such as the Welcome Fair and
    Sponsors’ Exhibition.~~”

  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>

    _GameDev Events Coordinator_ will become _Software Development Coordinator_
    with updated job description:

    “The Software Development Coordinator shall oversee the activities and
    events of the society related to **software and game development
    initiatives,** including hardware loans to members, **CTF activities and
    the DoCSoc Software Foundation.**”

  </text>
  <hr/>
  <text>

    _Vice President_ will get constitutional financial resposibility rights and
    will get Welcome Fair and Sponsors’ Exhibition responsibilities with the
    updated job description:

    “The Vice President shall oversee the day to day operations of the society
    **and assist the Treasurer in carrying out the financial duties of the
    society, including, but not limited to, approving claims, purchase orders,
    credit card requests and internal charges. They shall also lead the
    organisation of large events, such as the Welcome Fair and Sponsors’
    Exhibition**”
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>The Equality, Diversity and Culture Committee</heading>
  <text>
    Do you want to help encourage diversity and equality in Computing and
    represent your view? The Equality, Diversity and Culture Committee (EDCC)
    strive to continually maintain and improve equality and diversity amongst
    staff and students. Their current objectives are:

    No staff or student should be disadvantaged because of their gender,
    ethnicity, sexual orientation, disability or any other protected
    characteristics (Equality Act 2010).

    * The Department should provide an inclusive environment for all staff and
    students.

    * The Department should strive for diversity of staff and students along
    all dimensions.

    * The EDCC welcomes anyone to come and attend their bi-termly meeting to
    discuss such matters - all discussions are open!

    If you feel you have experienced something you would like to discuss
    however do not feel comfortable attending the meeting please do one or all
    of the following:

    * Talk to your year reps as they can discuss the issue for you.

    * Submit anonymous feedback by form here:
    https://edcc.doc.ic.ac.uk/contact/

    * Email anonymously to doc-equality@imperial.ac.uk - the exchange will be
      kept private
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <sign name="Stefan Radziuk"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '20/21"
    linkedin="stefanradziuk">
    Until next time,
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
