<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Netcraft Industrial Placements (Computing/EIE/JMC)" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <sponsor company="netcraft">
    **Looking for a six-month or four-month MEng industrial placement?** Netcraft is keen to receive applications for spring/summer 2022.

    Projects can involve working on a range of commercial services extending Netcraft’s network exploration and internet security services.

    Netcraft provides services to internet infrastructure, financial services, large enterprises, and governments in over fifty countries, including six of the world’s ten largest companies by market capitalisation, eleven of the top fifty banks, and five governments. In the UK, our services are used by the British Government and seven of the eight constituents of the FTSE-350 Banking index. Netcraft is positioned at the epicentre of the battle against cybercrime; we currently perform takedowns for three of the ten most phished companies on the internet and in aggregate against around 30% of all phishing attacks, running at around one takedown per minute.

    We’re looking to recruit high-performing software developers to join our team in [Westminster](https://goo.gl/maps/yEveRdTcrxRuiCaL6) or [Bath](https://goo.gl/maps/tkWptMuyZLABwsaq5).

    Important attributes in candidates include:

    - A broad knowledge of internet technology, together with an attention to detail, and a desire to find things out empirically rather than rely on conjecture.
    - A keen interest in network security, data mining &amp; machine learning, or web-based user interfaces.
    - Demonstrable programming ability and experience.
    - Prior experience with any of MySQL, Perl, Go, Python, PHP, Git, Puppet, Amazon Web Services, JavaScript, CSS, or Unix systems programming is useful but not essential.
    

    Apply by emailing your CV to [cv@netcraft.com](mailto:cv@netcraft.com). If you would like to find out more, please see our [recruitment booklet](https://netcraft.com/NetcraftRecruitmentBooklet.pdf).
  </sponsor>
</email>
