<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="DoCSoc Weekly Digest" agenda="true" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    Welcome to another week of DoCSoc events... (but this time it's spooky?) 🎃👻
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## This Week's Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>👻 DoCSoc Halloween Treasure Hunt 🎉</heading>
  <image src="https://imgur.com/hEaAP2P.jpg"></image>
  <event startDate="2024-10-30T14:30:00"
    endDate="2024-10-22T19:30:00"
    location="Robert Raikes Statue (WC2R 0BP)">
    <text>
      Calling all DoCSoc members, friends, and even your non-DoCSoc +1s for an unforgettable Halloween treasure hunt! It's the perfect chance to dive into a puzzle-filled journey through London's hidden gems.

      Updates to team formation 🎫: Non-DoCSoc guests are welcome, as long as at least 25% of the team are DoCSoc members. Teams of 2 are also allowed!

      📅 Tickets are now released on the Union Shop alongside Ticket Tailor - Get them here! (A DoCSoc member will need to purchase tickets for non-DoCSoc participants.)

      Gather your team of 2-6 people, meet us at the Robert Raikes Statue at 14:30 on the 30th, and prepare for an adventure of clues, mysteries, and fun! 

      Plus, enjoy free boba 🧋🧋  and pizzas 🍕🍕  to fuel your quest - see you there!

      Signup [here](https://buytickets.at/docsoc/1444584/r/mailshot)
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>IC Hack 25 Long-term Voluntunteer Information Session MOVED</heading>
  <text>
    You may have seen my message last week, but we've had to delay the session a week. The new date is Monday 4th November. See some information below in case you missed last week's digest.

    IT BEGINS! Want to help organise an event with more than 550 participants, that takes over the whole campus next February? One of Imperial's largest, most complex events? The one event to rule them all?

    Monday 4th starts the organisation for ICHack 2025, the UK's largest student-ran hackathon. No matter what your skills or talents - we have a team for you:

    Great at making merchandise and graphics designs? Join our Branding team! [(signups already open!)](https://forms.gle/TQpRzPDgPjZmtWzx9)
    Like food? Entertainment? Bar nights? Join our Hacker Experience team!
    And finally, want to boss all of those people around? Join our Logistics team!

    Find out more about all the roles you can help with, and how you can join us, Monday 4th - no event signup required.
  </text>

  <heading>Merch Drop and Collection Timings</heading>
  <text>
    Our merch is still available for purchase on [the union shop](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/student-groups/119)!

    If you're a fresher and haven't collected your freshers merch yetor you ordered merch from our summer drop last year and haven't collected it, you can also grab it then.
    
    ## Collection slots
    
    - Monday 28th Oct 4:15pm-6pm, Huxley 315
    - Thursday 31st Oct, 3:15pm-4:45pm, Huxley 315
    - Monday 4th Nov, 4:15pm-6pm, Huxley 315
    - Friday 8th Nov, 2:30pm-5pm, Huxley 218
  </text>
  
  <hr/>

  <text>## Student Society/Project/Event Showcase</text>

  <text>
    Every week or so we'll be showcasing a cool student society, project or event. Please email us if you want your cool society/project/event to be featured!

    Please see a message below from ic neurotech society
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Neurotech Society</heading>
  <text>
    The Imperial Neurotechnology society are putting on the second workshop of their 'Introduction to Neurotech' series, designed to give people of all backgrounds a foundation in the brain sciences and engineering used throughout the field. The 'Neurotech 102' workshop is all about the brain, covering:

    the foundations of neuroscience (the structure of the brain, how it is navigated, and what regions are responsible for what)
    an introduction to 'philosophy of mind' and what the mind/body problem is
    open questions in neuroscience, and how solving them will impact the world of Neurotech in the future
    The event is free, and open to all, irrespective of whether you have signed up to the society on the union page (although that is free and we highly recommend everyone to do so)!

    It will be on next Thursday, October 31st at 18:15 in RSM 1.31. We will post all communication about the event on our WhatsApp channel which can be joined here: https://chat.whatsapp.com/Ggk05q88JQR6doSkp8cApx

    Since it is Halloween after all there is a costume contest, with the best costume winning a pint (alcoholic or non-alcoholic) and curly fries!

    If you'd like any more information at all please get in contact with us via our email, neurotec@ic.ac.uk, or our Instagram @icl_neurotech!
  </text>
  

  <sign name="Aidan Madge"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '24/25">
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>

</email>
