<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Halloween Treasure Hunt" agenda="false" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We're happy to announce our Halloween treasure hunt! See below...
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/hEaAP2P.jpg"></image>
  <event startDate="2024-10-30T14:30:00"
    endDate="2024-10-22T19:30:00"
    location="Robert Raikes Statue (WC2R 0BP)">
    <text>
      Join the DoCSoc Halloween Treasure Hunt - A Puzzle-Filled Journey Through London!

      This Halloween, gather your DoCSoc family and friends for a treasure hunt through the streets of London! As a team, you'll solve puzzles and follow mysterious clues, uncovering hidden spots in central London, whilst also competing against other teams.

      Meet us at 14:30 by the Robert Raikes Statue (WC2R 0BP), where you'll be guided to the starting location. Don't worry about the clock—it will only begin when your team is ready! The hunt lasts 3-4 hours, with optional stops at pubs and cafes along the way. When the hunt ends, join us for food, drinks, and prizes for the winning team. Extra points if you take on the challenge with your DoCSoc family! Ready to explore London and crack the clues? Let the Halloween hunt begin!

      ***Team sizes must be between 3 to 6 people, this is strict.*** Start times for each team will be staggered.

      ***Note: All game participants must have phone numbers that are contactable by UK phones via WhatsApp. If you have a non-UK number, please make sure to include the correct calling code. Team captains must have a supported phone number from the following countries: UK, US, CA, AUS, NZ, DE, FR, ES, NL, PT.***
    
      ## Ticket information:

      **Please read all the ticket information before making a purchase. Tickets must be bought by one person on behalf of their group.**

      ***Tickets are £10, and release TODAY @ 18:00!***

      Be sure to grab yours early, as we have only a limited number available!

      As with all DoCSoc Ticketed Events, you must successfully reserve a ticket on ticket tailor before also purchasing it on the Union Shop within 24 hours. Failure to do both will result in you losing your reservation.

      If you are attending as a pair or group (up to 6 people), **only 1 person should reserve and buy all the tickets for your entire group!** Please ensure that everyone can attend and know their details (full name, short code, phone number) before you reserve the tickets. Please ensure you purchase the same &amp; full amount of tickets on the Union Shop as you reserve on TicketTailor. You will be on the same team. 


      **Before you reserve as a team (3-6 people), make sure you have**:

      - Details of every member (full name, short code, phone number)
      - A designated team captain that has a supported phone number (see above)
      - A team name
      
      If you are attending alone or as a pair, then you will be allocated a team.

      All attendees must have DoCSoc membership, otherwise your reservation and ticket(s) will be invalid. Computing, JMC and EIE students are automatically members of DoCSoc. Membership can be purchased online for £30. You may purchase membership after reserving on TicketTailor (but before purchasing on the Union Shop).

      Tickets can be obtained [here](https://buytickets.at/docsoc/1444584/r/mailshot)

      If you have any questions or queries, please drop us an email at: docsoc@ic.ac.uk
    </text>
  </event>


  <sign name="Aidan Madge"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '24/25">
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>

</email>
