<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="Welcome to DoCSoc!" agenda="false" logos="false">
  <!-- <image width="90"
    src="Image-URL"
    alt="Alt-text"
    title="Title"/>
  <hr/> -->

  <heading>Welcome to the Department of Computing!</heading>

  <text>
    Whether you are a new first year or a returning
    student, this is your first weekly digest of the year.
    This is an intro to who we are, what we do, what you can expect from us and some info about freshers events.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>What is DoCSoc?</heading>
  <text>
    We are one of the most active
    societies at Imperial College with £200,000/yr to spend and weekly social, academic and sponsor events. Our aim is to bring together
    all students in the Computing community, as well as provide students with
    amazing opportunities from our sponsors!
    As a student in the Department of Computing, you get automatic membership of DoCSoc and free access to all of our sponsors, events and free goodies.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Who are we?</heading>
  <text>
    Your DoCSoc committee are elected by you at the end of each year and do all the work running DoCSoc. This year they are:
    - **President**: Hashir Majeed
    - **Vice President**: Kishan Sambhi
    - **Treasurer**: Adi Prabs
    - **Hackathons Coordinator**: Tanvi Rana
    - **Secretary**: Aidan Madge
    - **Academic Events Coordinator**: Angad Kalra
    - **Sponsors' Liaisons and Industrial Events Coordinators**: Prabhas Vedagiri, Adithya Narayanan
    - **Marketing &amp; Publicity Officers**: Kevin Wang, Anna Votin
    - **Social Events Coordinator**: Marilyn Biju
    - **Events Officers**: Royce Chan, Callum Firth, Shivit Kapoor, Serene Liu
    - **Software Development Coordinator**: Charles Calzia
    - **Postgraduate Officer**: Prabhas Vedagiri
    - **Webmasters**: Nishant Jalan, Jay Abussaud
    
    If you want to get in contact with us about problems or with suggestions please email us at
    [docsoc@imperial.ac.uk](mailto:docsoc@imperial.ac.uk).

    You will also be supported by your departmental representatives (dep reps)
    who are responsible for representing the student body (you!) to the
    department. This year they are:

    - **Computing** – Academic : Prabhas Vedagiri
    [(email)](mailto:prabhas.vedagiri22@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **Computing** – Wellbeing: Adi Prabs
    [(email)](mailto:aditya.prabakaran23@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **JMC** – Academic: Daichi Kahtava
    [(email)](mailto:daichi.kahtava22@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **JMC** – Wellbeing: DaHyeon Lee
    [(email)](mailto:chris.lee22@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **EIE** – Academic: Daniel Coroama
    [(email)](mailto:daniel.coroama21@imperial.ac.uk)
    - **EIE** – Wellbeing: Danial Dehghan
    [(email)](mailto:danial.dehghan22@imperial.ac.uk)

    If you have any academic or wellbeing related queries, your dep reps are
    the people you can talk to.
    You'll be able to run for and elect your year reps soon too, in the autumn elections!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>What do we do?</heading>

  <text>
    We at DoCSoc are very passionate about our annual events. Here's what
    to expect:

    - **Talks and workshops** - DoCSoc runs many engaging and interactive talks
    and workshops together with our sponsors, usually in the evenings after
    lectures. (Don't confuse these
    with the Department's Applications of Computing in Industry talks.) You can
    expect announcements of these next week.

    - **Sponsors' Exhibition** - One of our biggest events, where you can meet
    our sponsors and interact with them in a friendly
    atmosphere. More details coming soon!

    - **IC Hack** - Imperial College's flagship hackathon is one of our biggest
    and most successful events and is the largest student run hackathon in the UK! For 24 hours
    we take over the campus to create the most amazing hacking atmosphere for
    our attendees, while running mini-events and workshops like karaoke, a treasure hunt, bingo and a barnight! Lots of
    coding, prizes, food and fun is guaranteed! Check out last year's montage
    [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CCASs8BVKGA).

    - **Barnights** - Twice a term we'll host a barnight at the Union bar with free (yes, free!)
    drinks and a great atmosphere to relax and socialise with your friends.    

    Throughout the year we also host a wide range of social events (like pub
    quizzes, games nights, pottery, ice skating) and academic events. Do you have suggestions for
    events? We're always looking for feedback so feel free to email us with
    anything you have in mind!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>What's happening next?</heading>
  <text>
  If you're a new first year look forward to our welcome talks
  and the traditional 'Feed the Freshers' event. You'll also see another
  email from me soon, where you can sign up for DoCSoc Mums and Dads! 

  Look out for our first weekly digest next weekend where we'll announce
  our first events and the DoCSoc Sponsors Exhibition, plus the Freshers Merch and first
  Mums and Dads event.
  </text>

  <sign name="Aidan Madge"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '24/25">
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>
</email>
