<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="DoCSoc Weekly Digest" agenda="true" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We're back again, more sponsor events, a pizza party and an escape room. What more could you want?
  </text>
  
  <hr/>

  <text>## This Week's Events</text>
  
  <hr/>

  <heading>HRT Sponsor Event</heading>
  <event startDate="2024-11-11T18:00:00"
    endDate="2024-11-11T20:00:00"
    location="Clore Lecture Theatre (Huxley)">
    <text>
      At this DoCSoc x AlgoSoc event, we'll be hosting one of our sponsors, Hudson River Trading, for a tech talk. 

      Sign up [here](https://events.hrt.careers/iclttf24)!
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/qkuEorB.jpg"></image>
  <heading>Marshall Wace Sponsor Event</heading>
  <event startDate="2024-11-12T18:00:00"
    endDate="2024-11-12T20:00:00"
    location="Clore Lecture Theatre (Huxley)">
    <text>
      At Marshall Wace we make extensive use of stream processing technology in order to build systems that process data quickly and at a huge scale (millions of events per second). This talk explains the basics of stream processing and the dataflow model, how it differs from traditional data processing, challenges involved, and where it works well (or doesn't!). No prior knowledge of distributed systems or real time data processing is expected! Knowing what a database is and the basics of any programming language is helpful.
      
      If you'd like to come, signup [here](https://buytickets.at/docsoc/1456355/r/mailshot)!
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/XO8XCXL.jpg"></image>
  <heading>November Pizza Party</heading>
  <event startDate="2024-11-15T18:00:00"
    endDate="2024-11-15T20:00:00"
    location="Huxley 341/342">
    <text>
      Free pizza for all DoCSoc members! Come along to celebrate the end of pintos, midterm exams or just to eat pizza. Looking forward to seeing everyone there!

      Sign up [here](undefined)!
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/tYm1PqL.jpg"></image>
  <heading>Escape Room</heading>
  <event startDate="2024-11-20T15:00:00"
    endDate="2024-11-20T19:00:00"
    location="Clue Quest (near Kings Cross)">
    <text>
      Ready to put your wits to the test? Gather your DoCSoc family and friends for an immersive escape room experience with ClueQuest, one of London’s top-rated escape room companies! Work together to solve puzzles, crack codes, and uncover hidden clues to escape before the clock runs out.

      Meet us at ClueQuest in King's Cross, where teams will gather and be briefed before the challenge begins. Teams will be competing to see who can escape their room the fastest. The games are designed for all skill levels, so whether you’re a seasoned escape room fan or a first-timer, there’s plenty of fun and mystery for everyone! 

      Event takes place next Wednesday 20th November over 2 timeslots at 15:00 and 17:00. You will be assigned and notified your time slot after allocation takes place. Team sizes have to be between 3 to 6 people and teams will be allocated an escape room based on previous experience. Tickets cost £7.50 per person and go live Wednesday 13th November at 15:00pm.

      Sign up [here](https://buytickets.at/docsoc/1465319/r/mailshot).
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Student Society/Project/Event Showcase</text>

  <text>
    Every week or so we'll be showcasing a cool student society, project or event. Please email us if you want your cool society/project/event to be featured!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/0iE4wDp.jpg"></image>
  <heading>Y Combinator @ ICL</heading>
  <text>
    Y Combinator at Imperial College London. Tom Blomfield, co-founder of Monzo and group partner at YC, will share his founding story and answer questions based on his experience and what he's seen from advising YC startups. Time for Q&amp;A and a reception will follow.

    Tuesday, November 26 at 5:30pm

    Sign up [here](https://events.ycombinator.com/ycaticl-2024).
  </text>
  

  <sign name="Aidan Madge"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '24/25">
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>

</email>
