<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<email title="DoCSoc Weekly Digest" agenda="true" logos="false">

  <text>
    Hi everyone!

    We're almost there! Final exams will be over in a week so we're bringing you a chill event in Kew Gardens to relax, a host of opportunities from our sponsors and, of course, some merch.
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <text>## Announcements</text>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/5Fxb8Sp.jpg"></image>
  <heading>Cargo Trousers Pre-Order Second Release!</heading>
  <text>
    Due to popular demand, we're launching an extra release of the Cargo Trousers pre-order, at wholesale price of just £14.50 each. Sales will close at noon on Wednesday so make sure to grab one asap!

    Buy [here](https://www.imperialcollegeunion.org/shop/csp/computing/docsoc-cargos-preorder-full-price).

    Keep an eye out, the rest of the lineup is coming soon!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>DoCSoc Discussions - Slides</heading>
  <text>    
    Thanks to everyone who came to DoCSoc Discussions - "Are We Heading Towards Doomsday?" last week, and thanks to Nathan Bailey for presenting!

    We had a few requests for the slides so we've put them up [here](https://drive.google.com/file/d/13xSDMUugbkfuUp3mDbHMQ3vlBB85a-5W/view?usp=sharing).
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Optiver Chess Championship</heading>
  <text>    
    From Optiver:

    We're thrilled to announce that registration is now open for the third edition of the Optiver Chess Championship!

    Take part in the virtual qualifiers and compete for a chance to reach the live finals in Amsterdam—where the top players will challenge Grandmaster Anish Giri or International Master Eline Roebers.

    Virtual Qualifiers
    🗓 Date: Monday, 23 June | 19:00-21:30 (CEST)
    🌐 Platform: Lichess.org
    🏆 Format: Choose from three skill-level categories—or compete in the new women's-only bracket!

    👉 Register [here](https://optiver.com/recruitment-events/optiver-chess-championship/) by Tuesday, 18 June at 23:59 CEST to secure your spot in the online qualifiers

    We can't wait to see your next move!
  </text>

  <hr/>

  <heading>QuantCo @ ICML Scholarship</heading>
  <text>    
    From QuantCo:

    We have another exciting opportunity to share - QuantCo will be attending ICML 2025 in Vancouver this July!

    As with previous years, we will invite students enrolled in a bachelor's, master's, or PhD program to apply for our fully funded travel scholarship, which includes return flights, hotel accommodation, and conference tickets. The deadline for applications is May 31st.

    Sign up [here](https://www.linkedin.com/posts/quantco_join-us-at-icml-were-excited-to-share-activity-7321168655528968194-SEMA/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;rcm=ACoAABjE8GgB5Ba5S4OGVnTPhKMkGnLu3jB8Irw).
  </text>
  
  <hr/>

  <text>## This Week's Events</text>

  <hr/>

  <image src="https://imgur.com/xzzfe2B.jpg"></image>
  <heading>DoCSoc Goes Kew Gardens</heading>
  <event startDate="2025-05-20T11:00:00"
    endDate="2025-05-20T16:00:00"
    location="Kew Gardens">
    <text>
      Time to switch up your scenaries from cheatsheets and edstem to floras and rosies 🥀 after exams
      
      Get your £5 ticket on [here](https://app.tickettailor.com/events/docsoc/1698760/r/digest) when it goes live at 17:00 on 15th May 🙂
    </text>
  </event>

  <hr/>

  <heading>Help Shape DoCSoc</heading>
  <text>
    We would love to get some feedback on some of our upcoming events we have planned for the summer term, please fill in your details here if you want to be contacted to help shape and give feedback on potential event ideas :)

    Sign up [here](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdfnNaNpLS6UCS5seB90T-3NcO-3xKYteD6-nJn7BZ9NZ2j3g/viewform?usp=dialog).
  </text>

  <hr/>
  
  <heading>DoCSoc Event Feedback Survey (Recently updated!)</heading>
  <text>
    This will be here, at the bottom of all our digests from now on. Feel free to speak your mind regarding events DoCSoc have been running so far, and also about DoCSoc in general. 
    
    Please find the link [here](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdC-21RmEP_KGDbCF7UjKbcAAYdxd4IBLhCTB9-9xfgiUy2_w/viewform?usp=sf_link)

    Individual survey results will be kept private.
  </text>

  <sign name="Aidan Madge"
    role="DoCSoc Secretary '24/25">
  </sign>
  <text>
    ![DoCSoc](https://i.imgur.com/1o6dcEV.gif)
  </text>

</email>
